Chapter 942: Zhao Hai’s Guess

Zhao Hai looked at the undead and smiled, “Is Excellency the Underworld’s Skeleton King?” The Skeleton King curiously looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Who are you? Where is this place? Why do you know my status? Are you the one that opened that spatial rift?” Zhao Hai looked at the Skeleton King and smiled faintly, “I don’t have that great of an ability. I might be able to open spatial rifts, but I can’t open rifts as large as the one you went through. And to be honest, no plane would want to open a spatial rift to the Underworld.” The Skeleton King looked at Zhao Hai and gently tilted his head. It was obvious that he was quite curious about Zhao Hai, then he said, “You are a man who is well-informed. You know that I’m the Skeleton King and that we’re from the Underworld, yet you don’t seem to be afraid. Are you strong?”

Zhao Hai slightly smiled as he said, “I have some confidence in my strength. Also, before you appeared here, I have already moved everyone, my family, my friends, as well as those who have a relationship with me. So even if you overturn the heavens here, it would still not affect me. However, I will take your subordinates away, I’m quite curious about them. I want to study them well.”

The flame in the Skeleton King’s eyes suddenly increased in intensity, he looked angry. The Skeleton King looked at Zhao Hai and spoke in a calm manner, “You want to turn us into your slaves?” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You can’t say that, but it’s about the same. I have an ability to turn all the undead I caught into my own servants.”

The flame in the Skeleton King’s eyes blazed even greater. He look straight at Zhao Hai and said, “Human, I know that you are strong, but you must die!” After speaking this, the Skeleton King reached back to his cape. When his hands came out again, two golden axes could be seen, huge golden broad axes.

The edges on these axes were like two huge semicircles with a diameter of about a meter. Engraved on the back of each blade was a skull pattern. The axe’s handle seem to be made of sections of vertebrae.

Zhao Hai looked at the Skeleton King’s appearance and couldn’t help but smile. He shook his magic staff, turning it into a sword. The appearance of this sword was just like a tang blade.

The Skeleton King looked at Zhao Hai’s sword with curiosity. However, he didn’t say anything as his figure moved and, just like a tornado, swung himself towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai discovered that the Skeleton King’s movements were very unusual. His whole person was continuously brandishing the two axes as he revolved. With the rotation as well as the weight of the axes, the force exerted by each axe was evidently astonishing.

However, at Zhao Hai’s level, this kind of attack wasn’t a threat. The weight of the weapon itself was useless against Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai waved his sword in order to block the axes.

Bang! A huge force rang through the tang blade. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be stunned. He didn’t expect the strength of the Skeleton King to be this strong. Even with his strength, he could still feel the impact of the attack. If it was any other God-rank expert, then they surely wouldn’t be able to receive it.

But what made Zhao Hai feel strange was the fact that the Skeleton King was evidently a very strong God-rank expert. He might have even reached the upper ranks of God-rank. However, the Skeleton King didn’t use a Domain, which puzzled Zhao Hai.

Still, the other party wasn’t useless even without using a Domain. After blocking the enemy’s attack, Zhao Hai’s body moved and went on to retreat.

However, the Skeleton King kept attacking Zhao Hai. This was where Zhao Hai discovered that the Skeleton King’s revolving attacks weren’t only used to amplify his attacks, but it also allowed him to attack repeatedly. Each attack was linked, tightly connected that even if the enemy steps back they would still be met with an attack. Zhao Hai was in this situation. The Skeleton King looked like a tornado spinning towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai saw this situation and knew that he couldn’t drag this on. He transformed his tang blade into a huge shield as he placed it in front of him to block.

The Skeleton King didn’t expect Zhao Hai to use this move, he didn’t think that Zhao Hai’s weapon could become this big. But the Skeleton King didn’t stop, he continued to revolve towards Zhao Hai, seeking a flaw in his defense.

Zhao Hai held his huge shield on one hand, and suddenly a red blade appeared on the other. The blade had a thick back, making it quite heavy. Naturally, this blade was made from the blood ghost staff. As Zhao Hai grasped his shield, he brandished his blade to attack the Skeleton King.

Finally, the Skeleton King’s rhythm was disrupted. At this time, Zhao Hai used his shield to smash towards the Skeleton King. Unable to bear the impact, the Skeleton King drew back several steps. Zhao Hai used this opportunity to jump out of the Skeleton King’s range. The shield and blade vanished as they returned to being the blood ghost staff.

Zhao Hai looked at the Skeleton King and smiled, “Your Excellency, I still have some matters to attend to, so I couldn’t fight with you for a long time. When I have time later on, I will certainly ask your Excellency for advice.” After saying this, his body immediately vanished.

Although they had only fought for a short time, Zhao Hai actually felt that the Skeleton King was very formidable. If he wanted to deal with the Skeleton King, then he would have to exert some effort. Because of this, he chose to retreat.

Since the clash was very short, Lewis and the others were unable to notice anything as they fought with the undead.

Upon seeing Zhao Hai vanish, the Skeleton King’s eyes couldn’t help but blaze up more vigorously. It can be said that the Skeleton King was truly angered by Zhao Hai. Then he turned to look at Theo’s group who were still fighting with the golden undead. The axes disappeared from his hand before he waved to his subordinates. Then a small number of crystal undead flew out and directly  threw themselves towards Lewis and the others.

At this point, Lewis and the others could neither run nor fight. Since this was the case, then they could only drag on. They knew that their base wasn’t far away. They were hoping that someone would be able to see their situation and send some support. Otherwise, they would surely be in extreme danger.

Fortunately, Lewis’ hopes came true. From their base’s direction, a thousand magic armors suddenly began to head out.

But at this time, the crystal skeletons were already near and had initiated their attack. This began an exchange that made Theo and the others feel chills. They didn’t expect the undead to be this violent, the magic armors were completely unable to block.

In a short time, four magic armors were destroyed by the crystal undead. They fell down to the ground, their pilots certainly dead.

After seeing this situation, Theo immediately made everyone throw every bomb they had. They need to resist these skeletons long enough for their reinforcements to arrive.

In the war tank, Lewis also had a similar type of bomb. He kept launching them to the point of covering the heavens and the earth. These bombs managed to keep the undead off, but they did little to no damage. However, the reinforcements had already arrived, both sides quickly began to fight each other.

With such a large movement, it was impossible for the other O’Neal family members to not notice it. Before long, more and more magic armors and war tanks began to head towards the ensuing battle.

Upon seeing the situation, the Skeleton King returned to his carriage. He knew that continuing wouldn’t be good, so he waved his hand causing the undead to retreat. Then they slowly went back to the Dark Mist. Although the O’Neal family wanted to pursue, they didn’t do it in the end.

The Skeleton King didn’t go too far from the Dark Mist. Before long, his entourage was surrounded by the underworld’s fog. There were still some magic armors who decided to head into the dark mist. But since the dark mist amplified the strength of the undead, they could only be destroyed.

The O’Neal family’s general saw this situation and immediately ordered a retreat. After returning to their base, he quickly wrote a letter and had it sent to the Patriarch at the quickest speed.

After Zhao Hai returned to the Hell King’s ship, Laura immediately went to welcome him. Then she asked, “Brother Hai, how was it? Is that really the Skeleton King? Was he strong?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “He’s indeed the Skeleton King, and he’s very strong. Even if the Supreme Elders use their ultimate weapons, they might not necessarily be his match. Moreover, I suspect he is just like the O’Neal family. They weren’t governed by Lu Wei.”

Zhao Hai said this as he entered the room. Lizzy and Megan were currently directing the undead to deal with the Pisces Divines. They were now having a much easier time since they now have a lot more ranged undead. All of these new additions came from the Sagittarius Continent. Now, they were all Zhao Hai’s people. The Space also increased their strength. So it was no wonder that the Pisces Divines simply couldn’t block their assault.

This was exactly where Zhao Hai’s abilities shone when fighting against people. His subordinates would only increase while the enemies number less and less. In this case, he naturally had the upper hand.

Seeing that Lizzy and Megan where wholly absorbed in their task, Zhao Hai decided to not disturb them. He looked for a place to sit down inside the room, then Meg offered him tea to drink. After that Laura said, “Brother Hai, how are you sure that they weren’t managed by Lu Wei?”

Zhao Hai replied, “This is just a feeling. It’s quite obvious that Lu Wei has handed this plane over to the Divines. Then he used the Divines to conquer other planes. However, the strength of the Underworld is obviously stronger than the Divines. If the Underworld was also under Lu Wei’s control, then why would he need to support the Divine Race? A territory only needs one King. If the Underworld was controlled by Lu Wei, and he still supported the Divines, then doesn’t it seem wrong? Moreover, have you noticed? The Divines as well as its contemporaries used Domains in order to fight. At the same time, even other races would used Domains during battles. I suspect that this is a feature of the planes being managed by Lu Wei. When I fought against the Skeleton King, he didn’t use his Domain.” Laura nodded, then she said, “So you mean that since the Divines changed the laws of the Ark Continent, they managed to connect two other planes that weren’t under Lu Wei’s control?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That is the most likely case. If that is so, then the Cultivation World might be more complex than we thought. Think about it, Lu Wei forbade anyone from studying magic armors. Magic armors belong to type of technological civilization. From this point, we can roughly infer that Lu Wei had some relationship with people using magic armors, or he might have a hatred against technological civilizations. The case of the Underworld is much more complicated. Almost all energy in the Underworld is dark and toxic. I can remember that there are demonic influences in the Cultivation Realm. And since Lu Wei is from an orthodox sect, he would have a grudge against them. Now that these three planes were connected together, I’m afraid things wouldn’t turn out well.”

Laura knit her brows and said, “Brother Hai, you mean this thing might cause some chaos in the Cultivation Realm?” Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “As for its effect, I don’t know. But from what I can see, since the planes are divided, those who ascend would have a mark of the planes where they came from. And since we have a grudge against Lu Wei, we would be marked by Lu Wei’s group when we ascend. I’m afraid that we would be chased down when that time comes.”

Laura’s expression couldn’t help but change upon hearing Zhao Hai. With an anxious voice she said, “Brother Hai, so what do we do? Can we do anything? Will our situation be even more difficult after we ascend?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “I’m afraid it can only be like this. But I still want to see what happens if we ascend in either the Atlanta Plane or the Underworld. Will we still be marked by Lu Wei? As long as we can temporarily avoid Lu Wei’s detection, then with the Space’s abilities, we would be able to have a stable foothold in the Cultivation Realm. When the time comes, it would be impossible for Lu Wei to deal with us.”

Chapter 943: The Hard to Deal With Gemini and Aquarius Continents

Laura didn’t think that Zhao Hai would have such thoughts. She looked puzzled as Zhao Hai as she asked, “Brother Hai, how did you come up with such ideas?’

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Just after fighting the Skeleton King. The Skeleton King reminded me that the Underworld and the Atlanta Plane weren’t managed by Lu Wei. After we ascend, we might not be far from Lu Wei, but we might end up in his enemy. If Lu Wei wanted to deal with us, it won’t be very easy.”

Laura nodded and said, “That would be the case if that is true. It’s worth trying. But Brother Hai, isn’t the energy inside your body increasing? With so many things left unsolved, what will happen if you suddenly ascend?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Then I could only count on a reserve plan. I think the Atlanta Plane would be good. Since I had this idea, we might as well pick this direction and go. What we have to do right now is to settle things we needed to settle before we go.”

Laura nodded before she turned her head. She looked at Lizzy and Megan’s progress in commanding the undead to deal with the Pisces Divines.

Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about Lizzy and Megan. Without their Supreme Elder to help, the Pisces Divines could only fall to the undead.

Sure enough, just like what Zhao Hai thought, Lizzy and Megan were able to deal with the Pisces Divines with little effort. At this time, Zhao Hai was carrying a few undead in order to deal with another continent.

Upon seeing that there were no issues in the Pisces Continent, Zhao Hai turned his head to Laura and said, “Since there are no problems in the Pisces Continent, should we go on to the next step?” Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “What does Brother Hai plan to do?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Aren’t the foreign races sending their army? Since we’re doing well, we should prepare to support them. With the help of the foreign races, we would be able to deal with the Supreme Elders. As long as we dealt with the Supreme Elders, we can then start making a move on the O’Neal family. Now that the Underworld has began to make moves, we need to settle our plans a little bit faster.”

Laura nodded then said, “Brother Hai, how about this. Since we have enough numbers in our hands, it would be better for us to attack two Continents at once. This way, we would be able to deal with the Divines as soon as possible. The Leo Continent is currently being left to the foreign races. As long as the Supreme Elders know that the Divines have been extinguished and that the Leo Continent was being conquered by the foreign races, then they will certainly settle accounts with the foreign races. At that time, we can clean them up and take their combat suits.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “Then we’ll deal with two Continents at once. Right, we need to study the Continent we’ll attack next.”

As Zhao Hai was researching his next target, the O’Neal family began to worry about one matter.

In the past, they only needed to think about the dark mist’s expansion. But now it was different, the undead has started to venture out. Moreover, their fighting strength was very formidable. And this was only a small group! If more of these undead come out, how would the O’Neal family deal with it?

It was because of this that the people in the Aksu Empire’s defensive line immediately sent a letter to the family. And while waiting for the family’s reply, the defensive line became even more careful. The patrols sent at night had increased a lot.

They were clear that the undead would have reduced strength during the day. But in night, they would be strengthened. The undead that came out this time went out during the day, and the O’Neal family already had difficult time dealing with them. If they came out during the night, how powerful would they be?

The O’Neal family’s northern defensive line became more vigilant than before. They didn’t want to fall under the undead’s blade.

Sending reports back to the O’Neal family was now faster than before. This was due to the Patriarch’s arrangements. Between the northern defensive line and the Divine Realm’s spatial rift were a lot supply stations. They could now send magic armors to send their letters since they could just resupply at these supply stations.

The reason why the Patriarch did this was because they need to make the communication more convenient. The Patriarch knew too well how important communication was when it came to the family’s operations.

When the letter reached his table, the Patriarch couldn’t help but get stunned. He never thought that an accident would happen in the northern defensive line this soon. This caused the final hesitation on his heart to disappear.

When he received Axe’s report, the Patriarch still had some reservations. Must they really risk moving their operation to the plane that Axe discovered? In any case, they already found their enemy in that plane. If they left the Ark Continent now, wouldn’t it be a waste? But this letter finally made the Patriarch determined to shift the family’s focus to the south.

The reason why the O’Neal Patriarch thought about this was because their headquarters was already much closer to the south. Therefore, it would be fine to shift the family’s focus there. Additionally, the Dark Mist had become much more dangerous. The Patriarch also knew that there seem to be no immediate danger in the plane that Axe discovered. Moreover, that plane was much bigger than the Ark Continent, which was important for the O’Neal family.

Therefore, upon receiving the news from the north, the Patriarch immediately sent a family elder in order to observe the plan that Axe discovered.

The Patriarch was still quite worried about Axe. After all, Axe wasn’t very successful in the beginning. He just listened to Zhao Hai’s words and returned home prematurely. He didn’t take the time and see the Ark Continent for himself. If he made the effort to scout the Ark Continent beforehand, the O’neal family would not have been in an embarrassing situation in the beginning.

Although he had decided to develop the south, the O’Neal family didn’t relax their surveillance over the northern part of the continent. The undead were too strong, the O’Neal family needed to be careful.

Just as the O’Neal family was preparing to move to the Divine Realm, the foreign races arrived at the Leo Continent. Recently, the atmosphere of the Leo Continent was becoming more and more tense. Ever since Zhao Hai’s attack, the Leo Divines have always waited for him to come back. Once he did, they would surely teach him a lesson.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t go to the Leo Continent, instead he destroyed the other continents one by one. This caused the Leo Divines to feel even more terrified. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this strong.

But the Leo Continent didn’t forget that they were members of the Divine Race. This caused the fire inside them to blaze more and more. As they were preparing to go all out against Zhao Hai, the foreign races’ attack came.

The Divines and the foreign races had a grudge, but just as the Leo Divines weren’t having a good time, the foreign races came to attack. This made the Leo Divines even more angry. A great battle between the foreign races and the Leo Divines quickly ensued.

The foreign race army was a coalition between three continents. They numbered more than 50 million in total. And since the Leo Divines had the territorial advantage, they already had an army prepared. Additionally, compared to the the foreign races, the Leo Divines had the help of the Fishman race. Because of this, both sides were at fairly equal states.

Naturally, Zhao Hai was aware of this situation. At this point, besides the Leo Continent, only the Gemini Continent and the Aquarius Continent was left, the other Continents were destroyed by Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai was now preparing to deal with the two remaining continents.

After carefully researching the Gemini and Aquarius Continents, Zhao Hai discovered that they were the most difficult continents to deal with.

It wasn’t strange for Zhao Hai to just know about this at this time. He didn’t know much about the Divine Realm. He was unaware about the various groups in the Divine Realm and what they were good at. It was only after he met these people did he know their abilities.

The Gemini and Aquarius Continents were difficult to deal with because they had their own unique abilities. The Gemini Divines were really worthy of their name. The number of twins in the Gemini Continent was much higher compared to the other continents. In ten households, five of them would have twins as their offsprings. It was a quite surprising statistic.

Because these twins grew together and trained together, they were able to have a tacit understanding about each others’ abilities. This boosted their strengths compared to any other paired groups. Because of this, the Gemini Divines were very well known to be very hard to fight against.

On the other hand, the Aquarius Divines were also quite formidable. They don’t have a lot of twins, but what made the Aquarius Divines very hard to deal with were their extreme talent for potions. They had potions that were very strange and unusual, with endless functions and uses. They could poison a person, or heal them, they could enhance one’s cultivation or just cure common illnesses. Because of their potions, the Aquarius Divines were known to be people one wouldn’t want to provoke. They had a similar status as the Dark Mages back in the Ark Continent.

Chapter 944: The Proud Winged Pegasus Patriarch

Actually, the various Divines in each Continent had their own characteristics. Although they were collectively called the Divine Race, each group actually had various qualities. The Gemini Divines had a lot of twins, the Aquarius Divines use potions, the Central Divines were the most arrogant, the Leo Divines were the most domineering, and etc. Some of these characteristics can be seen immediately while some were seen later on.

In the past, Zhao Hai wasn’t very familiar with these. But after dealing with the other Divines, he learned that each Divine group were terrifying in their own way.

The people in the Central Continent might look elegant in the surface, but they were also very arrogant. They wouldn’t get offended over ordinary things, after all, they were Central Divines. With their identity, it would be too below them to be offended by the smallest of things.

After Zhao Hai destroyed the Connecting Heaven Palace, the Central Divines turned insane, this was because of their arrogance. They couldn’t bear such a blow. They were like Princes being held down by a mere beggar. They couldn’t stomach such an insult.

After seeing the foreign races clash with the Leo Divines, Zhao Hai did intend to intervene. He wanted the foreign races to meddle in order to distract the nine Supreme Elders. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai would be dealing with the Gemini and Aquarius Continent.

Although it was said that the Gemini and Aquarius Continent were very hard to deal with, they weren’t that formidable for Zhao Hai. The Gemini Divines might pose a challenge, but the Aquarius Divines were nothing to Zhao Hai.

The Aquarius Divines use potions, but Zhao Hai’s subordinates were undead. The undead creatures were mostly immune to the potions of the Aquarius Divines. Because of this, the Aquarius Divines weren’t in Zhao Hai’s view. The more difficult ones were the Gemini Divines.

Twin Gemini Divines had great understanding of each other, which made them difficult to deal with. The power of twin Geminis outweigh the power of three people. Because of this, most of Zhao Hai’s attention was focused on the Gemini Continent.

Although the Gemini Divines were a bit difficult to deal with, Zhao Hai still wasn’t worried. After all, he had the superiority in numbers.

At this time, the Barbarians had completely moved to the Space. Meanwhile, the Winged Pegasus were still fighting against the Supreme Elders.

Along this span of time, the disadvantage of the Supreme Elders’ ultimate armors were beginning to show. Unlike Zhao Hai’s undead who could attack day and night, the Supreme Elders needed to stop once in a while. Therefore, their assault on the Winged Pegasus Clan wasn’t going very smoothly.

The nine Supreme Elders had truly overestimated themselves. In their opinion, Zhao Hai alone wouldn’t be able to completely deal with the Divine Race territory.

However, they’ve forgotten about one point. Zhao Hai had more than 1 billion undead in his hands. On the other hand, they were only nine people. With this disparity, it would be hard for them to keep up.

This didn’t mean that the Winged Pegasus were their match. But the Winged Pegasus were able to entangle them, even if the Supreme Elders weren’t paying any hard sacrifices.

In the first few battles against the Supreme Elders, the Winged Pegasus suffered heavy casualties since they didn’t understand the Supreme Elders. However, even if this was the case, this wouldn’t remain forever. The Winged Pegasus weren’t stupid. After a few more battles, they were able to find means to deal with the Supreme Elders.

After a while, the Winged Pegasus found ways to entangle the Supreme Elders. They would approach the Supreme Elders in a loose formation so that the Supreme Elders would have to fight for a longer time. Because of this, when the Supreme Elders retreated, the Winged Pegasus didn’t suffer very large losses. This also made the Winged Pegasus Patriarch more and more confident.

At this time, the Barbarian Patriarch appeared in the Winged Pegasus Plane along with Shan and the others. The Barbarian Patriarch didn’t regret moving to the Space. The environment inside was much better compared to their previous place. This made the Barbarians very happy. After settling for a bit, he immediately went with Shan to the Winged Pegasus Plane.

Shan was anxious since he knew that they didn’t have much time. The O’Neal family had entered the Divine Plance, but Zhao Hai was still dealing with the Divines. Even if the Winged Pegasus were able to block the nine Supreme Elders, they could still be attacked by the O’Neal family. Shan didn’t have confidence in the Winged Pegasus when it came to defending against the O’Neal family.

Upon knowing these facts, Shan badly wanted his people to enter the Space as soon as possible. Shan also knew why Zhao Hai didn’t offer any more help, and he couldn’t blame Zhao Hai for it.

Besides Shan’s group, the Barbarian Patriarch only brought 20 Barbarian guards along. However, when they came out of the room, they immediately attracted the attention of the Winged Pegasus members. Before long, they were encircled.

Shan was fearless as he looked at these people and said, “Let us pass, the Barbarian Patriarch is here for a visit.”

Upon hearing this, the Winged Pegasus couldn’t help but freeze for a moment. They didn’t expect Shan to be calm in this situation. And since the Barbarians were too imposing, the crowd immediately opened a path for them to go through.

The other Winged Pegasus looked at Shan with complication gazes. Shan’s reputation in the clan was very high in the past. A lot of people were optimistic about him. But now, he was seen as a criminal. And through the continuous propaganda by the Patriarch, Shan had become someone who wanted to sell their entire clan into slavery.

Shan didn’t care about the looks his clansmen were giving him. After talking with Zhao Hai, his mind has been opened up. Just like Zhao Hai said, there’s no need to worry about how they saw him, as long as he was doing the right thing. All Shan had to do was do what he thought was correct.

Shan and the others didn’t stop and walked towards the Pegasus Clan’s Grand Hall. Upon arriving, they saw the Winged Pegasus Patriarch in the entrance preparing to meet the Barbarian Patriarch. No matter what, the Barbarians were their close allies, the Winged Pegasus Patriarch had to give face.

Upon seeing the Barbarian Patriarch, the Winged Pegasus Patriarch immediately gave his greeting, “Brother Jinsong, you actually have time to visit us? Please, come inside.” The Winged Pegasus Patriarch didn’t even spare Shan a glance, he just treated him as though he didn’t exist. This attitude showed the Winged Pegasus Patriarch’s current thought.

Jinson looked at the Winged Pegasus Patriarch and laughed, “Brother Yifei is too polite. There’s no need for you to meet us outside.”

Before long, the group arrived inside the Assembly Hall. Inside the hall were Winged Pegasus members who held certain status. They were already inside waiting to welcome Patriarch Jinsong. The banquet has been set up, Patriarch Yifei even went on and personally served Jinsong.

After the dishes had been set up, Winged Pegasus Yifei took up his wine glass and said, “Brother Jinsong, your visit to the Winged Pegasus Clan truly made me happy. Unfortunately, since we are currently busy, you caught us unprepared. Please forgive me.”

Jinsong smiled faintly as he also held his wine glass up and said, “I’m aware that the Winged Pegasus are in a special situation. Brother Yifei’s preparation actually exceeded my expectations. Brother Yifei doesn’t need to be polite.”

Patriarch Yifei laughed and said, “Brother Jinsong’s words truly make me glad. In any case, the Divine Supreme Elders look very mediocre. They wouldn’t be able to pose a threat to the Winged Pegasus Clan. There’s no need for Brother Jinsong to worry.”

Jinson smiled faintly, he stayed silent and only raised his glass before downing it together with Yifei. Shan held a calm expression as well. He knew that Yifei’s words were directed at him, but he didn’t care. Instead, he felt pity for Yifei. He didn’t know anything yet he was acting as though he had everything in control.

Yifei gave Shan an emotionless gaze. He knew that he couldn’t do anything to Shan at this time. However, he thought that Shan was here because he asked Jinsong a favor in order to let him back into the Winged Pegasus Clan. The Winged Pegasus Patriarch plans to accept in order to show his magnanimity.

After drinking his wine, Yifei went straight to the point as he turned to Jinsong and said, “Brother Jinsong, are you here just to share a drink with me? If Brother Jinsong needs anything, then please don’t hold back.”

Barbarian Jinsong looked at Patriarch Yifei and said, “Brother might not believe me, but I really did want to visit the Winged Pegasus a long time ago. But since there were a lot of recent matters I need to take care of, I only had the chance today. However, there is indeed one thing I came here for. Brother Yifei, I hope that you can agree to move the Winged Pegasus to mister Zhao Hai’s Space.”

Upon hearing Jinsong say this, Yifei couldn’t help but get shocked. He didn’t expect Jinsong to persuade them about this matter. This was completely in the opposite direction of what he thought. After he gawked for a moment, Yifei’s expression changed, “Brother Jinsong, are you cracking a joke? Why would I enter Mister Zhao Hai’s Space? The divine Supreme Elders have no means to deal with us right now. Why would I subject myself to being a slave?!”

Jinsong looked at Yifei and said, “Brother Yifei, can you really completely defend against the Supreme Elders? The Supreme Elders have yet to go all out. Once they do so, things won’t be this easy anymore.”

Chapter 945: Selfishness That Leads to Insanity

Patriarch Yifei looked at Jinsong and said, “Brother Jinsong, what are you saying? Are you looking down on my Winged Pegasus Clan?”

Jinsong shook his head and said, “I’m not. The Winged Pegasus and the Barbarians have been allies for a long time, so I’m very clear about the strength of the Winged Pegasus. However, there’s something that Brother Yifei doesn’t know. Mister Zhao Hai has already eliminated the Central Divines, Cancer Divines, Capricorn Divines, Sagittarius Divines, and the Taurus Divines. He is now planning to deal with the other continents. At the same time, the foreign races are also planning to deal with the Leo Divines. If the Supreme Elders come to know about this, they will certainly go all out in dealing with the Winged Pegasus. Brother Yifei, are you really confident in dealing with the Supreme Elders?”

When he heard Jinsong, Yifei’s expression couldn’t help but change. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai would have the strength to deal with several continents.

Patriarch Yifei was clear about how the Divines would seek revenge upon this grievance. If they knew about this matter, they would definitely go mad. When the time comes, can the Winged Pegasus really block their attack? Yifei wasn’t too confident about this, after all the strength of the Supreme Elders were well known.

Patriarch Jinsong looked at Yifei and said, “Brother Yifei, to tell you the truth, I wasn’t able to come here earlier because I was busy moving my people to Mister Zhao Hai’s Space. We’ve just finished moving recently. The environment inside the Space is very good. We won’t need to worry about fighting, we won’t worry about eating and drinking as well. And if we want something, we can earn it with our own hands…..”

“Shut up!”

Jinsong didn’t even finish talking as he was interrupted by Yifei. He looked at Jinsong and said, “The decisions of the Barbarian Clan is the Barbarian Clan’s matter. The Winged Pegasus will never enter Mister Zhao Hai’s Space and become slaves. How strong could the Divines be? Up until now, they had yet to deal with us.”

Initially, Yifei was expressionless as he listened to Jinsong’s words. But suddenly a thought passed through his mind, “If we enter Zhao Hai’s Space now, then wouldn’t he look like a joke to Shan?” It was because of this that he decided to interrupt Jinsong.

Even after hearing Yifei, Jinsong didn’t give up, he sighed and said, “Brother Yifei, let me tell you, in the past, Mister Zhao Hai asked us to help him deal with the O’Neal family. Now, the O’Neal family has entered the Taurus Continent. It’s possible that they would discover our three planes soon. Brother Yifei, do you really want to plunge the Winged Pegasus War into endless fighting?”

When he heard Jinsong, Yifei’s expression turned angrier. He looked at Jinsong and said, “Is Brother Jinsong serious? Didn’t Mister Zhao Hai say that he will block the O’Neal family by entering the spatial rift?”

Upon hearing Yifei, Shan’s expression changed. Yifei already didn’t give Zhao Hai any face and doubted everything. But now, he decided to trust Zhao Hai about this matter, how thick can one’s face be?

Jinsong also despised Yifei, but he didn’t show it. He only replied, “Mister wanted to compel the Supreme Elders to return, so he had to withdraw majority of his troops away from the spatial rift. Moreover, there are a lot more O’Neal family troops this time. They were able to easily rush through the defense.”

Yifei looked at Jinsong and asked, “Brother Jinsong, this information, where did you get it from?”

Jinsong replied, “It’s from Mister Zhao Hai. What’s wrong?”

Yifei laughed and said, “Of course there’s something wrong. That’s a serious problem. Why would I believe the words that Mister Zhao Hai spoke? He just said this to deceive us into moving towards his Space.”

Jinsong stared, he never expected Yifei to say such words. At this point, why would Zhao Hai deceive them? What kind of person would actually think like this.

Jinsong quickly replied, “Brother Yifei, I’m afraid Mister Zhao Hai would not use this to deceive us. If the O’Neal family really arrives, then what would you do?”

Yifei waved his hand and said, “So what if the O’Neal family arrives? I don’t believe that they are stronger than the nine Supreme Elders. We managed to block the Supreme Elders, so why do we need to fear the O’Neal family? Brother Jinsong, when did your Barbarian Clan turned into cowards? You actually got scared by just a few words. You became slaves for another and you still wanted to persuade me.”

When Jinsong heard this, his expression couldn’t help but change. This wasn’t only an insult to him, it was also an insult to the entire Barbarian Clan. How could Jinsong just bear with it?

Barbarian Jinsong’s brows knitted as he stood up and looked at Yifei, “Winged Pegasus Yifei, since we’re disregarding face, do you really think that your Winged Pegasus Clan could contend with the various groups of the Divine Race? Mister Zhao Hai has already cleaned many Divine Race Continents. For him to deal with you would be very easy. Why would he even try to deceive you? You shouldn’t look too highly of yourself.”

When he heard Jinsong, Yifei couldn’t help but sneer, “What? You want to scare me? If Mister Zhao Hai really wanted to destroy the Winged Pegasus Clan, then let him come.”

Jinsong looked at the rotten Yifei. After a while, he calmed down and said, “I don’t think Mister Zhao Hai has time to waste on you. Just wait until the O’Neal family and the Underworld deals with you. We’re leaving.” Then he turned around and proceeded to leave.

At this time, Yifei suddenly opened his mouth, “Coward Jinsong, do you really think you can just leave like that?”

Jinsong turned back with a fierce look on his face. A killing aura began to well up from his body as he looked at Yifei and said, “What? Yifei, you also want to capture me today?”

Yifei looked at Jinsong and sneered, “I won’t be stopping you from leaving, but Shan couldn’t go with you. He is a Winged Pegasus. Moreover, I’ve issued an arrest for him. He cannot leave.”

Jinsong looked at Yifei and sneered, “Yifei, the reason for your order of arrest, you know what it is better than anyone. You also issued an arrest for Fei’er and Ding, so you also want them to stay? Yifei, it’s not that this Jinsong is looking down on you, but if Shan and the others really did want to kill you, do you really think that you would still be alive today? As a fellow Patriarch, I will take them with me and there’s nothing you can do about it.”

Yifei looked at Jinsong and said, “Don’t forget whose territory you’re in. You actually dare to talk to me like this in my Winged Pegasus Clan? Do you really intend to leave?”

Jinsong laughed and said, “We Barbarians don’t fear death. Dying in battle would be an honor to us. You want to use death to threaten me? You’re dreaming.”

The guards were already putting on a show. Jinsong’s guards wanted to open a way to outside, but the Winged Pegasus guards wouldn’t allow them. It didn’t take long before a conflict occurred.

When the Winged Pegasus members in the Great Hall saw this situation, they couldn’t help but stare. Their expressions were very complicated. If Jinsong suffers an accident here, then the Barbarians surely wouldn’t take it lightly. The Winged Pegasus couldn’t risk having another enemy at this time.

Also, at this time, the Winged Pegasus members in the hall discovered that Patriarch Yifei had turned mad. His arrogance has been turned to insanity.

At this moment, a person suddenly appeared inside the hall. This person wore a black mage’s robe. As soon as he appeared, the place immediately turned quiet, all eyes were concentrated on him. This person was Zhao Hai.

When Zhao Hai appeared inside the hall, he looked at Patriarch Yifei as well as the Winged Pegasus members and said, “I didn’t think that even after being careful, people would still doubt this Zhao Hai. Hahaha. I want you to be my slaves? In my hands are a billion undead, why would I want to enslave you? You Winged Pegasus really think highly upon yourselves. Good, since you don’t want to enter my Space, then I won’t persuade you any longer. If you don’t enter, then you won’t enter. I won’t lose anything in any case.”

Yifei couldn’t help but stare at Zhao Hai. He had met Zhao Hai one time before, this was when they were going to deal with the Taurus Divines. At that time, the three Patriarchs visited Zhao Hai. To be honest, his impression of Zhao Hai at that time wasn’t so good. This was because Zhao Hai looked too ordinary, he had no traces of extraordinary features. This was where he started to look down on Zhao Hai.

However, he didn’t expect Zhao Hai to suddenly appear inside the Hall. After he stared for a moment, Yifei’s eyes shone, it was as if he had something on Zhao Hai. He looked at Zhao Hai and shouted, “Zhou Hai, are you really incapable of helping us? Or are you just looking at the sidelines? Tell me the truth.”

Zhao Hai looked at Yifei and smiled, “Patriarch Yifei, you are truly smart. But unfortunately, you used your intelligence in the wrong place. Correct, from the very beginning, I was capable of helping your clan. But I chose to stay and observe in the side.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai say this, the mouths of Winged Pegasus members couldn’t help but drop. The Winged Pegasus always thought that Zhao Hai had no time to save them. Now that Zhao Hai said this, it was equal to telling them that he was using the Supreme Elders to force them to enter his Space. This caused the current atmosphere to change.

Yifei proudly looked at Jinsong and the others, then he sneered, “Good, so you finally admit that you are only using the Supreme Elders to compel us to your Space, right?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Correct. I intend to use the Divine Race in order compel you to the Space.”

Yifei laughed loudly and said, “Jinsong, Fei’er, Shan, can you see this? This came from Zhao Hai’s mouth, the one you’re trying to help. Hahahaha. This is too funny.”

Jinsong looked at Yifei and sneered, “Funny? We already knew about this matter. Mister already has a lot to think about. Besides the Supreme Elders and the O’Neal family, there’s also the Underworld in the Ark Continent. The underworld’s undead aren’t any weaker compared to the Divine Race. With all of those enemies, do you really think that you can block them by yourself?”

After speaking up to here, Jinsong turned to look at the other Winged Pegasus inside the Hall and said, “In the past, when the dealt with the Taurus Divines together with mister, we didn’t even need to dispatch troops. We only did so since we don’t want to one-sidedly accept mister’s kindness. We sent troops in order to gain an equal position as Mister. At that time, Mister didn’t say anything about it since he respected our decision. This caused our clans to suffer a huge loss. At that time, we blamed mister. We thought that Mister asked us for troops so that we would suffer losses. Tell me, did we really trust mister? What about later on, when we heard that the Divines are going to attack us. Mister sent troops in order to act alongside us against the Taurus Divines. Mister had always been helping us unconditionally. I just want to ask you, why was that?”

After speaking up to here, Jinsong looked at them and said, “Why would Mister save us now? We didn’t trust Mister. In the face of such an ally, would you come and save them?”

The Winged Pegasus listened to Jinsong’s words. They had to recognize Jinsong’s words. They didn’t trust Zhao Hai, so why would Zhao Hai save them?

Jinsong looked at the crowd and continued, “Mister has been silently helping us all this time. Because of the war against the Taurus Divines, we suffered huge damages to our strengths. Therefore, we were forced to return to our planes in order to recover. If not for Mister, we wouldn’t have been able to recover for a long time. The Divine Race’s army should’ve already attacked us. And now, we still suspect him, now that is funny.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, then he turned to Jinsong and said, “Patriarch Jinsong, there’s no need to waste words. We’re already aware that Patriarch Yifei isn’t willing to move to the Space. I just didn’t expect the other Winged Pegasus members to be the same as him. They clearly knew what was going on, but they still don’t know what to do. This Zhao Hai doesn’t want to bother saving such a race. Let’s just leave them on their own.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Shan immediately knelt down and said, “Mister, I ask you to please save my Winged Pegasus Clan. Otherwise, we will surely perish.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “In this case, what could I do? I’ll be unfair to you, but there’s nothing that I can do.”

Chapter 946: I Will Play With You Next Time

When Shan heard Zhao Hai, his expression couldn’t help but turn grey in defeat. After some time, he suddenly clenched his teeth. His eyes turned fierce as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, I ask you to remove Winged Pegasus Yifei. This way, nobody would stop the clan from entering the Space.”

Zhao Hai and everyone inside the Hall stared. Nobody thought that Shan would actually request such a thing from Zhao Hai. This was equal to publicly declaring his rebellion.

Everyone inside the hall stared at Shan, especially the members of the Winged Pegasus Clan. These people were high-level members of the clan, and it can be said that they observed Shan grow up. They completely understood what kind of person Shan was, but they didn’t expect Shan to actually say those words.

In an instant, all sorts of gazes turned towards Shan’s figure. Shan remained unmoving as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, I’m not trying to rebel. But Mister, think about it, if Mister doesn’t kill those who oppose the clan entering the Space, then the Winged Pegasus could only wait to be annihilated. In comparison, killing a few people could be considered nothing. I ask Mister to please accept my request.”

Zhao Hai gawked, to be honest, he really didn’t think much about it. To be honest, it was very easy to deal with Yifei. However, if he killed Yifei here, Jinsong and Fei’er might develop worries. This would be disadvantageous to Zhao Hai.

Most importantly, if this matter gets passed on and the vassal races and foreign races, Zhao Hai would have problems later on.

Actually, Zhao Hai had met a lot of vassal races during the times when he was dealing with the Divines. The vassal races had been lukewarm to Zhao Hai. The foreign races also had their own thoughts regarding Zhao Hai.

If his meddling in the Pegasus Clan’s matter was known by the vassal races, then these vassal races might cause troubles for Zhao Hai later. This was something that Zhao Hai didn’t want to see.

But now that it was Shan who asked him, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately decline. With Shan’s request, everything had changed.

If Shan didn’t ask Zhao Hai and just interfered with the Winged Pegasus Clan, then this would be akin to him wanting to usurp the Winged Pegasus Clan. Shan’s request transformed the situation into Zhao Hai being asked for help. This narrative was completely different.

Naturally, as for how other people saw it, Zhao Hai really didn’t care. Maybe in the eyes of the others, Zhao Hai and Shan were doing a two-man play.

Zhao Hai paused before turning his head to look at Jinsong. Although Jinsong was a straightforward Barbarian, he was clear about what Zhao Hai thought about at this time.

Jinsong said with a serious tone, “Mister, if you deal with Yifei, you will save a lot of people. This Jinsong requests Mister to do it.”

When Yifei saw this situation, he panicked as he screamed loudly, “Zhao Hai, if you dare make a move on me, the Winged Pegasus Clan will not let you go.”

Zhao Hai looked at Yifei as though he was looking at a clown. Then he coldly said, “The Winged Pegasus Clan wouldn’t let me off? Hahaha, do you think that I’m afraid of the Winged Pegasus Clan? If it wasn’t for Shan, I wouldn’t have considered your Winged Pegasus Clan. Haven’t you heard of how many people I killed in the Divine Race territory?”

When Zhao Hai said this, Yifei couldn’t help but be stunned. He knew that Zhao Hai wasn’t lying. The moment Zhao Hai stepped into the Divine Realm, he had already started killing. The number of Zhao Hai’s kills was much more than the entirety of the Winged Pegasus Clan.

It was at this moment that Yifei discovered that the things he has been clinging on were worthless  In the face of absolute strength, status and authority were mere sandcastles, once a wave comes they will quickly collapse.

After thinking about this, Winged Pegasus Yifei suddenly knelt to Zhao Hai and said, “I ask Mister to spare my life. I agree to move my clan to the Space.” For Yifei, this wasn’t shameful. In order to survive, he didn’t hesitate to do it.

Zhao Hai looked at Yifei and said, “If you think you can still save yourself, you’re too late. To be honest, I’m tired of talking to you. You threaten me, and you think you can still go away? Stop dreaming.” After that, Zhao Hai waved his hand. In the next moment, he was already holding Yifei’s head. Nobody even saw him move.

Then Zhao Hai turned his head to the other Winged Pegasus Members and said, “Is there anybody else who wants to object?”

The Winged Pegasus clan members looked at the bloody head in Zhao Hai’s hand. Nobody dared to speak. After seeing the head, nobody wanted to object.

Zhao Hai looked at those present and said, “Since everyone agrees, then everything else is easier to do. Go and prepare, I will go and see the nine Supreme Elders.”

After Zhao Hai went out, Fei’er and the others also left while Shan stayed. Now that the Patriarch is dead, the person with the highest influence was Speaker Fang. But since Speaker Fang and Shan were in the same faction, everyone was looking at Shan.

With Speaker Fang and Shan, and the fact that the Zhao Hai was still in the Winged Pegasus’ Plane, nobody dared to stop them. This allowed the migration to smoothly begin.

At this time, Zhao Hai was already inside the Hell King’s ship along with Fei’er, Ding, and Jinsong. They also found two Winged Pegasus members to guide them towards the Supreme Elders.

It was still daytime, the time where the Supreme Elders would make their move. At this point, the Winged Pegasus had been very slippery. They didn’t fight the Supreme Elders but they swarmed them like flies. This caused the Supreme Elders to feel terrible.

Gold Ben and the others were exploding with rage in these past few days. They knew that the more time they spent here the more losses the Divine Race would have. However, they couldn’t retreat now. If they retreat, then they would sooner or later be dealt with by the Demon Zhao Hai. Because of this, even if they feared that the Divines were already extinguished, they still need to persist.

Without the means to cure the hatred in their heart, Gold Ben and the others vented on the Winged Pegasus. This caused their attacks to be more fierce. However, with the arrangement of the Winged Pegasus Clan, their attacks were loud thunders but with small rain.[1]

On this day, Gold Ben and three others were fighting with the Winged Pegasus while Elder Star and the others were resting. Suddenly, Elder Star saw a small golden dot on the horizon. The dot got bigger and bigger until it became Zhao Hai’s Hell King’s Ship.

Upon seeing the enemy, one couldn’t help but feel hatred. Elder Star’s eyes were red after seeing Zhao Hai. However, he didn’t immediately attack. He just looked at the ship with his red eyes as it approached. He looked like an injured beast waiting to take revenge.

After staring at Zhao Hai for some time, Elder Star said, “Everyone, Zhao Hai has finally appeared, get ready.”

Upon hearing this, Gold Ben and the three others stopped, they immediately noticed Zhao Hai’s ship. This caused them to be happy before they moved and went into their positions with the Seven Star Heaven Lock disks in their hands. Elder Star didn’t participate in this formation as he held his Star Disk, preparing to attack Zhao Hai.

Before long, Zhao Hai appeared in front of Elder Star and the others. Zhao Hai decreased the ship’s altitude as he looked at Elder Star and said, “Elder Star, we meet again. I didn’t expect that you would use this method. It’s not easy to compel me to show up. However, you really are heartless. You chose to sacrifice your people just to deal with me.”

Elder Star icily looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, you finally appeared. We didn’t think that you would have such a ruthless heart. You actually allowed the Thunder Clan to be extinguished.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Elder Star, do you seriously think that you’ve eliminated the Thunder Clan? I’m only here today to tell you that of the ten Divine Continents, only the Leo, Gemini, and Aquarius Continents are left. The Gemini and Aquarius Continents are currently being attacked by me while the Leo Continent is assaulted by the foreign races. I came here to give you the last chance to save your Divine Race. Let me tell you, even if you eliminate the Winged Pegasus Clan today, I still wouldn’t stop. Do you really believe that the Winged Pegasus are important to me?”

Elder Star looked at Zhao Hai and smiled coldly, “Zhao Hai, do you think that you can escape today? Arrange the formation!” Just as Elder Star’s voice fell, Gold Ben and the others immediately moved and started the Seven Star Heaven Lock formation.

As the Seven Star Heaven Lock formation was being established, Elder Star also used his Star Disk. Upon seeing this situation, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but faintly smile. He didn’t move and just allowed Elder Star and the others to finish their action.

Before long, Gold Ben and the others launched their disks before returning to Elder Star’s side. The Seven Star Heaven Lock formation suspended in the air as it sent seven-colored lights from time to time.

When they arrived by Elder Star’s side, Gold Ben and the others immediately equipped their combat suits as they prepared to combat Zhao Hai using Elder Star’s ultimate weapon.

Zhao Hai looked at the situation before he suddenly laughed. Then he maneuvered the Hell King’s ship towards the Seven Star Heaven Lock before he waved his hand and taking the disks. After the disks were taken to the Space, Zhao Hai turned to Elder Star’s group and said, “Everyone, I’ll be taking the Seven Star Heaven Lock today. I will play with you next time. Hahahaha. Everyone, farewell!” After that, the Hell King’s ship vanished from sight.

* * *

Strong but with little effect

Chapter 947: Protecting The Last Bloodline

Elder Star stared at the place where Zhao Hai disappeared. It took him quite a while to recover. Then suddenly, he vomited blood, he was completely mad at Zhao Hai.

Gold Ben and the others also had the look of defeat on their faces. They knew that they truly lost this time. They had no way to deal with Zhao Hai.

After Gold Ben saw Elder Star shake and collapse, he immediately went forward to offer support. He wasn’t mad at Zhao Hai at this time, it can be said that he couldn’t afford to be angry at Zhao Hai.

When one meets a well-matched rival, one would get angry whenever one couldn’t defeat him and lose. However, when one meets an enemy that couldn’t be defeated, one wouldn’t have the means to be angry.

Perhaps the words that could describe Gold Ben’s emotion right now was ‘accepting fate’! Gold Ben had accepted his defeat.

After some time, Elder Star took a deep breath before looking at Gold Ben and the others and said, “We’re finished. We miscalculated. We didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this strong. The Divine Race has been destroyed by his hands.”

Jie Yu’s eyes were scarlet red as he said, “No, we must deal with him, we need to kill him. Elder Star, we can use Blood Sacrifice in order to have the Deity deal with Zhao Hai.”

Elder Star smiled bitterly and said, “Jie Yu, haven’t you understood Zhao Hai? If the Deity could deal with him, then he would’ve made a move already. He wouldn’t have allowed Zhao Hai to destroy the Divine Race. Don’t forget, he needs us in order to collect Faith Power. Also, where did you think Zhao Hai get his Hell King’s Ship? He took it from the Deity.”

Jie Yu couldn’t accept it as he said, “Then what do we do now? Do we just wait?”

Elder Star shook his head and said, “It would be too late for us to provide help, but we could still protect our last bloodline.”

Gold Ben and the others stared. They looked confused at Elder Star. They didn’t know what Elder Star meant. It was already too late for them to provide help yet they would protect their bloodline?

Elder Star looked at the group and said, “Haven’t you heard Zhao Hai? Although his words said that he had destroyed the Divine Race, he revealed that he was still dealing with the Gemini and Aquarius Continents. Although these clans couldn’t stop Zhao Hai, they could at least delay him for several days. Otherwise, Zhao Hai wouldn’t have come to pester us here. He also revealed another matter, he said that the foreign races are now dealing with the Leo Divines.”

As soon as they heard Elder Star, Gold Ben and the others quickly nodded. They understood what Elder Star wanted to say. They had fought against the foreign races for many years, so they knew how strong the foreign races were. It would be impossible for the foreign races to smoothly take the Leo Continent. Moreover, the Leo Divines had been holding their anger down all this time. Now that the foreign races came, they would be the target for this hatred. The foreign races wouldn’t be able to succeed in a short time.

The Gemini and Aquarius Continents were too far for them to rescue. Moreover, they had no way to deal with Zhao Hai. On the other hand, there were a lot of ways to deal with the foreign races.

Gold Ben and the others were watching Elder Star, they were waiting for what he would say next. Elder Star continued, “There’s no point in dealing with the Winged Pegasus Clan anymore. We’ll set out immediately and deal with the foreign races. As long as we attack the foreign races, their army would come back. And when they do so, we will return to the Leo Continent. Whether it was Zhao Hai or the foreign races, they would still have a hard time dealing with all nine of us. As long as we block their attacks, the Leo Continent would be saved, saving the last blood of the Divine Race.

Gold Ben and the others nodded. However, Gold Ben had some doubts, “What do we do if the foreign races don’t return?”

Elder Star shook his head and said, “No, the foreign races aren’t Zhao Hai. As Zhao Hai said, he had no close relationship with the Winged Pegasus Clan. Therefore, even if we deal with the Winged Pegasus just like the Thunder Clan, Zhao Hai might not return. On the other hand, the foreign races are different. Their roots lie in their continents, if we attack them, then they would definitely return.”

Gold Ben and the others nodded. They agreed with Elder Star’s words. After seeing the group agree, Elder Star nodded and said, “Since everyone agrees, then let’s not waste time. Let’s go.”

Jie Yu looked towards the Winged Pegasus Clan and said with indignation, “Do we let them off like just like that?”

Elder Star replied, “We will find opportunities to deal with them in the future. In any case, they won’t be able to run away. Let’s go.” Jie Yu looked at the Winged Pegasus once more before he turned around and followed Elder Star.

After seeing Elder Star and the others leave, Zhao Hai relaxed. If Elder Star and the others didn’t leave, then he might make some moves. It wouldn’t be good for Zhao Hai to fight right now, or else he would ascend.

The reason why Zhao Hai told Elder Star too much was because he wanted this result. He wanted the Supreme Elders to shift their hatred towards the foreign races. Now, it seems that he had succeeded. Zhao Hai was sitting in his room as he was looking at Elder star and the others. Because of this, Jinsong and the others were still unaware of what happened. Jinsong and the others were still inside the Hell King’s ship. They were anxious, afraid that they would encounter the anger of the Supreme Elders.

At this time, Zhao Hai exited from his room. Then he turned to Jinsong and the others and smiled, “It’s fine, there’s no need to be worried. The nine Supreme Elders are leaving the Winged Pegasus plane.”

Jinsong and the others stared, naturally they didn’t know that Zhao Hai was able to see Elder Star and the others.

Because of this, they didn’t believe Zhao Hai immediately. On the other hand, Fei’er didn’t doubt Zhao Hai. He had the longest contact with Zhao Hai, so he was aware of all the magical things that Zhao Hai could do.

Fei’er laughed before he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister is truly fierce. In just a few words, you managed to shift their target to the foreign races.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “It wasn’t that easy. If I told them yesterday, then they might not have retreated. It was only today that the foreign races arrived at the Leo Continent. If I told the Supreme Elders before that, then they might have stayed here.”

Fei’er nodded, then he looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Mister, are you telling the truth? That the only Divines left in the Divine Realm are the Leo, Gemini, and Aquarius Divines?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It’s true. I already told you when you entered the Space, I have many means. But the Divines aren’t the ones that worry me. There’s the O’Neal family as well as the Underworld. When the Supreme Elders decided to deal with you, I’m already prepared to send you to the Space. Even if not everyone entered the Space, I could still send people to constrain the Supreme Elders while you enter. I will also be dealing with the Divines in the meantime. When the time comes, I will release information so that the foreign races wouldn’t be able to sit by and do nothing. They will certainly dispatch their troops, providing a new target for the Supreme Elders’ hatred. You will be safe during that period of time, you won’t be having too much losses. Unfortunately, matters turned into this messy situation.”

Fei’er had the look of shame on his face, he bowed and said, “I’ve been unfair to Mister, I have disappointed you.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “This isn’t your mistake. You already tried your best. In any case, things had already happened, there’s no need to think too much about it. Just go and help Shan out.”

The group nodded before Zhao Hai led the Hell King’s ship towards the Winged Pegasus’ Palace. Shan was also inside the palace. Upon seeing Zhao Hai and the other come back, the expressions on the Winged Pegasus members’ face changed. They didn’t know what Zhao Hai came for this time.

Zhao Hai looked at Shan and smiled, “The Supreme Elders have retreated. You can now prepare in peace. I will be heading back, I still have a lot of matters to attend to.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the Winged Pegasus members relaxed. However, there were some members who had the look of indignation on their faces. They thought that Zhao Hai went too far. He obviously came intentionally late. This caused the Winged Pegasus to suffer a huge loss. Moreover, he even forced them to enter the Space.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about the expressions of these people. He turned his head to Shan and said, “Shan, I will leave things here to you. If something came up, then just contact me. I will come and help you.” After saying this, Zhao Hai scanned the Winged Pegasus members. These people couldn’t help but lower their heads.

These people were clearly aware. Although Yifei wasn’t the clan’s strongest expert, as a Patriarch, he wasn’t weak, he had achieved God-rank strength. However, such strength couldn’t even block Zhao Hai’s move. He couldn’t even make any move to resist as he was instantly killed. Zhao Hai’s strength made the Winged Pegasus members startled, they became afraid.

Shan understood what Zhao Hai said. He didn’t say anything else as he nodded and said, “Yes Mister. I will move the clan to the Space as soon as possible.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to look at Jinson and Speaker Fang. Then he bowed to them and said, “I will have to ask your help in order to settle the Winged Pegasus Clan. You need to move the clan in the fastest way possible. I’m afraid I won’t have time to manage things here. The Supreme Elders are now heading towards the foreign races. I need to quickly take care of the Gemini and Aquarius Divines in order to face the Supreme Elders. I hope I would have enough time to work with the foreign Supreme Elders. Otherwise, things would be troublesome.”

Jinsong and Fang immediately returned the bow and said, “Mister, you can rest assured.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then his figure flashed as he disappeared from the Winged Pegasus Clan’s palace.

Chapter 948: Different Ways of Ascending

Zhao Hai returned to his room. Laura and the others were looking at him with smiles. Although they were fighting with the Gemini and Aquarius Divines, the situation was already under Lizzy and Megan’s control. Because of this, they were able to relax.

When Laura saw Zhao Hai she immediately said, “Brother Hai, very well done. I didn’t expect that this matter would be solved this quickly. I must admit, Shan is very good. In the critical moment, he was able to make a firm decision.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “That fellow is indeed very good. Alright, there’s no need to manage them. We need to focus on our next step. First we need to deal with the Gemini and Aquarius Divines. Also, make sure to get the Aquarius Continent’s potion formulas. They might prove useful someday.”

Lizzy nodded. Then Zhao Hai continued, “Second is to lead the O’Neal family to the Winged Pegasus. I expect the migration to not be smooth. We’ll need to use the O’Neal family to whip them.”

Laura and the other stared. Laura looked confused at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, are you sure? Will they still dare? Didn’t the Winged Pegasus agree?”

Zhao Hai sneered and said, “Agree? It was because they were afraid. Most of the Winged Pegasus members are still reluctant to relocate. Do you really think that Jinsong would be able to convince them? To the Winged Pegasus, Jinsong is an outsider, he wouldn’t be able control them. At the same time, Shan is too inexperienced. If the Winged Pegasus decided to drag on, then that wouldn’t be good. Me being able to force the Supreme Elders back only added to the Winged Pegasus clan’s dissatisfaction. They think that I always had the ability to save them but I just decided not to. They certainly hate me more now. If you don’t whip those kinds people, then they will not believe you.”

Lizzy and Megan nodded. Commanding troops were their job, so luring the O’Neal family would also be left to them.

Zhao Hai continued, “Third, we need to support the foreign races. The Supreme Elders wouldn’t be polite to the foreign races. We will use this opportunity to get the Divine Race’s combat suits. As for the foreign Supreme Elders, we will need to find a way to get theirs.”

The group nodded. But as for the third one, Lizzy and Megan didn’t have anything to do about it. They were tasked to direct the army, as for the Supreme Elders, that was for Zhao Hai.

At this time, Laura opened her mouth and said, “Brother Hai, since we have time, why don’t we combine the Seven Star Heaven Lock and the Hell King’s ship. This way, the ship would be stronger. Then we would be more relaxed when dealing with Elder Star.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Right, I forgot. But let’s place the Seven Star Heaven Lock in the Space first. Let’s see if a prompt would appear.”

Then Zhao Hai waved his hand, taking the Seven Star Heaven Lock from the warehouse to the Space. But much to Zhao Hai’s surprise, there was no prompt. This caused him to feel awkward.

After that, Zhao Hai decided to run the formation through the Universal Scanner.

When the entire procedure was finished, the scanner issued a sound, “Seven Star Heaven Lock disks detected. Asking for permission to proceed. Will need 100 thousand gold coins to continue the analysis.”

Zhao Hai didn’t know whether to laugh or cry, then he turned to Laura and said, “You always said that I would die for money. Look, it seems like I really would.”

Laura and the others laughed. Then Zhao Hai said, “Immediately start analyzing.” A hundred thousand gold coins immediately vanished from Zhao Hai’s stockpile. Before long, the scanner spewed out some words, “Analysis completed. Seven Star Heaven Lock disks detected. Item is unique to the Cultivation Realms. Grade, low. Materials used are, gold essence, silver essence, soul stone. Proportions are 1 to 3 to 0.5. Forging method used is a common method of the Cultivation World, which contains forty-nine sets of arrays. Arrays used respectively are, magnifying array, reduction array……”

“Asking the host for permission to extract the Seven Star Heaven Lock’s abilities. Minerals required are present inside the Space, but are not enough. If Host want to proceed, 10 million gold coins are required. If Host wants to extract the formation, 1 million gold coins are required.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, then he turned to Laura and the others. The women understood Zhao Hai’s gaze, the Space was asking for money once more. After seeing Zhao Hai’s bitter smile, they couldn’t help but laugh again. Fortunately, they were a lot of saved money inside the Space. In addition to the mines in the Demon Realm, Ruyen was also doing great business in the Ark Space. Because of this, the Space wasn’t short on money.

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “Proceed.” After issuing this order, 11 million gold was immediately deducted.

Zhao Hai sighed, then with an intention, he sent the Hell King’s ship into the Space. As the ship entered the Space, a prompt was immediately heard, “Seven Star Heaven Lock disks may merge with the Hell King’s ship to increase the ship’s strength. The Hell King’s ship will acquire the ability to trap enemies. Asking Host for permission to proceed.”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment, he thought that this action would cost money once more. However, it seems like the Space was doing this for free. Zhao Hai quickly felt happy as he quickly said, “Begin merging!”

After issuing this order, the Seven Star Heaven Lock disks immediately flew towards the Hell King’s ship. In a flash, the disks and the ship met each other. The integration caused a bright light to emerge. When the light vanished, Zhao Hai observed the Hell King’s ship. On each side of the ship, four disks could be seen. These eight disks looked like wheels.

Naturally, these disks were the Seven Star Heaven Lock disks. As the eight disks stood on each side of the Hell King’s ship, they kept on spinning. This caused the ship to have the feeling of being fast. It looked like it was there for a moment, then at another place in the next. An outsider wouldn’t be able to determine its specific position.

Zhao Hai knew that this was due to the formation. With the addition of the formation disks, the Hell King’s ship looked even more mystical.

Zhao Hai made an intention in his mind, making the Hell King’s ship approach. However, they didn’t embark. They just stood outside and looked at the ship.

In the past, the Hell King’s ship would give one the feeling of brilliance. But now, the ship had a ethereal aura. It fluttered in place as though it was a mirage.

Laura’s eyes shone as she said, “Very good. It looks very nice.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly. At this time, the ship had already arrived in front of them.

Laura and the others stood on the ship and looked around. However, they were left disappointed, there were no changes inside the ship.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, don’t worry about it. Let’s go, we still need to carry out our plans. Lizzy, Megan, I will leave the Gemini and Aquarius Divines to you. Deal with them as soon as possible. Don’t forget about the potion formulas.”

The two nodded before they turned around and left the room. After that, Zhao Hai turned to Laura and said, “We need to update Bingya and the others about the situation. They had been crazily cultivating these past few days.”

Laura smiled and said, “Right, if you didn’t say that, I would’ve forgotten about them. They didn’t come out when the Hell King’s ship was being modified. Will they have any problems?”

Zhao Hai replied, “It’s fine, rest assured. They wouldn’t be able to hear any noises from outside. Just like how they didn’t hear what we said to Fei’er and the others.”

Laura nodded and said, “Right, we can’t let them know that. From what I can see, even if they are getting more and more loyal towards you, they are still very concerned about their families. If we let them know about our plan, then they might inform their clans and think that we are planning on doing bad things to them.”

Zhao Hai sighed, “I feel like I have no choice. The Divine Realm’s 13 ultimate weapons would be a very big help to us if we gather them all.”

Laura nodded, then she went on to comfort Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, don’t think too much about it. After we ascend, there would be a lot of enemies going after us. If we suffer any accidents, then everyone inside the Space would be gone.”

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “Right, we cannot control the incoming danger. We just need to be extremely careful.”

Laura nodded, “Brother Hai, if you can choose where to ascend, would you pick the Atlanta Plane or the Underworld?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “If I could choose, then I would head to the Atlanta Plane. The Underworld is full of undead. Even if I ascend there, we wouldn’t be able to live well.”

Laura agreed, “Then we need to know more about the O’Neal family. Right, Brother Hai, how about we ask the O’Neal family undead about any legends of ascension that they have.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he nodded and said, “Right, I forgot about this. Let’s go ask them right now.” Then he waved his hand as three undead magic armor pilots appeared in front of him. The three undead quickly bowed and said, “We have seen the Young Master.”

Zhao Hai had met them before when he asked about the magic armors. So after Zhao Hai nodded, he immediately went straight to the point, “Have you heard any tales of ascension from the Atlanta Plane?”

The three undead nodded. Zhao Hai’s mind shook as he pointed to an undead and said, “You, what tales have you heard?”

The selected undead stepped forward and said, “Young Master, in the Atlanta Plane, tales of ascension are divided into three types. Each of the three continent have their own tales. In the Warrior Continent, I heard that after one practiced to a certain degree, then they would be able to use their battle qi to cut the firmament open before ascending. In the Mage Continent, the situation is similar. As long as a mage practices to a degree, they can rend the firmament in order to ascend. However, our Magic Armor Continent is somewhat special. We practice spiritual force and our method of ascending is different. If someone from the Magic Armor Continent wants to ascend, then we would have to rely on our magic armors. In the Magic Armor Continent, the clans keep a special type of magic armor. These magic armors are called Ascension Magic Armors. These magic armors aren’t the same as conventional magic armors. Their attacking strength is more powerful but are more difficult to operate. Whenever someone thinks that they could operate the magic armor, then they would have to apply to the families and be tested. Only those who passed the tests would be qualified to use those magic armors. Once they manage to successfully use the magic armor, then they can assault the heavens in order to ascend. I heard that even if one ascends, the Ascension Magic Armor would remain.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to the other two and said, “Do you have anything to add?”

The other two shook their head. Then Zhao Hai waved his hand, putting those undead away.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “It looks like we need to go to the Atlanta Plane. As for ascending, I’m afraid we would need to head to the Mage or Warrior Continents.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “That wouldn’t be easy. It seems like ascending would not be so simple. If we have time, we’ll have to go to the Atlanta Plane to take a look.”

Laura nodded, then suddenly she said, “Brother Hai, you could also head to the Magic Armor Continent and find a way to get your hands on these ascension magic armors. See if you can operate them. If you can, then you can just use them to ascend. What do you think?”

When he heard this, Zhao Hai’s eyes shone, “That’s good as well. Good, then after we settle things here, we’ll go to the Magic Armor Continent and see if we can steal an ascension magic armor for ourselves.”

Chapter 949: Letting Me Do Free Work?

Axe quietly sat on top of the war tank as he stared at the vast expanse of land outside their base. He could see that the land was very fertile and its air was much better compared to the Ark Continent. But aside of being happy, Axe was also annoyed.

They didn’t encounter any attacks in the defensive line, but when they sent their scouts for reconnaissance, they began to be assaulted, and all of the enemies were undead.

However, the situation made Axe more annoyed than worried. There weren’t a lot of undead, but they were very fast. Their coordination was very good as well. One would be easily entangled once one fought them. Although they weren’t a threat to Axe, they made it very difficult for the scouts to do their job.

After failing several times, Axe lost his patience. He dropped the scouting plan and instead focused on the base’s construction.

It’s also strange that while they were building their base, the undead didn’t come to attack them. This caused Axe to be confused. He already told his father about this matter.

Axe was also informed by his father about the appearance of strong undead in the Ark Continent’s Dark Mist. Because of this, the family has decided to shift their center of development. Moreover, in the near future, his father would bring important people of the family to this place.

After hearing about this, Axe became both worried and happy. He was worried about the dark mist but happy because the family has decided to shift their attention to this place. This was equal to Axe having set up a great contribution. This was something good for him.

While Axe was thinking about these matters, someone suddenly arrived. Axe turned his head and saw that it was George. After accepting the other party’s salute, Axe looked at George and said, “George, why did you come?” Axe’s war tank was now stopped right outside the base. He came out in order to relax. Because of this, he was surprised to see George appearing here. He already told his people to leave him be unless an important matter had come.

George bowed to Axe and said, “Young Lord, the Clan’s Elders have arrived. This time, they presented the Patriarch’s mark to inspect. After their inspection, it’s possible that the Patriarch would come here.”

Upon hearing this, Axe gave a nod and said, “Alright, let’s go back.” Then he proceeded to command the war tank and returned to the base.

Actually, this investigation was just a casual stroll in the surroundings. The O’Neal family’s elders were already clear about their current state. The north wasn’t getting any quieter and the family had no way to deal with it. Because of this, it was inevitable for the family to move southward.

Additionally, the environment here was really good. Although there had been some traces of war here, it had already happened months ago. With time being the only factor left, the grass grew back, causing the natural appearance of the place to be appealing.

The elders didn’t dally for too long, they immediately wanted to tell the Patriarch about the situation. After they left, Axe quickly ordered for the expansion of the base.

Just as Axe was busily expanding the base, the Underworld was also beginning to make their move. The expansion of the Dark Mist went faster and more undead began to venture out at night. The scope of their operations were also becoming bigger and bigger.

In the face of this, the O’Neal family could only draw back. Their relocation was already imminent. The O’Neal Patriarch immediately issued the order to move.

It’s fortunate that the Ark Continent wasn’t their land. Because of this, they managed to pack up their things quickly. However, the relay stations were kept in place. The O’Neal family’s Patriarch still wanted to use them to monitor the Dark Mist’s situation.

While the O’Neal family was preparing to move, Zhao Hai’s battle against the Gemini and Aquarius Divines was nearing its end. In fact, the Aquarius Continent was already done. The potions of the Aquarius Divines were indeed very good, but they had little to no use against the undead. Because of this, their defeat came faster. The only remaining target right now were the Gemini Divines.

On the other hand, the Leo Divines and the foreign races were still fighting. The tenacity of the foreign races was quite strong, but the Leo Divines were able to block their attack, dragging the foreign races into a long-term battle.

The foreign races wanted to take advantage of the situation while Zhao Hai was attacking the Divine Race. They dispatched their troops in order to gain profits. However, they didn’t think that they would be met with the Leo Divines. Halting their advance through the Divine Race territory.

With the Leo Divines blocking their attack, the foreign races weren’t having an easy time. The Foreign race territories weren’t close to the Leo Continent. Because of this, their supplies only depended on their rear ships. With this, their supply line would inevitably suffer some issues. As time passes, the price that they would pay could only rise.

The foreign races didn’t have any good means to solve this situation. If they don’t succeed in this war, then they would have wasted their earlier investments. Giving up at this point would cause them huge losses, but if they continue, they still wouldn’t be able to take the Leo Continent in a short time.

Actually, from the very beginning of the battle, the foreign races felt that something was wrong. The Leo Divines seem to be prepared for war. This caused the Foreign races to suffer a huge loss, they were placed in a disadvantageous position.

Zhao Hai was paying attention to this matter. He was also aware that the Supreme Elders were heading towards the Foreign Race territories. He wanted to see the reaction of the foreign races when they hear this news.

Just as Zhao Hai was being busy with these things, the O’Neal family officially began their relocation. The entire O’Neal family took their troops and began to gather in the Taurus Continent.

Naturally, Zhao Hai knew about this. However, he didn’t make a move. He was just waiting for them to finish making their base. When that time comes, they definitely won’t just stay still. Once they begin to expand outward, he would lead them to the Winged Pegasus Clan.

The Winged Pegasus Clan’s migration wasn’t going very smoothly. The Winged Pegasus were angry at Zhao Hai because of what happened. Although they agreed to move under his threat, the speed of relocation was going at a snail’s pace.

Shan was aware of this development, but he didn’t want to trouble Zhao Hai. He already asked Zhao Hai for help once. If he couldn’t manage things this time, then he really wouldn’t have any face left to meet Zhao Hai.

Even if Zhao Hai knew about the situation of the Winged Pegasus Clan, he still didn’t go and deal with them. He knew that the more he interfered, the more the Winged Pegasus would resent him. And Zhao Hai didn’t want this to happen.

After three days, the Gemini Divines were finally dealt with, making Zhao Hai feel at ease. He was now waiting for the news regarding the nine Supreme Elders beginning their attack on the foreign races.

Zhao Hai believed that when the nine Supreme Elders attacked, the foreign races would surely inform Bingya and the others. At that time, he would know.

The nine Supreme Elders didn’t let Zhao Hai wait for long. Two days after Zhao Hai had dealt with the Gemini Continent, Bingya suddenly went to see Zhao Hai. After allowing Bingya into his room, Bingya immediately said, “Mister, please help the Foreign Races!”

When he saw Bingya’s appearance, Zhao Hai knew what Bingya was going to say. He smiled faintly and said, “Bingya, what’s wrong? Say it slowly, there’s no need to be anxious.”

Bingya stabilized his mood before he said, “Mister, we don’t know why, but the Divine Supreme Elders suddenly attacked the Foreign Race territory. Our three Supreme Elders are currently resisting them. I ask Mister to help us out.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, I will depart immediately.” Bingya happily nodded before he turned around and left.

After Bingya left, Lizzy immediately opened the monitor to show the situation with the Leo Continent. They wanted to see the response of the foreign race army.

Zhao Hai looked at the monitor and said, “Did the foreign race army not receive any news? Why aren’t they preparing to head back to help?”

Lizzy shook her head and said, “They should have. A messenger fish is certainly present in the army, they can’t just keep their soldiers in the dark. I think they had already received the news but they don’t plan to retreat. And this time, Bingya asked us for help. I reckon they plan to have us cooperate with the three Foreign Race Supreme Elders in order to constrain the nine Supreme Elders. Meanwhile, they will use this opportunity to sweep the Leo Continent.”

Zhao Hai thought about it for a moment before he laughed and said, “So the Foreign Races wanted me to do free labor. Hahaha. Interesting. I figured they’d do that.”

Lizzy looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Big Brother Hai, what do you plan to do now? Should we help them?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “We’ll help, why wouldn’t we? Not only would we help, we’ll see it to the very end. Since they wanted use to cooperate with the Foreign Supreme Elders, then we’ll cooperate in order to deal with the nine Supreme Elders. However, don’t forget that our goal are the combat suits. Other matters aren’t important.”

Lizzy nodded and said, “Alright, I understand. But Big Brother Hai, do we just let the foreign races gain such a huge benefit?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “We do not have something we need in the Leo Continent. If they want it then we’ll just hand it over. This would also have them owe us a favor. In this case, if we were to borrow their ultimate weapons, they surely would have a hard time rejecting.”

Chapter 950: Two Matters, One Problem

When they heard Zhao Hai, Lizzy and the others stared. Then they quickly understood what Zhao Hai meant. The Foreign Race were really quite sly this time, they actually wanted to use Zhao Hai as free labor. However, Zhao Hai plans to use this opportunity to have the foreign races owe him a favor. Otherwise, the foreign races wouldn’t comply if he ever wanted to borrow their combat suits one day.

If it was someone else, then even if they managed to borrow the combat suits, they still wouldn’t be able to gain something from it. However, Zhao Hai was different since he has the Space. As long as he managed to borrow the combat suits and sends them to the Space, he could immediately produce seeds. When those seeds are made, he can then return the combat suits to the foreign races. In this case, the foreign races could only benefit from the situation.

After thinking about this, Lizzy and the others smiled. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, do we head to the Foreign Race Territory now?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Rest assured, we will head to the Foreign Race Territory. You go and rest. I’ll be heading out, Bingya and the others should still be outside their rooms.”

After he said this, Zhao Hai walked out of his room. Indeed, Bingya and the others were outside and had yet to return to their room.

At this time, Bingya and the others were extremely worried. They didn’t expect the nine Supreme Elders to attack the Foreign Race territory. For them, this was terrible news.

Bingya and the others had experienced the strength of the nine Supreme Elders. Even Zhao Hai wouldn’t dare to meet them head on, not to say about other people.

Although the Foreign Races also had three Supreme Elders, and their ultimate weapons were the same as the Divine Race, they were still at a numerical disadvantage.

Moreover, Bingya and the others knew that overwhelming the nine Supreme Elders with numbers was impossible. Only people with the same calibre could match them.

Therefore, they were anxious. One shouldn’t underestimate the nine Supreme Elders. Their collective strength was enough to make the Foreign Races shudder.

After looking at their expressions, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Why don’t you enter your rooms and rest? Rest assured, I will provide help. Since I haven’t been to the Foreign Race Territory, I can’t use my space transmission. We can only head there slowly using the ship.”

Although Zhao Hai mentioned that they were going slowly, their actual speed was actually very fast. After being upgraded by the Seven Star Heaven Lock disks, the ship’s speed was greatly improved.

However, Bingya and the others weren’t able to truly notice this point. Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the three quickly turned their heads. They immediately gave Zhao Hai a bow and said, “Mister.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he smiled and said, “It’ll be fine, don’t worry about it too much. The troops sent by your clans to attack the Leo Continent haven’t retreated. It seems like the nine Supreme Elders aren’t going all out. So there’s no need for you to be anxious about it.”

When Bingya heard this, his eyes couldn’t help but reveal a trace of shock. He didn’t know if Zhao Hai’s words were intentional or not.

In fact, Bingya and the others already knew about their clan’s plan, they weren’t excluded from knowing the facts. Although they thought that using Zhao Hai wasn’t good, they continued to keep quiet for the benefit of their clan. However, they didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this frank about the topic.

Bingya looked at Zhao Hai with some anxiety. Zhao Hai’s smile was the same as before, Bingya didn’t know if it was an illusion or not, but he felt that Zhao Hai’s eyes seem to flash for a bit.

Bingya could feel a cold sweat coming out, but he still bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Yes. Mister should also know that using ordinary troops against the Supreme Elders would be useless. There’s no point in them heading back.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly at Bingya and said, “Really? I haven’t thought about this point. Alright, let’s not talk about this anymore. According to our present speed, how long do we need to travel in order to reach the Foreign Race territory?”

Bingya thought for a moment and answered, “By our current speed, we should arrive at the Foreign Race territory in three days.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Go and send word to your clans, tell them to drag the nine Supreme Elders as long as possible. The sudden attack of the Supreme Elders is certainly because of the attack made by the foreign races. They want you to retreat so they went to the Foreign Race territory, If they see that your army didn’t retreat, then they might go to the Leo Continent. Or else they risk being exterminated.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Bingya immediately knew that Zhao Hai was aware of their plan. He even guessed the plan of the nine Supreme Elders. Bingya couldn’t help but be ashamed as he answered, “Yes Mister, I will send word immediately.”

After that, Bingya and the others returned to their room. Zhao Hai looked at the three and faintly smiled. He said so much because he wanted to send a strike at Bingya. At the same time, he wanted to borrow Bingya’s mouth to tell the foreign races that he was aware of their plan.

Zhao Hai wasn’t the type to grab merit, but there were some times where it was necessary. If he didn’t let the other side know that he was aware of the tricks they were pulling, then they would only treat him as a fool. But if you make them aware that you knew about their plan, then they would need to feel grateful to you. This was Zhao Hai’s intent.

When Bingya returned to his room, he immediately took his messenger fish out and said, “Patriarch, Patriarch, are you there?”

A low and deep voice was heard, “Bingya, how was it? Did Zhao Hai agree?”

Bingya’s heart couldn’t help but skip a beat. There were no means of respect from the Patriarch’s words. This caused Bingya to feel uncomfortable.

However, Bingya still replied, “Patriarch, Mister Zhao Hai seems to be aware of our plan. He just told me that our troops in the Leo Continent aren’t planning to withdraw, I think he’s implying something. However, he still decided to help us and is currently rushing towards the territory. He told me that the nine Supreme Elders were attacking us because they want our army to withdraw. And if we don’t retreat, they would head back or else risk losing everything.”

However, Bingya didn’t expect the Patriarch to just snort and said, “I don’t need you to teach me how this works. Tell Mister Zhao Hai to rest assured. We will hold the Supreme Elders here.”

Bingya’s expression sank, however he still nodded and said, “Yes, Patriarch. I will relay your words.” After that, Bingya placed his messenger fish down.

Bingya’s conversation with the Patriarch was also heard by Ryder and Yehta. Their expressions weren’t attractive. The Patriarch was very impolite. This impoliteness made them feel disgraced.

The three were with Zhao Hai for a long time but they also gave huge contributions to their clans. The three always thought that they were regarded as great characters. But now, it seems like they were treated as nothing.

This made the three feel indignant. Zhao Hai was very strong, but even he was very polite to them, he was very kind. Zhao Hai never treated them as though they were his subordinates. Zhao Hai even treasured his undead.

Compared to Zhao Hai, their Patriarch’s response was truly poor. After some time, Bingya turned to Ryder and Yehta, he sighed and then said, “The Patriarch is really too tall to see the picture. He really thinks that he can plot against Mister. From what I can see, Mister already knew about their plan.”

Ryder forced a smile and said, “If Mister isn’t someone who can do those calculations casually, then he wouldn’t have lived up to this day. I just hope that the clan wouldn’t do anything excessive. Otherwise, the foreign races might follow the steps of the Divine Race.”

Bingya sighed and said, “Alright, let’s not talk about this. In any case, Mister already knows what we are doing. And we don’t have a control of the direction we’re heading at.”

Ryder forced a smile and said, “We want to take control, but unfortunately we can’t. Forget it, we’ll just let it be.”

After not saying anything for a while, Yehta suddenly said, “If Mister becomes hostile against the Foreign Races one day, which side will the both of you help?”

If Yehta brought this issue up earlier, then Bingya and Ryder might immediately say that they’ll help the clan. But now, Bingya and Ryder were unsure.

To be honest, their hearts were leaning towards their clansmen. However, the way their Patriarchs handled things left the three of them disappointed. On the other hand, the three had seen how Zhao Hai handles things in the past few days. Although the relationship between Zhao Hai and the foreign races was just superficial, Zhao Hai still greatly helped the foreign races. In this case, instead of being grateful to Zhao Hai, the clan actually plotted against him. They were acting like fools, something that Bingya and the others couldn’t accept.

After the two didn’t say anything, Yehta couldn’t help but bitterly smile. To be honest, she also didn’t have an answer. It was because of this that she decided to ask Ryder and Bingya, she didn’t expect the two of them to be indecisive as well.

As the three became silent, their mood became complex. They just hope that Zhao Hai wouldn’t become their enemy one day.

Chapter 951: Demonstration of Authority

Normally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t eavesdrop on Bingya’s group. But at this time, he actually did.

After seeing the three being silent, Zhao Hai turned his head to Laura and said, “Laura, how do you see this?”

Laura smiled and said, “It’s a good thing. We can see that they are more inclined towards Brother Hai. However, they still can’t let go of their clans. It seems like they couldn’t bear the attitude of their Patriarch.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I really didn’t expect that those people from the Foreign Races would actually have a plot for me. Interesting.”

Lizzy was somewhat indignant as she said, “Big Brother Hai, so what do we do now? We shouldn’t help these kinds of people.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “In any case, we know about their plan. And now that they’re aware that we know, they would have no way to change it. From what I can see, there’s no need to stop their plan. We can also make use of them and have them help us deal with the nine Supreme Elders. Our ultimate goal are the combat suits. We need to send them to the Space no matter what. And at the very least, they have some sort of relationship to us. The three races of the Ark Continent have them as ancestors.”

Lizzy nodded, “Big Brother Hai, you truly have a tender heart. We don’t need to think about these people at all. Just go and take control of them. Look at the Winged Pegasus, everytime I see them, I couldn’t help but get pissed off.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and didn’t say anything. He knew that Lizzy was right, he really was tender-hearted. However, this property of his was relative.

Laura smiled and said, “Alright Lizzy, stop complaining. If Brother Hai isn’t this soft hearted, then he wouldn’t be Zhao Hai. Brother Hai, now that the O’Neal family has started to relocate towards the Taurus Continent, should we make a move?”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said, “Don’t worry, let’s have them settle down first. In any case, we made Axe aware that the enemy is in the Taurus Continent. And that’s enough for now.”

Laura nodded, “Then we’ll let them prepare for a while. From what I can see, the Winged Pegasus will take a very long time before they move, a few months at least. We have enough time.”

Zhao Hai smiled and bit, he didn’t say anything. He knew that Laura was also feeling angry inside. The Winged Pegasus clan were still disobeying. A turtle would be quicker compared to their current pace.

Over the next days, nothing significant happened. The armies of the foreign races and the Leo divines were still fighting in the Leo Continent. Both sides had no way to gain the upper hand. Zhao Hai also used these days to travel.

The Hell King’s ship was fast. Compared to Bingya’s expectation, the arrived in the Foreign Race Territory a day earlier. They encountered the Aries Continent First, the continent of the Beastmen, Bingya’s home.

Zhao Hai stood on the Hell King’s ship as he looked at the vast continent in the distance. He couldn’t help but smile, he wanted to know how the Beastmen would treat him.

Bingya’s group as well as Laura and the others were standing beside Zhao Hai. Laura and the others were curious about the continent while Bingya and the others were anxious.

They had been away for almost a year. All this time, they were with Zhao Hai and haven’t returned. They were unaware of the state of their clans.

However, upon thinking about his Patriarch’s attitude, Bingya couldn’t help but feel cold. They were getting closer and closer to the continent. Upon reaching a certain distance, the sentries of the continent would surely see them. However, there seem to be nobody here, not a single guard nor civilian.

Bingya’s face turned ugly as he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “We’ve been unfair to Mister. Maybe the guards have been eliminated when the Supreme Elders came. That’s why they failed to see us.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and didn’t say anything. He already knew that the Beastmen had noticed them. However, they didn’t come because they wanted to demonstrate their authority.

Sure enough, when Zhao Hai’s Hell King’s ship entered the Aries Continent, a large group of people suddenly flew up from the ground. Then they formed a circular formation and surrounded the ship.

After looking at this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh. He didn’t go forward and instead just stopped the ship. He wanted to see how the Beastmen play this scene out.

These Beastmen weren’t very different compared to the Ark Continent’s Beastmen, but they were indeed visibly stronger.

Bingya and the others weren’t fools, so when they saw this situation, they immediately understood what the clan wanted to do. The three’s expression changed. They didn’t think that the clan would do such a thing, they were playing with Zhao Hai’s face.

After thinking about this, Bingya couldn’t help but turn to look at Zhao Hai. He saw a teasing expression in Zhao Hai’s eyes. After noticing this, Bingya’s heart sank. He had seen this expression whenever Zhao Hai saw an enemy opposing him. After seeing this look, the enemy wouldn’t have a great time.

At the thought of this, Bingya immediately turned to the Beastmen and said, “Everyone, are you here to greet Mister Zhao Hai? This lowly one is the Wolf tribe’s Bingya.”

Bingya did this in order to provide his people with stairs to step down. This would also give Zhao Hai face while preserving the clan’s reputation.

Bingya thought that his plan was good. But unfortunately, he didn’t have a large prestige in the clan. For him to provide Zhao Hai face in behalf of the clan was simply not possible. Because of this, the people still didn’t react after hearing him. Instead, they stepped closer to the Hell King’s ship.

Then one Lion Beastman stepped forward. This man wore leather armor and had a huge sword in his hand. There was an uncommon might in the Lion Beastman’s eyes as he looked at Bingya and the others with disdain. Then when he looked at Zhao Hai, he seem to have a smirking gaze.

The Lion beastman stood there and looked at Zhao Hai before saying, “We were ordered by the Patriarchs to look for suspicious people. Anyone who wants to enter the Beastman Continent needs to be examined.” Naturally, the Lion meant the Aries Continent. Only after the Beastmen occupied this place was it called Beastman Continent.

Zhao Hai looked at the Lion and couldn’t help but smile. Then he said, “So the Beastman Continent has this rule. I apologize for offending you with my ignorance. Since this is the case, then I will take my leave.” After he said that, the Beastmen suddenly discovered that the ship had already disappeared from their encirclement. When the Hell King’s ship reappeared, it was already outside the continent.

When the Lion saw Zhao Hai’s move, he couldn’t help but get stunned, then he panicked. They thought that Zhao Hai would have reactions to this, such as anger or reluctance. However, they didn’t expect Zhao Hai to just turn and leave. He even managed to escape their encirclement. Because of this, the script that they made had become useless.

Most importantly, Zhao Hai was here to help them against their enemies. However, the three Patriarch wanted to occupy a higher position when cooperating with Zhao Hai, so they needed to take him down a notch. However, who would’ve thought that Zhao Hai would just turn around and leave? He ended up not caring about their affair, leaving the foreign races to deal with the nine Supreme Elders all by themselves. To be honest, the three foreign races aren’t capable of stopping the Supreme Elders.

When Zhao Hai came out of the encirclement, he turned and then flew back. The ship’s speed wasn’t very fast. When Laura and the others saw that Zhao Hai went out of the encirclement, they immediately laughed. Zhao Hai could just choose to not play along, and the Beastmen had never thought of it.

Bingya was looking awkwardly at Laura and the others. He didn’t know what to say while his anger started to well up.

It was the Patriarch who told him to ask Zhao Hai for help. And now that Zhao Hai was here, they instead forced him to leave. This basically threw Bingya’s face into the water. If not for the hair on Bingya’s face, Zhao Hai would have seen Bingya becoming as red as a tomato.

Ryder and Yehta were also feeling very awkward. They knew that this matter wasn’t only decided by the Beastman Patriarch, the three Patriarchs should have reached an agreement to demonstrate their authority. Because of this, Ryder and Yehta felt very bad.

Zhao Hai looked at the three and smiled, “It’s fine, you three doesn’t have to wear that expression. I know that this matter is out of your control. There’s no need to be embarrassed. Now I want to see what kind of characters your Patriarchs are, to be able to think genius ideas as this. Hahaha.”

Although Zhao Hai was ridiculing their Patriarch, Bingya and the others weren’t offended. They were currently feeling incensed towards their clan, especially towards their Patriarchs.

Laura and the others stopped laughing, then Laura smiled and said, “Brother Hai, do you think the three Patriarchs would come and invite us back?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I cannot say for certain. It depends on the nine Supreme Elders. If they’re formidable and couldn’t be blocked, then they would ask us back. But if the nine Supreme Elders aren’t pushing hard, then they might not.”

Laura replied, “How could the nine Supreme Elders not push hard? They’re currently holding a lot of hatred in their stomachs. And they want to make the foreign race army retreat from the Leo Continent. In this case, they surely wouldn’t hold back.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I think so too. In fact, the nine Supreme Elders are making the right move. If they attack the foreign races, then the three Supreme Elders surely wouldn’t be able to stop them. In the end, they could only order their army to retreat, freeing the Leo Continent from crisis. And if the foreign races doesn’t call their troops back, then they would return to the Leo Continent and deal with the invading army. This would also free the Leo Continent from its predicament. More importantly, they would be able to cause heavy damages to the foreign races along the way. However, they seemed to exclude me from their calculations, which makes me a bit confused.”

Laura replied, “Perhaps they believed that you are still entangled by the other Divines. Since you don’t have time, they decided to go with their plan.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That is possible. Alright, in any case this is a good opportunity for us to deal with the Supreme Elders. If we miss this, then it might be difficult to do so in the future.”

Laura agreed, “Right, the Supreme Elders are also starting to become smart. They knew that  we couldn’t deal with all of them at once, so they decided to stay together. It wouldn’t be easy for us to deal with them this way.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I think the Supreme Elders are now trying to preserve their blood.”

While Zhao Hai and the others were talking, Bingya’s group were looking anxiously at the Aries Continent. They were waiting for people from their family to come and invite Zhao Hai back.

However, they could only be disappointed. Their people didn’t come out. It seems like Zhao Hai had nothing to do with them anymore when he left.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about this as he waved his hand and had the ship descend. After falling to the sea’s surface, it stayed there and floated, just like any other ship.

Then Zhao Hai turned to Laura and the others and said, “We haven’t had the time to relax. Since we have a few days to spare then we might as well. What do you think?”

Laura smiled, ”Good. We haven’t relaxed for a long time. Younger Sister Meg, please make us a couple of dishes. We’ll be drinking a few cups with Brother Hai.” Meg nodded before she turned around and went to prepare.

After seeing Zhao Hai’s reaction, Bingya and the others didn’t know whether they should be relieved or be worried. They should be relieved since Zhao Hai didn’t go away despite leaving the Aries Continent. He’s close to the Aries Continent so he would be able to quickly offer help. Bingya understood that this was an opportunity provided by Zhao Hai. As for what the foreign races plans to do, he wouldn’t care.

However, Bingya and the others were also worried because of the people in their clan. It has been quite some time before Zhao Hai left the Aries Continent. However, up until this time, nobody went to look for them. This doesn’t make any sense. Bingya was afraid of Zhao Hai being offended, causing the foreign races to suffer a loss.

Chapter 952: Feeling!

Zhao Hai could also see the expression of Bingya’s group. However, Zhao Hai didn’t say anything. He just gave Bingya and the others a nod before he sat down on the deck.

Before long, Meg brought out various types of dishes and set them out on the table. Zhao Hai took some liquor as the women took a seat. Then Zhao Hai raised his glass towards Bingya and said, “Bingya, you couldn’t be blamed for what just happened. This type of thing is not strange for me. In any case, I will not let the Divine Supreme Elders go. You can rest assured.”

Bingya couldn’t say anything, he could only bitterly smile. Even if Zhao Hai didn’t mention it, he already gave great face towards the foreign races. If it was anybody else who was treated like Zhao Hai, then they would have already been angered.

After Zhao Hai drank from his glass, he said, “We’re not just waiting for the foreign races to come for us. We’re also here to prevent the nine Supreme Elders from leaving. This is the only way to get to the Leo Continent. As long as we wait here, then we would surely meet the nine Supreme Elders. Even if they give up on assaulting the foreign races, we can still stop them here.”

Bingya nodded, then he held a wine glass up for Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, I apologize. I’m also unaware of this matter. I ask mister to forgive me.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s alright. This isn’t your idea. People your age cannot come up with these kinds of plans. Come and eat, how has your cultivation been these days?” Upon hearing Zhao Hai mention this, the three couldn’t help but be shaken. It can be said that they were very happy these recent days. With their constant cultivation, they already reached peak God-rank, half step towards the boundary. Just in their clan, only a a few people had reached this level.

They had received a lot of benefits because of Zhao Hai. At the very least, their speed of practice was much better compared to when they were back in their clans.

The three also knew that they couldn’t practice as peacefully in their clans as in the Hell King’s ship. There were a lot of matters in their families, tasks for people like them to do. Every time they take care of something, they would delay their cultivation. But if they don’t do those tasks, then they would be punished. This wasn’t the case with Zhao Hai. They had almost nothing to do here. As long as they kept contact with their family and be polite to Zhao Hai, everything was alright. Because of this, they had a lot of time to practice, which was very good for them.

After eating, Bingya and the others returned to their room. They wanted to communicate with their clan and ask about what just happened.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about them. After eating, he went back to his room as he sat drinking tea and looking at the screen. The screen wasn’t showing the situation with the foreign races, instead it showed the O’Neal family’s base.

The base construction of the O’Neal family was very quick. Although they didn’t use magic, their specially designed magic armors made things very convenient.

The base was enormous and the area around it has been levelled. Except for the advance base that was built at the center, the area around it also had beginning stages of construction. These were prepared for the future.

The O’Neal family’s commodities were also beginning to be transported to the Taurus Continent. It’s good since the spatial rift was located in the Radiant Empire. Surrounding the rift on three sides was water. Allowing the O’Neal family to move easily.

The O’Neal family’s Patriarch didn’t immediately leave. Instead, he remained in the Rosen Empire. He wanted to wait for the opportune time before moving. After all, moving the family’s base was a strategically crucial decision.

Laura was sitting besides Zhao Hai. After taking a sip of her tea, she turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, why are we waiting? Shouldn’t we make a move?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “We don’t need to do anything right now. Let’s just wait here and rest for a few days. To be honest, besides this place, nothing else in the Divine Realm interests me.”

Laura nodded. The other places in the Divine Realm were already insignificant to them. What’s left for them to do was to acquire the 11 combat suits as well as Elder Star’s Star Disk. As soon as they get these things, the Divine Realm was no longer worth paying attention to.

Lizzy was also looking at the O’Neal family. After some time, she turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, do you think the O’Neal family has an Ascension Magic Armor?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Currently, I don’t know. But now, the magic armors that they have are only up to God-rank. These magic armors are now useless to us. These magic armors are almost the same. Moreover, their materials aren’t that special. Acquiring higher ranked magic armors would be much harder.”

Laura nodded and said, “We already have a lot of formations inside the Space. However, we still don’t have the means to digest them. We can use these formations on other things, but not on magic armors.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “After dealing with the nine Supreme Elders, our next target would be the Atlanta Plane’s Ascension Magic Armor.”

Laura replied, “Right, I also think that we should go to the Atlanta Plane first. If the magic armor is really useful to us, then that would be the best.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “The reason I don’t want to go to the Underworld was because I can feel a sense of strangeness there. It’s possible that there are even more powerful beings than the Skeleton King. Because of this, I plan to head to the Atlanta Plane first.”

Megan seemed puzzled as she asked, “Elder Brother Hai, you mean that the Skeleton King isn’t a top existence in the Underworld? But didn’t you say that the Skeleton King could compare to the Supreme Elders? If the Underworld had stronger beings, then why would they still be in a lower realm?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “This I don’t know. I just feel like that Underworld isn’t simple. Because of this, we need to be completely prepared for our safety. I have a feeling that entering the Underworld would be much worse than entering the Cultivation Realm. It might even be more dangerous.”

When Megan and the other heard this, their expression couldn’t help but change. Although Zhao Hai said that it was just a feeling, those who were with him for a long time knew that Zhao Hai’s instinct was sometimes very accurate.

Laura nodded and said, “Alright. After we take care of the matters here, then we’ll head to the Atlanta Plane to take a look. Brother Hai, when do we start leading the O’Neal family to the Winged Pegasus Plane? I’m starting to get annoyed at the Winged Pegasus.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Forget it, just leave them for now, there’s no need to be annoyed. Just take a rest. We might have a tough battle in the following days.”

Laura smiled and said, “If it’s tough even for you, then there’s no need for us to join in. You can just solve it alone. You can take a rest Brother Hai, you can leave us here to watch.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, I’ll go take bath first then rest.”

After saying that, Zhao Hai went to the Hot Spring.

Completely different from the leisurely Zhao Hai were the foreign races. The three Patriarchs had come together to discuss their situation.

The Beastman Patriarch looked at the other two and said, “What do you think about this matter? What is the meaning of Zhao Hai’s reaction?”

The Dwarf Patriarch said, “I already said before that the plan won’t work. Zhao Hai is here to help us, but instead you want to demonstrate your authority. I won’t be able to help you if he goes away due to anger.”

The Elven Patriarch looked at the Dwarf Patriarch and said, “Alright, there’s no use arguing at this point. We need Zhao Hai to help us deal with the nine Supreme Elders. However, if Zhao Hai doesn’t come, will the nine Supreme Elders still attack us? From what I can see, the biggest enemy of the nine Supreme Elders aren’t us, but Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai is now about to destroy the Divines. If the nine Supreme Elders kept attacking us, then shouldn’t Zhao Hai appear?”

The Dwarf replied, “Let me ask, what have we done to help Zhao Hai? Why would he help us? Right, we got in contact with the vassal races and let them rebel. However, we all know that the impact of the rebellion is only very small. Zhao Hai doesn’t need our help. He can deal with the Divines on his own. In this case, do you think he had feelings towards us?”

The Beastmen Patriarch coldly snorted and said, “Alright, we wanted to demonstrate our power but instead lowering our position. Now that this had happened, we should think about how we can make Zhao Hai come back and help us. I think this is a good opportunity for Zhao Hai, he shouldn’t let this go. Zhao Hai understands that the nine Supreme Elders are his biggest enemies. He needs to concede a lot of things in order to face them. Because of this, despite knowing about our plan, he still came to support us. As long as we can please Zhao Hai, he will certainly come back.”

The Elven Patriarch actually knit her brows and said, “How about we ask Yehta and the others about Zhao Hai’s reaction? Let’s see if we still have an opportunity to bring Zhao Hai back. What do you think?”

The Beastman Patriarch nodded and said, “We should ask them. They followed behind Zhao Hai for a long time. Zhao Hai shouldn’t place them in an awkward situation.” The other two nodded. At this time, the Beastman Patriarch’s messenger fish suddenly sounded.

Chapter 953: Not Planning To Go Back

The Beastman Patriarch stared for a moment before holding his messenger fish. The messenger fish was connected to Bingya, the Beastman Patriarch quickly said, “Bingya, what happened?”

When Bingya heard the Patriarch’s voice, his anger couldn’t help but flare up again. However, he still replied, “Patriarch, why did you treat Mister Zhao Hai like that? He is very angry.”

Upon hearing Bingya’s inquiry, The Patriarch calmly replied, “Bingya, you should know your identity. You are a Beastman. You should consider our race first, not outsiders.”

It was at this point that Bingya angrily replied, “Is the Patriarch being responsible for our clan? Mister Zhao Hai said that the reason the nine Supreme Elders attacked us is because we dispatched troops to the Leo Continent. They attacked us because they want us to retrieve our troops. If our army doesn’t turn back to help us, then the Supreme Elders would return to the Leo Continent in order to eliminate the army. Wouldn’t that cause huge losses to the clan? Has the Patriarch thought about this?” Along the last lines of his statement, Bingya was almost roaring. Normally, he wouldn’t have the guts to do so. Beastmen were stern people. Daring to talk to the Patriarch like this was a deadly sin. However, since Bingya was quite angry, he couldn’t help but berate the Patriarch.

The Beastman Patriarch and the other two Patriarch couldn’t help but stare when Bingya roared. Then their expression changed. They knew that if what Bingya said was true, then their army in the Leo Continent would suffer under the Supreme Elders.

But the Beastman Patriarch recovered as he immediately replied, “Bingya, don’t say useless things. How is Zhao Hai now? He really doesn’t want to help us?”

When he heard the Patriarch, Bingya replied, “He shouldn’t for a while. But as long as the Patriarch asks Mister, he should go back. However, the Patriarch needs to be fast. Otherwise, if Mister Zhao Hai is gone, then our loss would be great.”

When the Patriarch heard this, he said, “Wait a moment.” Then he turned to the two patriarchs and said, “What do you two think about this?”

The Dwarf Patriarch said, “What else can we do, we need to ask him back. Pleasing someone as strong as Zhao Hai isn’t a disgrace. If Zhao Hai doesn’t care about our situation, then the one suffering losses would be us. Moreover, the nine Supreme Elders have no means to deal with him. Do you think that the foreign races could fight like Zhao Hai? If we push him away, then we would only harm ourselves with no benefits.”

Although the Elven Patriarch was arrogant, she wasn’t a fool, so she nodded and said, “We were indeed excessive this time. We need to ask Zhao Hai to come back. Nothing is more important than the lives of our clansmen. And with Zhao Hai’s help, our troops would be able to deal with the Leo Continent, providing us with a new good territory. Meanwhile, the vassal races would seep into their own continents. In the end, we would not have any problems keeping our continent.”

The Beastman Patriarch nodded and said, “Alright, then we’ll go ask him. In any case, the one who will benefit the most would be us.” The Dwarf Patriarch didn’t reply. Although we wasn’t happy about this, he also knew that it was good for their people. He wouldn’t deny anything that could benefit his race.

After seeing that nobody wanted to add anything, the Beastman Patriarch nodded and said, “Alright, let’s go and prepare. We’ll ask Bingya where they currently are and then we’ll go see them.”

The Dwarf Patriarch and the Elf Patriarch nodded before leaving the Beastman Patriarch’s room. After returning to their respective rooms, they immediately took their messenger fish out to ask whether the situation was indeed as Bingya said.

However, they didn’t think that Bingya and the others were now acting as one. While Bingya was talking to the Beastman Patriarch, Ryder and Yehta were also with him. Because of this, they heard everything that Bingya said to the Beastman Patriarch. So they didn’t say anything wrong when asked.

When the two put their messenger fishes down, they looked at each other and sighed. Bingya looked at the two and said, “I’m actually surprised. I thought our three races were very close. I didn’t expect the alliance to waver over a small thing.” Ryder sighed, then he turned to the two and said, “To tell you the truth, after this even, I’m won’t be heading back to the clan. I’m prepared to follow mister along with my family. I feel like following Mister would make my family more comfortable. At least Mister doesn’t use condescending tones when speaking to us. Moreover, he doesn’t seem to be eager in manipulating people for benefit.”

Ryder’s words made Bingya and Yehta stunned. The three of them had some prestige in their clans and they were quite famous. They were even called geniuses by some people. However, they were clear that there were more geniuses like them in the clan. The only reason these geniuses weren’t famous was because they haven’t had any merits to their name yet. This wasn’t because they were lazy, nor was it because they couldn’t take hardships. In the battle against the Divine Race, these geniuses died because of the decisions made by their own side.

In the beginning, Ryder didn’t think that the world would be this dark. However, the deeper he understood the matters of the world, the more he was made aware of the truth. Because of this, he was cautious whenever he handled affairs. He didn’t dare to be arrogant nor bear a deep grudge. Otherwise, a day would come when he would suffer the consequences of his decisions.

To be honest, to those who were ambitious, they would just treat this danger as a game. If they win, then they would be rewarded. But if they lose, then they would die.

However, Ryder wasn’t this kind of person. He belonged to the kind of people who want their family to grow and develop. Because of this, he was very uncomfortable when it came to plots. He already had too much of it in his life.

But he couldn’t fully divorce themselves from this life since he already entered the circle. Only dead people can get away from this. Even if you held great power, as long a you enter this circle, you still couldn’t guarantee that you can retire from it.

Now, Ryder finally found an opportunity for him to remove himself from such a life, and that was with Zhao Hai. With Zhao Hai’s strength, he wouldn’t be afraid of retaliation from the foreign races. Moreover, they had followed Zhao Hai for some time, so Ryder beleived that Zhao Hai already understood them. Because of this, he opened this matter up with Bingya and Yehta.

Bingya looked at Ryder and said, “Have you really thought this through? If you did, then let’s not think about whether your family agrees or not, instead, think about the other Dwarves. You will be offending them.”

Ryder nodded, “I have thought about it. I will ask Mister tomorrow and see if he will agree. If he does, then I will find a way to move my family.”  Bingya looked at Ryder and said, “Alright, I’ll ask Mister as well. Yehta, you’re with us right?”

Yehta looked at the two and smiled, “Of course, you can count me in. Why would I want to be left behind? Let’s not wait until tomorrow, let’s go now.”

Just as her voice fell, Zhao Hai’s voice was heard, “Hahaha. There’s no need to look for me. I’ve waited for this day for a long time.”

The three stared, then they saw Zhao Hai walked into their room. The three stared for a moment before they quickly got up and bowed. Then Bingya asked, “Mister, why did you come here?” Zhao Hai looked at the three and said, “I heard your words. What’s wrong? Surprised? Don’t forget, your inside my Hell King’s ship. Nothing can evade my sight inside the ship.”

As soon as the three heard Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but gawk. Zhao Hai looked at the three and smiled, “I don’t listen to your conversations all the time. But today is an exception. I know that you would talk to your Patriarchs. I just want to know the reactions of your clans. To be honest, their conduct disappointed me. However, you three made me glad.”

Bingya couldn’t help but get embarrassed, then he asked, “So Mister agrees with our request?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Agree, of course I agree. After the fight, you can go and take your families to the ship. I will arrange a good place for them, you can rest assured.”

Bingya looked at Zhao Hai, but he was still uncertain so he asked, “MIster, if I may ask, did you send the Demons and the Divines to that place? From what I can assume, you didn’t arrange them at the same place as the Ark Continent. So where did they go?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “This is my biggest secret. Since you asked, I can only tell you that it is an absolutely safe place. If you want to go, then I can take you over there to have a look. However, you need to pledge to your heart’s demon that without my permission you cannot tell anyone about this matter.”

Zhao Hai knew that for Bingya and the others, the binding force of a Blood Oath would be too weak. Fortunately, he was made aware of the Heart’s Demon Oath. The restraint of this oath is very strong. As long as one cultivates and pledges to a Heart’s Demon Oath, then once they violate their oath, they will be possessed by a Devil and die.

Chapter 954: Heart’s Demon Oath

Naturally, this oath wasn’t invincible. The most important condition for this oath was that the person who made this oath should have a lower cultivation compared to the one who issued for it.

Once the pledger becomes more powerful, then they can break this pledge at any time. Because of this, the oath wasn’t perfect.

However, this pledge was extremely useful for Zhao Hai. He has the Space, and as long as Bingya and the others enter for some time, then they wouldn’t betray him. Because of this guarantee, Zhao Hai dared to issue them this pledge.

This Heart’s Demon Pledge wasn’t from the Divine Realm. Instead, it was a Cultivation Realm’s method acquired from Lu Wei. This pledge would be used by both the pledger and the person who accepts the pledge. Otherwise, there would be no results. This was also the method used by Lu Wei to control the Divines. Other than calling Lu Wei the Deity, no other matters about him should spread.

Lu Wei used this method on the Divines due to the existence of the plane’s laws. This made it impossible for the Divines to be stronger than Lu Wei as long as they were in the Divine Realm. This enabled the Divines to keep Lu Wei’s secrets, including the method of collecting Faith Power. Among the Divines, there were only a few people who knew about Lu Wei’s method to collect Faith Power.

But although most of the Divines didn’t know what Lu Wei was doing in the Divine Realm, the method of Heart’s Demon Oath was passed down. Because of this, a lot of people in the Divine Realm were aware of it.

Naturally, Bingya and the others were also aware of this. However, they didn’t expect Zhao Hai to make them undergo this vow. The oath was useful for people with lower cultivation, but it couldn’t control a person’s loyalty. As long as you do what you vowed to do, then everything else you do was irrelevant.

For example, if one makes an oath to keep a secret, then as long as you keep that secret, you can do whatever you want. You can kill the one you made an oath to and it wouldn’t break the oath. This was also a way to cancel the oath. It can be said that this was the Oath’s largest flaw.

Bingya’s group didn’t think that Zhao Hai would restrain them using this oath. To be honest, this pledge was just too loose.

Zhao Hai looked at Bingya’s group and smiled, “What’s wrong? Are you unwilling?” Bingya quickly shook his head and said, “No, I willing. Mister can rest assured.”

Ryder and Yehta also agreed.

After the three agreed, they immediately began to murmur a spell. Zhao Hai also began to recite alongside them. The voices of the four people seem to meld together. Before long, the oath made by Bingya’s group began to form tangible words as it floated on top of their heads. On the other side, three little devils flew out of Zhao Hai’s body. These three devils were covered with green flames as they went to the words and ate them. After that, the devils merged with Bingya, Ryder, and Yehta’s bodies. That action concluded the oath-taking ceremony.

When Laura and the others saw this ceremony, they couldn’t help but sink into a daze. But after the Oath was cast, they immediately recovered.

Zhao Hai looked at Bingya’s group and said, “It’s done. You’re now part of my Buda Clan. Starting today, just call me Young Master. Laura, take them to see the Space. Don’t hide anything from them.”

Laura nodded before she turned to the trio and said, “Come with me.” The trio nodded. Zhao Hai waved his hand to open a spatial rift. Then the group entered.

After the group had gone, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. To be honest, he didn’t expect Bingya and the others to reach a decision at this time. However, this was a good thing. Zhao Hai had already seen their abilities. Even if he hadn’t seen everything they can offer, that doesn’t matter. As long as they become his people, then everything was fine.

Zhao Hai turned around and then entered his room. He believed that the Beastmen would come looking for him. Although the Beastman handled the matter strangely, they wouldn’t be able to hold off against the nine Supreme Elders for long. They weren’t fools, after weighing the advantages and disadvantages, they should be looking for him for help.

At this time, Laura brought Bingya and the others to enter the Space. Naturally, the first place they went to was the Ark Space.

And just like Zhao Hai said, Bingya and the others were shown the entirety of the Space. They were also shown the state of the three races, showing them their current living condition.

Bingya’s group looked at the Space with stunned faces. They didn’t think that there would be such a mysterious place. This was simply a perfect place.

Zhao Hai calmly sat inside his room as he observed the state of the O’Neal family. From time to time, he would switch the display to show the Leo Continent. He believed that the foreign race army should have been made aware of their current state. Zhao Hai could see the foreign races’ decision by looking at their movement.

The foreign race army in the Leo Continent didn’t move. They didn’t attack nor retreat. Instead, they guarded the cities that they had captured and just stayed there.

Upon seeing this, Zhao Hai knew that the foreign races would come and see him. If the foreign races didn’t plan to see him, then the army should have retreated. Otherwise, once the nine Supreme Elders returned, the army would be over. Now that the army didn’t move, this was to say that the foreign races had decided to deal with the nine Supreme Elders. With the current strength of the foreign races, there was only one way they could do this and it was to ask Zhao Hai for help.

For people in Zhao Hai’ level, fighting against them was no longer a matter of quantity. Even if they were besieged by millions and millions of people, they would still be able to kill all of the enemies. However, one shouldn’t forget that the foreign races also had three Supreme Elders. If they wanted to constrain the Supreme Elders, then as long as they don’t care about casualties, then they should be able to do it.

However, the elite troops of the foreign races were now attacking the Leo Continent. Entangling the Supreme Elders using an ordinary army wouldn’t be a good idea. Not to say about their strength being insufficient, their willpower was also weak. Their training wouldn’t be up to par to the point of affecting the entire outcome of any battle.

Zhao Hai also believed that even if the three Patriarchs had small brains, they still wouldn’t use this method. They would certainly cooperate with him. This was because using human wave tactics would just cause huge casualties without even a certainty that they would be able to block the nine Supreme Elders. Also, once the nine Supreme Elders plans to retaliate in full force, the foreign races would surely be living in a nightmare.

On the other hand, if they invite Zhao Hai, then with Zhao Hai’s strength, they would surely be able to hold the nine Supreme Elders back with little to no casualty. Only fools wouldn’t know which option to choose.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but rub his blood ghost staff. Presently, the staff only had the Scorpio symbol. He was hoping to see 12 symbols in the future.

Several hours passed and Laura returned with Bingya’s group. After seeing the Space, Bingya and the others have become more respectful towards Zhao Hai. They had seen the Ark Space, the Demon Space, the Fishman Space, the Goblin Space, as well as the Divine Space.

At the same time, Laura also told them the reason why Zhao Hai couldn’t accompany them. It was because if Zhao Hai stays too long inside the Space, then he would risk ascending once he goes out.

Upon hearing this, Bingya and the others couldn’t help but be surprised. Although the Divines had been spreading rumors about ascension, they haven’t seen anyone ascend before. But now, they heard Zhao Hai’s possible ascension.

Originally, Zhao Hai planned for Bingya and the others to stay in the Space for some time. However, Bingya had to come out this time because he had something to tell Zhao Hai. The Beastman Patriarch just called and asked about their current location. It seems like the Patriarch was preparing to meet Zhao Hai himself.

Because of this, Bingya didn’t have a choice but to come out of the Space. After hearing Bingya, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Did you tell them where they can meet us?”

Bingya nodded and said, “I did, but I didn’t tell them our current location. I told the Patriarch that the Young Master is heading towards the Taurus Continent. I believe that they will go there in order to find us.”

Zhao Hai nodded with satisfaction and said, “Alright. How was your visit to the Space? When your family comes, I will arrange a good place for them.” Bingya smiled and said, “Young Master, I’d like us to settle in Wild Dragon Island so that we can offer some help. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, then I’ll prepare a place for you there. However, although Wild Dragon Island seems relaxed, we don’t want to accommodate idlers. You need to find things that you can contribute towards.”

Bingya nodded and said, “Mister can rest assured. Our families aren’t senior officials or nobles. They couldn’t sit well if they do nothing.” Zhao Hai nodded and said, “In fact, you should have already seen that the jobs in the Space are just a means to spend time. Even if people didn’t go to work, they could still eat and be warm. But if you think about it, working will give people a purpose. Otherwise, they would be no different than a pig.”

Bingya and the others nodded. Then Zhao Hai asked, “Do you really want to move your family to the Space? If so, I can give you three command tokens. After you meet your family, you can use these tokens to open a spatial rift to the Space. What do you think?”

Bingya was stunned for a moment, then he said to Zhao Hai, “Young Master, we have one request.” Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, tell me.” Zhao Hai had a faint guess about their request. After Bingya and the others saw the situation inside the Space, they should have the inkling to have more people move in. After all, the situation inside the Space was very good.

And just as Zhao Hai thought, Bingya said, “Young Master, we want our clansmen to enter the Space.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I don’t oppose to having more people move to the Space. However, this will offend your Patriarchs. Under the current circumstances, I don’t want to have a conflict with them. At the very least, I don’t want any troubles before dealing with the nine Supreme Elders.”

The expression of the trio brightened up as they nodded. Then Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “Go and take a rest. You’ll have to stay on the ship in the next few days.” The three nodded before heading back to their rooms.

After waiting for the three to leave, Laura turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Congratulations Brother Hai. The three of them are quite strong. They also some ability to lead. They’re quite talented so they should be good after some training.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I really don’t care about using them. In fact, there are a lot of talented people like them inside the Space. I just want them to help me move the foreign races to the Space.”

Laura nodded. There were now a lot of races inside Zhao Hai’s Space. There are the people from the Ark Continent, the Fishmen, and the Demons. Almost all of these people were now Zhao Hai’s followers. They would agree to Zhao Hai’s requests, so there weren’t that much need for talented leaders. However, when it came to moving the foreign races to the Space, only Bingya and the others had the ability to do so. Zhao Hai could also use the undead to snatch people, just like what Zhao Hai did with the Divines. However, Zhao Hai didn’t want to use that method unless otherwise needed.

And just as Bingya said, the foreign races began to travel towards the Taurus Continent. The Hell King’s ship had also changed its route and headed there to wait for the Patriarchs.

It was good that the Taurus Continent wasn’t far. And with the Hell King’s ship’s speed, Zhao Hai arrived at the route to the Taurus Continent before long. Then he stopped in place as he waited.

Zhao Hai wasn’t worried much about waiting for the nine Supreme Elders. After all, the route from the Leo Continent and the foreign race territories was already mapped by him. If the Supreme Elders decided to run, Zhao Hai could quickly catch up.

Chapter 955: I Have a Request

Zhao Hai sat calmly on the ship’s deck. There was a small table on the side of his reclining chair with a cup of tea on top of it. Zhao Hai also held a book in his hand, one couldn’t help but see him as being unfettered and free.

His chair was made from his staff. Zhao Hai felt that sitting this way on the ship’s deck would make him look comfortable. This was to let the foreign races know that he wasn’t worried too much about their matter.

Laura and the others weren’t outside. Instead, it was Bingya’s group who stood beside Zhao Hai. The trio were becoming more and more respectful to Zhao Hai. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have a thing as magical as the Space. To be honest, they couldn’t wait to move their family.

At this time, Zhao Hai suddenly smiled. The book he was reading was just a book about magical formations, there wasn’t anything much about it. The reason why Zhao Hai had this book was just to let the Patriarch see that he was reading it.

Zhao Hai smiled because he knew that that Patriarchs had arrived. However, Zhao Hai didn’t go out and just lied down on his chair, reading his book. It looks like he wasn’t able to notice the visitors that arrived.

Before long, a group of people appeared in the sky. Being the representative, Bingya turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, they’re here.” Zhao Hai already had talked to them about what to do in advance.

Zhao Hai didn’t think about retaliating against the foreign races. There was no need to be spiteful. After all, Zhao Hai still needs to cooperate with them. Before he achieved his goals, then Zhao Hai would have to play nice. As for after that, nobody knows.

Zhao Hai placed his book on the small table before looking at the flying foreign races. The group was already quite nearby. Zhao Hai waved his hand, making the Hell King’s ship fly upwards to meet the guests.

Before long, Zhao Hai arrived in front of the foreign races. In front of the group was a Lion Beastman, then a Dwarf was to his left while an Elf was to the right.

The three leaders were also sizing Zhao Hai up. The two sides didn’t speak. After some time, the Lion bowed slightly towards Zhao Hai. He looked like an iron rod as he bowed, he looked very stiff, every move was done very laboriously. It can be said that he just made a light leaning motion as he said, “Beastman Patriarch Solomon has seen Mister Zhao Hai.”

Compared to the Lion, the Dwarf was much more polite as he bowed and said, “Dwarf Patriarch Leir has met Mister Zhao Hai.” The Elven woman also gave a bow and introduced herself, “Elf Yerd has seen Mister Zhao Hai.” The Elf Queen’s attitude towards Zhao Hai was better than the Beastman but worse than the Dwarf. Because of this, Zhao hai couldn’t figure out which side she was on.

Zhao Hai can see how intimate these people felt towards him judging by their attitudes. Zhao Hai had a good feeling about the Dwarf Patriarch. However, separating them at this time would be impossible.

Zhao Hai also gave a bow and said, “Zhao Hai has seen the Patriarchs. I didn’t expect the three Patriarch to pay me a personal visit. I’ll have to invite you to share a few cups with me on the ship.”

After being invited by Zhao Hai to embark, the three people looked at each other before they nodded. Then the trio descended to the Hell King’s ship. While on the ship, Zhao Hai waved his hand, producing three additional chairs.

After the three were asked to sit down, Laura and the others walked out of their room. On each of their hands were dishes and some wine.

Upon seeing this display, the three Patriarchs knew that Zhao Hai had been prepared. The Patriarchs couldn’t help but get stunned. Then the three turned towards where Bingya and the others were. Bingya just shook his head gently before turning to look at Zhao Hai.

Naturally, Zhao Hai saw their movements. Zhao Hai looked at the Patriarchs and smiled, “I’ll have to apologize to you three. Before, when I came to the Foreign race territory, I left because of a little bit of anger. I regretted my action at that time. And now that the Patriarchs came to personally visit, I couldn’t help but feel ashamed.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Solomon looked more arrogant, Lier looked quite ashamed, while Yerd seems unresponsive, however, a glint flashed through her eyes.

Zhao Hai immediately knew what was going on upon seeing their reaction. Solomon thought that Zhao Hai admitted defeat. While Lier thought that Zhao Hai was satirizing them. As for Yerd, Zhao Hai didn’t know what she was currently thinking about.

Solomon, with his proud expression, looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister came in to help us, we shouldn’t have taken things too far. It was only because the nine Supreme Elders had been very ferocious in their attack that we decided to be extra careful. If Mister misunderstood, then let this Solomon offer his apologies.” Although he said this, Solomon’s arrogant expression betrayed his apology.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “So the Patriarch is just being careful, this Zhao Hai can understand. So why did the Patriarchs come and see me today?”

A flash of anger appeared in Solomon’s eyes. He thought that he had already given Zhao Hai face by his apology. Zhao Hai shouldn’t be acting ignorant at this time.

However, Solomon was also aware that he couldn’t offend Zhao Hai at this moment. Therefore, he could only answer, “The three of us came today to invite Mister to the foreign race territory in order to cooperate with us in dealing with the nine Supreme Elders. What does Mister think?”

Zhao hai smiled faintly and said, “Of course I agree. It’ll be great if we can deal with the nine Supreme Elders. But before I go and fight, I have a request that I’d like the three of you to agree first.”

The trio looked at each other, they didn’t expect Zhao Hai to negotiate with them at this time. Solomon was angry, but he still had to suppress his temper, so he said, “Mister, please tell us.”

Zhao Hai replied, “It’s this, since we will deal with the nine Supreme Elders, then after we’re done, their ultimate weapons would lose their masters. I’m not greedy, so the ultimate weapon would go to the ones who kill their master. Do you agree to this?”

The three looked at each other before they all nodded. Although they want to obtain the ultimate weapons, they knew that if they didn’t accept Zhao Hai’s request, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t help them. Because of this, they could only agree to Zhao Hai’s condition.

However, the three didn’t know that this wasn’t Zhao Hai’s request. His request wasn’t this simple, so Zhao Hai continued, “I happen to like researching things, this includes the Ultimate Weapons. If I’m able to get ultimate weapons in this fight, then I’d like to exchange it with your three clans so that I can do my research. This also includes the three ultimate weapons of your clan as well as the Scorpio ultimate weapon that I have. After I’m finished with my research, I will give all the ultimate weapons to you guys, including my Scorpio ultimate weapon.” Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as an ultimate weapon appeared on deck, it was the Scorpio combat suit.

Although Zhao Hai’s conditions were very awkward, Solomon and the others could understand that Zhao Hai wanted the 13 ultimate weapons to be in his hands.

This caused the three to get awkward. However, when they thought about Zhao Hai’s later conditions, they couldn’t help but feel that it was possible. After all, Zhao Hai was giving up the combat suit that he had.

Zhao Hai’s possession of the Scorpio combat suit was already known by the three Patriarchs. Even if Zhao Hai couldn’t obtain a combat suit in the upcoming battle, his own combat suit as a condition was already enough.

Solomon looked at Zhao Hai and said, “If Mister wants to study the ultimate weapons for a few days, then do you need to have all of them in your hands?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Of course not. I can study them one by one. This also depends on the number of ultimate weapons that I have. If I haven’t killed a Divine Supreme Elder, then I can research one ultimate weapon at a time. If I have two ultimate weapons, then I can research two at a time. But no matter how many ultimate weapons I have, my research wouldn’t take more than three days. What do you think?”

No matter which angle Solomon and the others looked at it, this was a profitable trade for them. How could they just let go of this opportunity? The three looked at each other before Solomon turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, are you telling the truth?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Of course, I don’t need to lie. You can rest assured. In any case, you could always keep at least three ultimate weapons in your hand at all times. What do you need to be afraid of?”

The three nodded simultaneously. Solomon looked at the other two, then after seeing their agreeing nod, he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Then we’ll accept Mister’s condition.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, then since we have reached an agreement, there’s no need to discuss anything more. Let’s go and deal with the Supreme Elders. Please have your guards enter the ship so that we can get going.”

The three looked at Zhao Hai before turning their heads to their guards. All in all, their guards numbered 30 thousand people. How could all of them fit inside the ship? Wouldn’t Zhao Hai’s ship sink?

Zhao Hai saw their doubtful expressions, but he just smiled and said, “Rest assured, my ship can fit all of us. Just order them to head in.” The three Patriarchs nodded before they waved their hands, commanding their guards to embark on the ship. Under the shocked gzes of the three Patriarchs, the Hell King’s ship acted like a bottomless vessel as it continuously took in all of the 30 thousand guards. The three curiously inspected the situation of their men only to find out that each guard had their own personal room. This caused the three Patriarchs to be startled.

Chapter 956: If You Believe In Me, Then You Will Have Eternal Life!

While Solomon and the others were looking at the Hell King’s ship, the ship had already departed. And when they headed back out into the deck, they were already close to reaching the Aries Continent.

When Solomon and the others saw this, they couldn’t help but look at each other. It seems like they had to re-evaluate Zhao Hai’s strength.

They knew that Zhao Hai was strong, but they weren’t able to see it firsthand. Zhao Hai being able to rush towards the Aries Continent in such a short time was a testament to his own strength.

Zhao Hai stopped right outside the Aries Continent, he didn’t enter but instead looked at Solomon’s group and said, “Patriarchs, where are we heading?”

Solomon looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Let’s turn and head to the Libra Continent.” After that, Zhao Hai turned the ship towards the Libra Continent and then went straight towards it.

The speed of the Hell King’s ship had now reached its limit. However, the ship was still very calm, as though it was stationary and only had a few light breezes. This made Solomon and the others more and more impressed.

As the ship was traveling, Zhao Hai turned his head to the three Patriarchs and said, “Patriarchs, I’m not too familiar with the foreign races, can you help me understand?”

The three Patriarchs looked at each other. And then, Solomon and Yerd took a step back, leaving Leir in front. It was clear that they wanted Leir to do the explaining.

After Leir saw this situation, he couldn’t help but smile awkwardly and said, “It looks like I will be the one explaining to Mister.” Solomon nodded before he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, we want to rest first. Leir should be able to accommodate you. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai nodded before he turned to Bingya and said, “Bingya, I’ll have to ask you to lead Patriarch Solomon and Queen Yerd to their rooms so that they can take a rest.”

Bingya’s group nodded before proceeding to lead Solomon and Yerd to their rooms. Yerd managed to notice that their rooms were one of the better rooms inside the ship. However, there seems to be more of these types of rooms present.

After waiting for Solomon and the others to head down the ship, Zhao Hai clapped his hands. Laura and the others immediately offered Zhao Hai some wine. This time, the wine was one of the better wines in Zhao Hai’s hands. Zhao Hai offered Leir a glass before he held his own and said, “Patriarch Leir, among your group who sought me, only you saw me in a positive light. Let this Zhao Hai offer you a glass.”

As soon as Leir heard Zhao Hai, his face couldn’t help but show his embarrassment. He also thought that Solomon was quite excessive this time. However, he still held his glass up and replied, “Actually, Solomon and Yerd doesn’t have any bad intentions. They’re just used to acting like this because of their position. I hope that Mister won’t be offended.”

Zhao Hai pretended to be angry as he said, “If it wasn’t for the fact that I wanted to deal with the nine Supreme Elders, then I wouldn’t have stomached such attitude. Alright, there’s no need to talk about this. With Patriarch Leir’s temperament, I’m certain that we would have a good future together.”

Leir smiled and replied, “Mister is really lifting me up. It’s my pleasure to be Mister’s friend. If you need the help of the Dwarven race in the future, then please don’t hesitate to tell us.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “To be honest, I feel quite strange. Back in the Ark Continent, my relationship with the three races is quite good. Whether it be the Dwarves, Beastman, or Elves, all of them are my friends. However, it seems like the Beastmen and the Elves of the Divine Realm aren’t looking at me favorably.”

Leir couldn’t help but bitterly smile. He was very clear about why Solomon didn’t like Zhao Hai. In Solomon’s eyes, Zhao Hai was a destroyer of the established order. He managed to throw off the balance of the Divine Realm, this caused Solomon to be afraid of him.

Zhao Hai was just too strong. With his own strength, he managed to almost destroy the entire Divine Race. The Divines were much stronger than the foreign races. And if Zhao Hai decides to turn on the foreign races, then the foreign races would have a hard time stopping him. It was also for this reason that Elf Yerd was reluctant to get in contact with Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai looked at Leir’s expression and smiled, “Actually, I couldn’t stay in the Divine Realm for a long time. I don’t belong to this place and I have more matters to attend to. The reason I dealt with the Divines was because I wanted the Ark Continent to have vengeance. To be honest, my enmity towards the Divines have gone too thin. If I wasn’t worried about the nine Supreme Elders eliminating the foreign races, then I might have left the Divine Realm a long time ago.”

Leir looked puzzled at Zhao Hai, “Why would Mister say that? The Divines have been greatly damaged. Even if the nine Supreme Elders retreats, they shouldn’t be able to deal with us right?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “No, it’s the opposite. If the Supreme Elders manages to retreat, then your days would be bad.”

Leir was still puzzled, but before he manages to ask, Zhao Hai continued, “The reason why you can block the Divines was because the Divine Race aren’t a united group. Instead, they divided themselves into ten different groups, each had their own Elders and plans for going forward. Because of this, they didn’t do their best during their attacks towards the foreign races. And when a group of them attack you, their Supreme Elders were less than what you have. But this time, the nine Supreme Elders are concentrated in the Leo Continent. This means that a single Divine Race group now has more Supreme Elders than you. As the war progresses, the foreign races would slowly be defeated.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Leir couldn’t help but stare blankly. He wiped a cold sweat, they haven’t thought about this point. After being reminded by Zhao Hai, Leir felt that things are far from being great as they imagined.

Zhao Hai looked at Leir and continued, “To be honest, dealing with the nine Supreme Elders wouldn’t provide any benefits for me. Back in the Taurus Continent, the Supreme Elders wanted to threaten me using the Thunder Clan and the others. And at that time, they realized that if they return to the Leo Continent, then they would have a chance to save the Divine Race. Because of this, they went to attack you so that you would make your troops retreat. In this case, I am not in the equation anymore. They don’t care about me. I don’t have to deal with them and I can just leave. But do you know why I didn’t leave? No matter what, your races provided me with help in dealing with the Divine Race. You also sent Divine Artifacts to your people back in the Ark Continent, providing them with great kindness. My relationship with the three races in the Ark Continent is very good. I’m a Crown Prince of the Beastman, and a Foreign Elder to the Elves and the Dwarves. Because of this, I decided to help you one time in dealing with the Divine Race.”

Leir listened quietly to Zhao Hai’s words and found out that Zhao Hai wasn’t wrong. From looking at Zhao Hai’s appearance, he seems to be a kind of person who didn’t want to rule the Divine Realm. Otherwise, he wouldn’t destroy the Divine Race. Zhao Hai could just leave, he didn’t need to care about the muddied waters of the Divine Realm anymore.

Zhao Hai looked at Leir and smiled, “Patriarch Leir, you’re a Patriarch, so you should be familiar with this word.”

Leir became confused at Zhao Hai’s query. So upon hearing Zhao Hai, Leir tilted his head and asked, “What word?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and answered, “Ascension!”

As soon as Leir heard this, he couldn’t help but gawk. Then he said, “Ascension? Does Mister want to ascend?” As a Patriarch, he wasn’t a stranger to ascension. However, he didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have thoughts about it.

Zhao Hai looked at Leir and said, “Do you think the Divine Realm can hold me?”

Leir stared, then he smiled bitterly and said, “Right, even the nine Supreme Elders couldn’t stop you. With your current strength, there’s no way for the Divine Realm to accommodate you. The next step for you would be to ascend.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Right, I will ascend after taking care of things in the Divine Realm. Because of this, I won’t be here in the future. Later on, the foreign races wouldn’t have anything to do with me.”

Leir smiled bitterly, he felt unworthy because of Solomon. Solomon was worried that Zhao Hai would replace the position that the Divine Race held. It seems like Zhao Hai wants to ascend, he simply didn’t have anything left to do in the Divine Realm.

Upon thinking up to here, Leir couldn’t help but sigh. Then he drank from his wine glass before looking at Zhao Hai and asking, “Mister, did you subdue the Demon Race?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Correct. The Demons, the people in the Ark Continent, as well as the Goblins have now become my people. They’re currently in a very safe place. Maybe I could even take them with me when I ascend.” When Leir heard this, he stared for a moment before he said, “Bring them when you ascend? How is that possible?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “What if I had better things like the Hell King’s ship?” Leir’s eyes lit up, then he said, “Is Mister telling the truth?”

Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “If you believe my words, then it’s true. If you don’t then it’s false. And if you believe in me, then you will have eternal life! Hahahaha.” After that, Zhao Hai drank his wine before turning to look at the distant horizon.

Leir stood up, his eyes seem to be filled with passion as he said, “Mister, can you take us along?”

Zhao Hai chuckled a bit before answering, “This isn’t something that you can decide in a short time. In your case, ruminate on this idea for some time. However, I hope you don’t tell Patriarch Solomon and Queen Yerd about this.”

Chapter 957: Violent Debate

When Leir heard this, he couldn’t help but feel regretful. He also knew that things like these weren’t something that he could decide alone.

At this time, five people came out. Solomon had a smile on his face as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, let this Solomon congratulate you. I didn’t think that Mister would want to ascend, I’m really envious.”

As soon as Leir heard Solomon, he couldn’t help but get startled. Then he turned to look at Zhao Hai. He thought that Zhao Hai’s ascension was only something that the two of them knew. Now it seems like this wasn’t the case.

Zhao Hai gave Leir a smile, making the latter relax. Then Zhao Hai turned his head to Solomon and said, “The Patriarch’s congratulations are a bit early. I’m not even sure if I can ascend.”

Solomon smiled and said, “Not early, not early. The Divine Realm cannot hold someone like Mister for too long. Mister should inform us when you ascend, we need to attend the ceremony. If this Solomon can see someone ascend, then I wouldn’t have lived this life in vain.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Of course. If I am about to ascend, then I will inform the Patriarch. Rest assured.”

When Leir heard the conversation between Zhao Hai and Solomon, he couldn’t help but think. Then he turned to look at Bingya who stood behind Solomon and Yerd. He now understood that Solomon had called Bingya over to his room and asked about Zhao Hai’s situation. It should have been Bingya who told Solomon about Zhao Hai’s ascension. Because of this, Solomon’s attitude towards Zhao Hai had changed.

However, by listening to Solomon’s words, it seems like Bingya didn’t tell him that Zhao Hai can take people along with him when he ascends. This might be because Bingya and the others were unaware of this fact.

If Bingya didn’t know, then there was nothing strange about the current situation. But if they knew but didn’t say it, then that could only mean one thing, they had already become Zhao Hai’s people.

At the thought of this, Leir couldn’t help but take another sip of his wine. After placing his wine glass down, he felt shock. He understood that Bingya’s group had already sided with Zhao Hai.

When Leir placed his glass down, he understood the truth. Zhao Hai only gave him a glass to drink, yet Leir already felt close to him. He even felt dissatisfied towards Solomon and Yerd. Bingya and the others had been with Zhao Hai for so long, so how could they not be swayed by Zhao Hai’s influence? Additionally, with the bait of being taken along when Zhao Hai ascends, it was natural for Bingya and the others to submit to Zhao Hai.

After figuring this out, Leir couldn’t help but take another glance at Zhao Hai; who was currently talking with Solomon. Leir suddenly found Zhao Hai to be terrifying. He seemed to have calculated every step of the way. And even if one knew his purpose, there was still no way to stop him. Zhao Hai would use a person’s interest in order to pull them into his circle. As long as he wants something, then he would make sure that everyone would have a share. In this case, even if one knew his plans, they would still find themselves helping him.

Was he an ally, or an enemy? What was he? As he thought about the state of the nine Supreme Elders, Leir couldn’t help but shudder. As the Dwarf Patriarch, he had a certain understanding about the Supreme Elders. Upon seeing the appearance of the nine Supreme Elders, Leir was shocked. If Elder Star and the others didn’t use their ultimate weapons, then Leir wouldn’t have believed that they were the Divine Race’s Supreme Elders. And to think that this suffering was caused by Zhao Hai alone.

When he thought about this, Leir quickly decided to not be Zhao Hai’s enemy. Leir couldn’t help but look at Solomon’s relaxed expression as he chatted with Zhao Hai. Leir sighed in his heart, he knew that Zhao Hai wouldn’t befriend Solomon and Yerd. At the same time, Zhao Hai was also giving Leir a test. If Leir could keep Zhao Hai’s secret, then Zhao Hai might treat him as a friend. If Leir couldn’t, then he won’t be getting on Zhao Hai’s good side.

Leir let out a long breath. He held his wine glass towards Zhao Hai and laughed, “Mister, you’re liquor is really great. I don’t know if MIster would agree to giving me some. If I cannot drink this liquor later on, then I’m afraid I would have trouble sleeping.”

Although this seems to be a simple request for liquor and nothing else, there was a hint of friendliness in those words. If he didn’t regard Zhao Hai as a friend, then how could he ask for Zhao Hai’s wine? Who would want to drink a stranger’s liquor?

Leir talked to Zhao Hai in this manner because he believed that Zhao Hai could understand. Zhao Hai was a smart man.

And just as Leir thought, Zhao Hai’s smile became wider. He turned to Leir and laughed, “If the Patriarch likes my wine, then I will definitely give you some. This is not a big deal.”

Solomon and Yerd didn’t suspect anything. They were aware that Dwarves were famed for their love of liquor. Additionally, Leir had always been acting positively towards Zhao Hai, so asking for liquor was not strange.

At this time, a continent appeared on the horizon. The Continent gave one a heavy earthly feeling.

Leir stood up and pointed to the Continent and then said, “Mister, that is the Libra Continent where the Dwarves live. It is the place with the richest deposit of minerals in the Divine Realm. The reason why the nine Supreme Elders attacked us was because almost all of the weapons used by the Beastmen and the Elves were made by us. As long as they deal with us, then they would find it easier to deal with the other two races.”

Solomon and Yerd didn’t find fault in Leir’s words. This was because Leir was right. The three foreign races were interdependent on each other. The Elves mainly supplied food, the Dwarves supply the weapons, and the Beastmen provide mounts and armor. This way, the three races were closely related.

However, the Dwarves were a bit more important. This was because both the Dwarves and the Beastmen were already mostly self sufficient on food. As for armors, God-rank experts rarely find any uses for them. On the other hand, weapons were indispensible for any expert. Good weapons would allow someone to fight stronger enemies.

Because of this, the Divines always attacked the Dwarves first. But since the other two races were quite close, they were able to support the Dwarves. This allowed the Dwarves to stay safe for a long time.

Zhao Hai nodded, “Dwarven weapons are indeed very good. Back in the Ark Continent, I had a lot of interactions with the Dwarves. At that time, the three foreign races were being ostracized by the Radiant Church. There basically isn’t any easy way to come in contact with them. In the end, I was able to make good business. I would trade for the Beastman Race’s milk wine with Dwarven Weapons. I also use Elven artware to trade for goods with the Humans. Then I use what I earn to buy living commodities for the Beastmen and the Dwarves. Hehe.”

Upon hearing this, Leir and the other gawked. They didn’t have much information about Zhao Hai’s life back in the Ark Continent. Now that Zhao Hai revealed his experiences, they couldn’t help but feel that Zhao Hai was a merchant.

The trio looked at Zhao Hai with confused expressions. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The Patriarchs aren’t thinking incorrectly, I am indeed a Human Merchant, a very good one. Not only did I do business with the Humans, I also traded with the Beastmen, the Dwarves, the Elves, the Fishmen, basically almost everyone in the Ark Continent. Of course there are exceptions, I didn’t trade with the Radiant Church. Since I am a Dark Mage, they would burn immediately want to burn me on sight. I also didn’t trade with the Dragons since they are the dogs of the Divine Race. And finally, I didn’t trade with the magic beasts, they really didn’t have anything that I want.”

Leir and the others just smiled, they were now more curious about Zhao Hai’s life back in the Ark Continent. How could a Merchant have such a status? How did he manage to acquire his current strength?

As they were thinking, the ship had entered the Libra Continent. Zhao Hai calmly looked around the place. However, it seems like there were no fighting going on. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but turn to Leir and asked, “Where are the nine Supreme Elders? Aren’t they here?”

Leir smiled bitterly and answered, “They’re here. But us Dwarves live just like our people back in the Ark Continent, in caves. After the nine Supreme Elders came here, they already destroyed several of our settlements. Because they were caves, we couldn’t see any signs here in the surface.”

After that, Solomon interjected, “They never did this before. The Divine Supreme Elders are very arrogant. In the past, they greatly disdained going underground. However, they broke the norm this time. They engaged in guerilla warfare with us inside the caves. Because of this, most of the fights happen underground.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “They have no other way. This time, they only came with nine People. They don’t want to waste too much energy, so the best way they can go forward is to just kill people.”

The group nodded. The means of combat used by the nine Supreme Elders had greatly changed. It seems like they really suffered a huge loss under Zhao Hai.

At this time, a mountain in the distance suddenly exploded. Then several humanoid forms came out.

Zhao Hai saw this and immediately said, “It’s the Supreme Elders. Patriarchs, I will have to evict you from the ship. I won’t have time to take care of you when the fight starts.”

After saying that, Zhao Hai waved his hand. Solomon’s group immediately got ejected from the ship, as did Bingya’s group and the thirty thousand guards. Nobody knew how they managed to get out of the ship.

While they were dumbfounded, Zhao Hai already threw himself towards the battlefield.

Naturally, the two sides who were fighting had noticed Zhao Hai. When they saw Zhao Hai, the three foreign race Supreme Elders couldn’t help but smile. They were being besieged by Elder Star and the others. Now that Zhao Hai was here, he might be able to save them.

At the same time, when Elder Star and the others saw Zhao Hai, their expressions also turned happy.Then their faces turned serious before reforming in preparation for fighting Zhao Hai.

However, the three foreign race Supreme Elders actually separated from the fight. They turned away from Elder Star and the others but they didn’t go near Zhao Hai.

Upon seeing this situation, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but criticize them. The three Supreme Elders were too stupid. In face of an enemy, they actually acted like this. Were they making it clear that they weren’t in the same side as him? This point could be used against them.

And just as Zhao Hai thought, when Elder Star saw the reaction of the foreign Supreme Elders, his eyes flashed. Then he turned calm but he had a hint of joy in his expression.

Zhao Hai slowed his ship down as he stopped about a hundred meters away from Elder Star’s group. Meanwhile, the three Supreme Elders placed themselves on the left side of the Divines. This caused the parties to form a triangle.

Elder Star looked at Zhao Hai with eyes full of hatred as he said, “Zhao Hai, I didn’t think that you would actually appear here. For a black-hearted person like you, you actually came to help the foreign races. I couldn’t help but be surprised. You just watched as the entire Thunder Clan got exterminated. So why did you come here to help the foreign races?”

Elder Star’s words were nothing less than poisonous. This was simply telling the foreign races that Zhao Hai was a cruel person. He just stayed still as the Thunder Clan was exterminated by Elder Star’s group, he didn’t offer any help. Now that Zhao Hai came here to assist, he surely has some sinister plot going on.

Zhao Hai looked at Elder Star and smiled, “You know that I can’t beat you, so why would I run into your trap back then? Do you think I’m stupid? But now, the situation is different. Along with the three Foreign Supreme Elders, I have confidence in keeping you here. In a few days, you would be the remaining Divines in the Divine Realm. After that, the Divine Realm would belong to the foreign races.”

A sharp tongue, this was a true sharp tongue. Elder Star used words in order to put a wedge on Zhao Hai’s relationship with the foreign races. At the same time, Zhao Hai also used words in order to convince the foreign races to deal with Elder Star’s group. Only then could the foreign races gain complete freedom in the Divine Realm.

Elder Star’s mouth turned into a sneer as he said, “Is it? If you deal with us, then wouldn’t the Divine Realm belong to you!?”

Elder Star wasn’t easy to deal with. He launched another verbal blow.

Chapter 958: Fierce Battle

Zhao Hai could understand Elder Star’s purpose. Elder Star wanted to remind the foreign races that if Zhao Hai could deal with the Divines, then he could also deal with the foreign races.

Checks and balances was a method used by leaders, almost everyone used it. If a leader couldn’t use checks and balances, then it would be impossible for him to be a great leader. [1]

Elder Star was the Central Continent’s Supreme Elder, so he was very familiar with this system. Naturally, he also knew how to use it.

Sure enough, after Elder Star said this, the three foreign race Supreme Elders didn’t look great as they turned to Zhao Hai. It’s very obvious that they realized Elder Star’s thought a long time ago. Otherwise, they would have went to Zhao Hai after seeing him. Instead, they chose to maintain a safe distance away.

After seeing the reaction of the foreign race Elders, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile faintly as he turned to looked Elder Star and said, “Elder Star doesn’t have to worry about this. I already discussed this matter with the Foreign Race Patriarchs. After I deal with your group, I will then leave the Divine Realm. The Patriarchs also knew the reason why I have to leave.”

Zhao Hai’s words towards Elder Star made the three Supreme Elders feel embarassed. Zhao Hai turned his head towards the three Supreme Elders and said, “If you lose the opportunity to deal with them, then you will never have the upper hand. I will leave the Divine realm in the future. And when the time comes, only the three of you will be left to deal with the nine Supreme Elders.”

When the three Supreme Elders heard Zhao Hai, their complexion couldn’t help but change. To be honest, Zhao Hai’s words hit them in their greatest weak spot.

Zhao Hai’s threat was just a possibility, it was still left to be proven. After all, Zhao Hai was their ally at this time. If Zhao Hai left, then the entire Divine Realm would be left to the foreign races and the remnant group of the Divine Race. However, the Divines were the enemies of the foreign races, they were hostile towards each other for tens of thousands of years. Their hatred had already penetrated their bones. If the foreign races didn’t use this opportunity, then the foreign races would have to be left to deal with the Divines all on their own when Zhao Hai leaves.

When Elder Star heard this, he knew that his side of the debate was not doing well. His eyes narrowed as he gave his command, “Let’s begin!” Along with his voice, he also activated his Star Disk.

The Star Disk moved in Elder Star’s hand. It rotated quickly as it launched lights in all directions. After that, Zhao Hai felt a change in the surroundings. Then he was met with a starry sky.

Zhao Hai didn’t panic as he observed the situation around him. The distant sky had constellations floating around. What made Zhao Hai strange was the fact that the Star Disk seem to have much more constellations than he expected.

After looking at these extra constellations, Zhao Hai understood that they belonged to the foregn races. It was the Aries Constellation, Libra Constellation, and the Virgo Constellation.

Zhao Hai didn’t know if it was his imagination or not, but the three constellations seem to be quite grey. The three combat suits also seem to be struggling.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Elder Star, I didn’t expect you to use this move. However, this didn’t work the last time. Did you forget? I have broken this before.”

After Zhao Hai said that, he moved his hand as the Dao Lotus went to the sun where the Star Disk was. With Zhao Hai’s power as well as the Dao Lotus’ strength, a loud bang was heard before the illusion in the sky disappeared.

But although the illusion had disappeared, Zhao Hai discovered the situation was still not very good. The three Supreme Elders of the foreign races seem to be under Elder Star’s control. They were standing there, motionless, but their bodies seem to be gently shaking.

Zhao Hai knew that the three Supreme Elders were fighting against Elder Star’s control. They were currently in the process of breaking loose. But before that, Zhao Hai had to face the nine Supreme Elders alone.

Elder Star looked at Zhao Hai and laughed, “Zhao Hai, coming here is your biggest mistake. Now that the three of them are restrained by me, you will have to face us all alone. Let’s see what you can do now.”

Zhao Hai just gave a faint smile as he said, “What? Do you think I’m afraid of you?” After that, Zhao Hai waved his hand as a red scorpion went out of his staff. The scorpion shook its body before it threw itself towards the Supreme Elders. The Surpeme Elders’ expressions changed. Naturally, they could recognize that this was the Scorpio Clan’s ultimate weapon. They didn’t dare to underestimate it, so Gold Ben went forward in order to fight the scorpion.

Zhao Hai didn’t pay any attention towards Gold Ben. Instead, he had the Hell King’s ship fly towards Elder Star. However, the other Supreme Elders besides Elder Star went forward to stop him.

At this time, Zhao Hai sent Laura and the others to the Space. Then he reduced the ship’s size and handed its control over to Cai’er. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai wielded his staff as he went to attack the Leo Supreme Elder. The staff in his hand turned into a sledgehammer before it slammed towards the Leo Supreme Elder.

The Pisces Supreme Elder, Mingdasir, as well as the Cancer Supreme Elder, Jie Yu, came to assist. As the group clashed, a dogfight immediately occured.

However, since Zhao Hai wasn’t able to use his full strength, he was pushed to the defensive side. But he wasn’t in any real danger. Meanwhile, Elder Star closed his eyes, his head was sweating. He was trying his hardest to suppress the three Supreme Elders as long as possible.

The three Supreme Elders have forgotten that Elder Star’s Star Disk was able to suprress them. The reason why Elder Star didn’t use this earlier was because using the Star Disk in this manner wasn’t an easy task. It would require immense energy from Elder Star, it would also have some side effects.

The 13 ultimate weapons were a set. If they were used to face an enemy, then they were naturally very powerful. However, if you have them fight each other, then it would cost a lot It was just like having a person fight his right hand using his left. The one who would be injured would be the man himself.

Solomon and the others observed the fight in the distance. They couldn’t help but feel that the battle was too terrifying. Although the fighting was in the sky, hills around the Supreme Elders and Zhao Hai were being destroyed while mountains were swaying violently. At the same time, ripples in the firmament could be clearly seen. Solomon and the others felt that the skies were being twisted.

At this moment, Gold Ben was fighting with the red scorpion, the Hell King’s ship was also able to tie four Supreme Elders down, and Zhao Hai was fighting three Supreme Elders. Zhao Hai’s opponents were exerting their full force. They knew that as long as they eliminate Zhao Hai, the Hell King’s ship would turn useless.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t easily dealt with. Although Jie Yu’s group had the upper hand, Zhao Hai was still able to counter-attack. At the very least, self-preservation was possible for Zhao Hai.

At this point, Zhao Hai’s body had turned into its crystal form. His magic staff was ever changing. In any moment, it would turn into a weapon, and the next moment it would become two weapons. Even after being besieged by three people, Zhao Hai was still far from defeat.

Jie Yu and the others couldn’t help but worry. They knew that it was impossible to hold off the three Supreme Elders for a long time. If they couldn’t deal with Zhao Hai soon, then when the three Supreme Elders gets loose, the state of the battle would be flipped over.

Jie Yu and the others didn’t know how fierce Zhao Hai was. Now, they finally understood that they had underestimated Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai was just too strong.

Time passed by and Jie Yu’s group were getting more and more worried. Elder Star was also sweating more and more. At the same time, the three Supreme Elders were shaking more violently.

It was at this moment that Zhao Hai felt something strange. Although he was at a disadvantage, he wasn’t worried, he wasn’t even injured. Because of this, Zhao Hai was still able to observe the current state of the battlefield.

Although the Hell King’s ship had tied four Supreme Elders, these Supreme Elders weren’t really incapable of leaving the battle. As long as three of them stop the ship, the other one could just leave for a moment and deal with the three Supreme Elders. This would eliminate Elder Star’s troubles. However, why haven’t they done this?

Suddenly, Zhao Hai thought of something that he’d like to try. He immediately contacted Cai’er using his mind. When Cai’er heard Zhao Hai, she immediately complied.

While Jie Yu and the others were heavily engaged with Zhao Hai, a group of undead suddenly appeared near Elder Star. Upon seeing this, Jie Yu and the others weren’t afraid, instead they looked at Zhao Hai with ridicule. They thought that Zhao Hai wanted to deal with Elder Star using these undead.

However, what the undead did next startled them. The undead didn’t deal with Elder Star, instead, they turned around and threw themselves towards the three Supreme Elders.

Upon seeing this, the complexion on Jie Yu and the others’ faces changed. However, they knew that they wouldn’t be able to stop the undead. The undead established their Domain and attacked the foreign race Supreme Elders. When Solomon and the others saw this, they couldn’t help but be confused. They didn’t understand why Zhao Hai would attack their Supreme Elders at this time.

But much to their surprise, when the Undead attacked the foreign race Supreme Elders, a loud bang was heard. The bodies of the foreign race Supreme Elders shook as they opened their eyes slowly. Meanwhile, Elder Star’s body shook before he vomited blood. This made Solomon and the others even more shocked, they couldn’t understand what just happened.

At this moment, Zhao Hai laughed wildly.

* * *

The system of checks and balances in government was developed to ensure that no one branch of government would become too powerful

Chapter 959: Elaborate Sneak Attack

Zhao Hai laughed as he looked at Jie Yu, “I never understood why you didn’t attack the foreign race Supreme Elders despite being able to suppress them. If Elder Star can suppress them for a long time, then the three Supreme Elders wouldn’t have survived up to this time. As it turns out, attacking them would actually break the suppression. Hahahaha. Three Elders, come help me.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the three foreign race Supreme Elders couldn’t help but laugh as well. The Beastman Supreme Elder smiled and said, “Mister Zhao Hai is really extraordinary. You were still able to see through this despite being besieged at all sides. Great. You two, let’s go.” After he said that, he rushed towards Elder Star. Meanwhile the two other Supreme Elders flew towards Gold Ben, evidently planning to deal with him first.

After seeing the situation, Gold Ben couldn’t help but fluster. His figure moved as he went towards the group fighting the Hell King’s ship. Using their collective strength, they were hoping to destroy the ship, the scorpion, as well as the two Foreign Race Supreme Elders.

At this time, Elder Star also moved and decided to join the battle. Naturally, the Beastman Supreme Elder adjusted his course in order to clash with Elder Star.

When Zhao Hai saw this, his complexion slightly changed. He could understand what the three Supreme Elders wanted to do. It might seem like they weren’t doing anything wrong and that they just decided to focus the enemies in one point. However, Zhao Hai knew that there was something hidden underneath.

And this thing was the foreign Elders’ plan to use the nine Supreme Elders to cause damage to Zhao Hai. This way, when they win against the Divines, Zhao Hai wouldn’t become another threat.

But even if the three Supreme Elders had this plan in mind, Zhao Hai had already been alert from the very beginning. He wouldn’t place himself in danger, so instead of having the scorpion join the large battle, he had it regroup with himself. With the scorpion assisting him, the pressure on Zhao Hai became lighter.

When the pressure on his lightened up, Zhao Hai couldn’t’ help but laugh as he strengthened his power. And with the weapons in his hands always changing forms, Jie Yu’s group began to be pushed back.

When Elder Star’s group saw this situation, their expression couldn’t help but change. However, they had no cards left to play.

According to the situation, Elder Star and the others should have been on the defensive. After all, the Hell King’s ship could already block four. With the addition of the three Supreme Elders, the number advantage should have been flipped.

However, this wasn’t the case. Because of Elder Star’s participation, the strength of the Divine Supreme Elders have been strengthened. If not for the Hell King’s ship, the three foreign race Supreme Elders should have already been in a dangerous position.

Zhao Hai also noticed this situation, but he didn’t say anything. Instead, he strengthened his offensive and placed more pressure on Jie Yu’s group.

Jie Yu’s group began to be overwhelmed by Zhao Hai. This caused Jie Yu to become more and more angry. They desperately attacked, but their disadvantage couldn’t be compensated by just mere effort. They were in a complete disadvantage. Every ten attacks made by Zhao Hai, they could only make two.

When Jie Yu’s group began to be completely overwhelmed, Zhao Hai’s figure suddenly vanished. In the next moment, Zhao Hai reappeared behind the Pisces Supreme Elder. HIs staff transformed into a huge sledgehammer before hitting the Elder’s back.

Mingdasir was currently fighting against the giant scorpion. Although the scorpion’s attack wasn’t weak, it wasn’t a threat towards him. Moreover, he also knew that Zhao Hai was being entangled by Jie Yu, so he was safe for the moment. Because of this, he relaxed his body for a bit. But who would’ve thought that Zhao Hai would suddenly appear behind him.

Mingdasir suddenly felt an immense force strike his back. Although his muscles vibrated in order to mitigate the damage, he could still feel the damage done. The hammer cracked his bones. After that, Mingdasir felt his internal organs being assaulted. He never expected that Zhao Hai’s attack would reach this magnitude. Mingdasir’s internal organs were smashed. Then as he spurted out blood, the scorpion’s tail suddenly came and pierced his throat.

After hitting Mingdasir with his hammer, Zhao Hai immediately vanished. Then he reappeared near Jie Yu.

Zhao Hai’s move surprised everyone. They didn’t expect that while being in the middle of a fight, Zhao Hai still managed to sneak attack Mingdasir.

While everyone was stunned, Zhao Hai had already succeeded. Mingasir died in the hands of Zhao Hai. It was also at this time that the scorpion returned to Zhao Hai’s side.

Jie Yu roared in anger as he went all out against Zhao Hai. Jie Yu was using his own life force to attack. Zhao Hai could only parry, he didn’t have the chance to hit back for some time.

At this moment, the scorpion went to attack once again. Meanwhile, Mingdasir’s body disappeared into a spatial rift. The scorpion’s next target was the Leo Clan’s Supreme Elder.

Jie Yu kept desperately attacking Zhao Hai. Anyone would know that this wouldn’t be kept for long. However, not everyone noticed that Jie Yu was slowly pushing Zhao Hai towards the Hell King’s ship.

As Zhao Hai got closer and closer to the Hell King’s ship, Zhao Hai’s figure suddenly stopped mid-air. He didn’t retreat and instead turned his magic staff into a rapier as he sent a strike towards Jie Yu’s throat. But at the same time, Jie Yu also sent a punch towards Zhao Hai’s chest.

This exchange looked life-threatening. If Zhao Hai continued his rapier’s attack, then he would be hit in his chest. In this case, Zhao Hai should be taking his rapier back. However, he didn’t do it.

Zhao Hai’s rapier proceeded to strike, not caring even a bit about Jie Yu’s punch. Jie Yu’s eyes couldn’t help but show panic. His current actions were actually a gamble. He bet that with Zhao Hai at the winning side, then he wouldn’t go all out. Because of this, he pretended to be desperate. However, it seems like he bet wrongly.

The reason why Jie Yu was acting desperately was because he wanted Zhao Hai to be pushed towards Elder Star’s group. This way, everyone could group up to kill Zhao Hai.

The timing of Zhao Hai’s attack was very good. It was too late for Jie Yu to withdraw right now. Jie Yu could only watch as his throat was pierced by Zhao Hai.

When he saw this, Jie Yu couldn’t help but go truly all out. Although he couldn’t change the course of his fist, he still did his best to dodge Zhao Hai’s rapier. However, Jie Yu forgot that Zhao Hai’s weapons can transform. Just as Jie Yu dodged the rapier, the rapier suddenly turned into a shovel, transforming the strike into a slash.

Although Jie Yu can manage to dodge the strike, he couldn’t evade the slash. Jie Yu’s head met the shovel and was cut down. And since everything happened too fast, Jie Yu’s fist still managed to hit Zhao Hai’s shoulder. However, the force was just too small.

But even if the punch was weak, Zhao Hai was still pushed towards Elder Star and the others. Elder Star and the others already noted Jie Yu’s situation. After seeing Jie Yu push Zhao Hai towards them, they immediately knew what Jie Yu was planning. Because of this, Elder Star and the others were already prepared to deal with Zhao Hai.

However, who would’ve thought that Zhao Hai had already calculated Jie Yu’s plan. Although he noticed Jie Yu pushing him towards Elder Star, he still pretended to be unaware. In fact, he was just waiting for an opportunity.

Zhao Hai’s shovel hit Jie Yu in the head, and at the same time, Zhao Hai was also pushed towards Elder Star’s group. Upon seeing this, the eyes of the Divines turned red. Then Gold Ben and two other Supreme Elders immediately moved and attacked the back of Zhao Hai.

But at this moment, Zhao Hai’s figure suddenly vanished. This time, Zhao Hai reappered behind the Leo Supreme Elder who was currently fighting against the scorpion. Zhao Hai turned his staff into a rapier once more and attacked the Leo Supreme Elder’s head. With his previous momentum still preserved and the fact that Zhao Hai appeared close by, the rapier didn’t take too long before it punctured through the Leo Supreme Elder’s brain.

At the same time, the scorpion used this opportunity to sever the Leo Supreme Elder’s head using its pincers. Then Zhao Hai’s figure drew back along with the scorpion. After that, Zhao Hai waved his hand as the Leo Supreme Elder’s body and combat suit vanished in mid-air.

Zhao Hai also did the same to Jie Yu’s corpse. Meanwhile, the scorpion went forward in order to join the battle on Elder Star’s side. Elder Star and the others stared. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to kill three of them in a short time. This caused their eyes to turn even more red.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t give them an opportunity to stare. His figure moved as he joined the large fight. This caused Elder Star’s side to be completely pushed back. There simply wasn’t an opportunity for them to flip the situation over.

A sense of despair flashed through Elder Star’s eyes. Then he stopped in mid-air before turning his head to Zhao hai and spoke, “Mister Zhao Hai. Please stop, I have some words to say.”

Zhao Hai stopped along with the Hell King’s ship and the scorpion. Upon seeing the situation, the three foreign race Supreme Elders stopped as well along with the rest of the Divine Supreme Elders. All of them were looking at Elder Star, waiting for his words to be spoken.

Chapter 960: The Biggest Benefit Is Yours

Elder Star looked at Zhao Hai as he smiled bitterly and said, “Zhao Hai, I have to recognize that the biggest mistake the Divines has made was to become your enemy. You are indeed very strong.”

Zhao Hai stood on the Hell King’s ship, he smiled towards Elder Star and replied, “I’ll have to thank the Elder for the recognition. However, I still won’t let you off.”

Elder Star forced a smile and said, “I’m not counting on you letting us go. However, I hope that you can agree to a request. As long as you comply, all of us will kill ourselves in front of you. None of us will rebel.”

Zhao Hai looked into Elder Star and said, “Then please tell me your request.”

Elder Star replied, “In this situation, we already don’t plan on going out alive. However, if you don’t agree, we will go all out. I believe that 1 or two of us would be able to escape. Those who would escape wouldn’t seek revenge against you, instead, they will kill everyone in the Divine Realm, no matter civilian or experts. When that time comes, it would be a headache for you.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It truly will. Tell me your request.”

Elder Star took a deep breath and said, “I hope that you can assure us that the Divines would survive. Leave a few Divines alive, don’t kill them all.”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment. He didn’t expect this to be Elder Star’s request. He thought about it and said, “Alright, I agree. Although this Zhao Hai is ruthless towards his enemies, I can still keep my words. To be honest, there’s no point in lying to a few dead people.”

Elder Star nodded and said ,”Alright, I believe you. I hope you can keep your promise.” After that, Elder Star vomited blood before any signs of life vanished from his eyes.

When the other Divine Supreme Elders saw Elder Star’s action, they didn’t hesitate and did the same. Every one of them vomited blood before falling down from the sky.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and took the corpses of the Supreme Elders to the Hell King’s ship’s deck. Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “No matter what, you are heroes of your race.”

After that, Zhao Hai made the Hell King’s ship fly towards where Solomon and the others were. At this time, the foreign races’ Supreme Elders were aleadry beside their race’s Patriarchs.

Zhao Hai glanced at the group before turning his head to Solomon, “Patriarch Solomon, as you have seen, I will be taking the ultimate weapons with me. Three days later, I will give them all to you. When the time comes, I hope that you can give me the ultimate weapons of your races.”

Solomon knew that the elimination of the Divine Race’s Supreme Elders was all because of Zhao Hai, so he nodded and said, “Alright, we will certainly comply.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then the Hell King’s ship vanished in mid-air. A while after Zhao Hai vanished, the three foreign race Supreme Elders turned to Solomon and asked, “Solomon, what is this all about? Why would you hand the ultimate weapons of the three races over?”

Solomon proceeded to explain the pre-arranged condition. Naturally, he emphasized the fact that Zhao Hai would give them all 13 ultimate weapons in the end.

The three Supreme Elders gawked, but they didn’t oppose to Solomon’s acceptance of Zhao Hai’s condition. Accepting Zhao Hai’s request would give them 13 ultimate weapons. On the other hang, if they don’t accept, then they would develop a hatred towards Zhao Hai. If Zhao Hai decides to deal with them, then they would certainly find it hard to resist.

At this time, Zhao Hai sent the combat suits to the Space. Along with the prompts, Zhao Hai also acquired eight more combat suit seeds.

Then suddenly, the Star Disk made Zhao Hai stunned. This was because the Star Disk’s prompt was different compared to the combat suits.

The prompt for the Star Disk went like this, “Special group plate detected. This formation disk can be used alongside the Seven Star Heaven Lock Disk. Formation is incomplete. Upon completing the formation, the Host would find a pleasant surprise. Hoping for the host to complete the formation as soon as possible.”

Unexpectedly, the Star Disk didn’t produce a seed. Zhao Hai was stuck with what to do. When the time comes, if he couldn’t hand the Star Disk over, wouldn’t Solomon and the others become angry?

However, Zhao Hai changed his thoughts about this matter. Even if he didn’t hand the Star Disk to Solomon and the others, what can they do about it? Can they beat Zhao Hai with their current strength? At the thought of this, Zhao Hai relaxed. However, he didn’t immediately combine the Star Disk with the Seven Star Heaven Lock.

At the same time, Zhao Hai also commanded Cai’er to plant the eight combat suit seeds. These seeds would take less than three days to mature. However, Zhao Hai still allocated three days in the agreement in order to provide himself with some allowance.

On the other hand, the original combat suits had integrated themselves into the Blood Ghost Staff. Now, the staff has eight additional constellations. At the same time, eight huge beasts were added to Zhao Hai’s staff. These beasts were quite special. All of them had the appearance of a scorpion but with little differences here and there. Their abilities weren’t the same as well. What made Zhao Hai puzzled was the fact that all of them turned into scorpions. Shouldn’t they transform into the form of their constellations?

After asking the Space, Zhao Hai understood that the 12 beasts could change form at will. But since the most powerful form for them at this time was a scorpion, all of them adapted to this image. If Zhao Hai wanted, they could transform into any constellation he wants to.

Zhao Hai immediately had them change their form. Before long, they all became their own figures. Zhao Hai asked the Space about why the scorpion had the most powerful form. The response made Zhao Hai unsure whether he should laugh or cry.

It went like this, when Zhao Hai took in the Capricorn combat suit, the Space could’ve turned it’s form into a goat. But since a goat was a herbivorous creature and wasn’t suitable for slaughter, the Space went according the laws of the 12 combat suits and turned the Capricorn combat suit into a scorpion. This was because scorpions not only have two pincers, they also have an attacking tail. At the same time, they could also use their mouths and even their feet to attack the enemy. Lastly, of all the animals, the scorpion’s carapace provided it with a good defense. Because of this, the Space went for the battle-ready scorpion form.

Naturally, scorpions weren’t this flexible. It would be impossible for their tails to be like whips. However, the Space still deemed its form appropriate. So the Space turned all of the combat suits into scorpions. Zhao Hai hadn’t thought about this before, so he only reacted upon seeing them now.

However, this was still good news for Zhao Hai. With all these combat suits, Zhao Hai would have more means to attack. And with the combat suits’ diverse forms, they would have more methods of attack. With all of these in hand, of course Zhao Hai would be glad.

Three days passed by in a blink of an eye. Three days later, Zhao Hai appeared in the skies of the Libra Continent. Solomon and the others were already waiting there for him. Zhao Hai waved his hand as nine ultimate weapons appeared in front of Solomon and the others. Naturally, these combat suits were made from the seeds in the Space. The original combat suits had integrated themselves to Zhao Hai’s staff.

However, this didn’t mean that the seed combat suits were much worse compared to the original. These suits might not be stronger than the original, but they were now free from the Star Disk’s control. Also, the problems of energy consumption and other shortcomings of the original combat suits had been fixed.

Of course, only the original combat suits could combine with the Blood Ghost Staff and transform into different forms at will. However, the foreign races didn’t need to know about this.

Zhao Hai handed the nine combat suits to Solomon before he said, “Patriarch Solomon, I’m afraid I would have to be unfair to you.”

The complexion on the faces of Solomon and the others changed. Every one of them began to feel anxious, they think that Zhao Hai wanted to snatch the combat suits of their Supreme Elders. Upon seeing their expression, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile faintly and said, “Patriarch Solomon, there’s no need to be anxious. I’m not here to steal the ultimate weapons. But I do have something to tell you. I finished researching these ultimate weapons. However, a mishap occurred when I began to study the Star Disk. I didn’t expect the Star Disk to combine with my Hell King’s ship. You should know that I snatched my ship from the Divine Race’s Deity. My understanding of the ship is extremely limited. I didn’t think that the Star Disk would fuse with the ship. So now, I cannot take the Star Disk out. I hope that the Patriarchs could forgive me.”

After hearing this, Solomon and the others relaxed. To be honest, even if Zhao Hai didn’t give them the Star Disk and a couple of ultimate weapons, they could still accept it. After all, they were profiting big in this exchange.

Solomon looked at the others and saw their expressions loosen. Solomon became relieved as he turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, there’s no need to apologize. Since this is the case, then Mister can have the Star Disks. Elders, please give Mister your ultimate weapons.”

The three Supreme Elders didn’t say anything as they took their combat suits off and handed them over to Zhao Hai. At the same time, Zhao Hai also gave the nine combat suits to the Supreme Elders. Zhao Hai didn’t take the three combat suits immediately, instead he looked at the three elders and said, “Elders, I made some modifications on the nine combat suits. I hope that you can try them on and tell me what you think. If you like it, then I will be taking these three ultimate weapons. If you don’t then I will just leave them behind.”

When the three Elders heard Zhao Hai, their expressions changed. But after a moment, they chose a combat suit and proceeded to wear it.

They had used combat suits for a long time. Although they had traded their combat suits, they didn’t feel anything strange. Combat suits don’t recognize masters. Because of this, the elders just equipped the ultimate weapons.

Upon wearing the combat suits, the Elders immediately felt the differences. In the past, whenever they wear their ultimate weapons, even if it increases their strength, they could still feel a constricting feeling. This made it impossible for them to use the combat suits for a long period of time.

But now, these combat suits didn’t have this feeling. Instead, they were very comfortable. Moreover, the power that they can exert right now was not much less compared to before.

The three elders felt that this might be an illusion. So they tried other combat suits and even compared notes. In the end, the result was the same, this made the Elders feel relieved.

Also, as the three looked at the combat suits, they discovered that they were shiny as though they were new. There wasn’t even a small dent seen, it was surprising.

One must know that ultimate weapons were around for who knows how many years. The ultimate weapons would surely be damaged along the way. However, these combat suits were flawless, it seems like Zhao Hai fixed them.

The three elders looked at each other and saw the surprise on each other’s eyes. Then the three bowed slightly to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, there’s no need to worry about it. They’re very comfortable to wear and it seems like Mister even repaired them. We need to thank Mister for this.”

Solomon and the others were looking anxiously at the three Elders. After hearing the elders, they couldn’t help but feel relieved. Then they looked at Zhao Hai differently while also feeling some guilt.

Zhao Hai smiled and replied, “It’s good that the Elders liked them. To be honest, my research on these combat suits didn’t take too much time. However, it took a lot of effort to repair them. Fortunately, nothing went wrong in the repair. This shall be my gift to the foreign races. Everyone, I’ll be taking these three suits. After three days, I will come back here and return them to you. You can rest assured.”

After he said that, Zhao Hai brought his Hell King’s ship and vanished from the Libra Continent. When Zhao Hai reappeared on the Taurus Continent, Laura and the others came out. Plastered on their faces were huge smiles.

Upon looking at their expressions, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get puzzled as he asked, “What happened? Why are you all smiling?”

Laura smiled and said, “Brother Hai, your methods are too great. Although biggest benefit is yours, it was still them who had to give thanks. You haven’t noticed, but even Solomon and the others were looking gratefully towards you.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Actually, this isn’t considered as me taking advantage of them. Although they can use the original ultimate weapons, it would still be a waste. Those ultimate weapons are much more useful in my posession. In their hands, the ultimate weapons would just be like sledgehammers being wielded by three-year olds. At that age, the most they could use are wooden swords. The combat suits produced by the Space is more suited for them. Not only was the burden removed, their effective strength was also further improved.”

Laura smiled and said, “In any case, you gained advantages this time. Brother Hai, didn’t the Space say that a reward would be given when the collection is complete? Quick, let’s see what that reward is.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, I’m quite curious as well. This isn’t the first time that the Space produced mysterious things. But every time we gained a lot. This time, I wonder what benefits we could get.” Then after saying that, Zhao Hai sent the combat suits to the Space.

Chapter 961: Huge Level Ups!

As soon as the three remaining combat suits were sent to the Space, a prompt was immediately heard, “12 Constellations combat suits Libra, Aries, and Virgo detected. The 12 Constellations Combat Suits are now complete.”

Zhao Hai also took out the Star disk and threw it into the Space. Another prompt came, “Special use map formation discovered. Formation disk is known as Star Disk. Formation can be used along with weapons and other materials in order to make it more powerful. Host can combine the Star Disk to the Seven Star Heaven Lock and the Hell King’s ship. This will allow the Hell King’s ship to use the strength of the stars as well as break every formation that is related to constellations. Host can now also unite the Dao Lotus with the Hell King’s ship, further strengthening the ship. This will allow the ship to use the strength of the myriad worlds and break all kinds of formations. Finally, the Host can combine the Hell King’s ship with the Blood Ghost Staff. The Hell King’s ship wouldn’t only exist as a plate, its form can also be changed at will.”

Upon hearing this announcement, Zhao Hai felt great happiness. He didn’t expect that things would be this good. However, this great event was still far from ending. The Space continued to speak, “Since the Star Disk contains the power of the stars, the Space has gained stars. Everywhere in the Space now has stars in the sky, complementing the Space. Space levels up to 100 and has met the requirements for becoming a low-grade Cultivation Space. Host can now purchase 50 ordinary backgrounds and 10 low-grade cultivation backgrounds. Universal Scanner and Universal Processing machine has reached intermediate standard, allowing for the analysis and manufacturing of low level Cultivation items. Host can now assign a region to be an accelerated place. Presently, Host can accelerate a region’s time by ten times. Note: It can also make plants mature quickly, but they would have more years to their record. The special region is good for growing natural treasures. Host may also use the region to cultivate. Ten years of cultivation inside the region would be the same as one year of cultivation outside.”

Zhao Hai laughed out loud. He didn’t think that the Space would become this powerful. It rose to level 100 and became a low-grade Cultivation Space. For Zhao hai, this was an absolutely good thing. This was especially true for the time acceleration function. It had great uses for him.

At this moment, there were plenty of things inside the Space that can develop to become heavenly treasures. Unfortunately, these things needed a lot of years in order to grow. Now that the ability to dilate time had come, the time needed to cultivate these things had reduced by a lot.

However, that still wasn’t the end. After the previous prompt ended, another one came, “Since the Star Disk is an item with Stellar energy, special high level cultivation method has been provided. Myriad Stellar Transformations Secret Art acquired. Cultivation method is divided into three aspects, attack, defense, and auxiliary methods. Once Host combines the Dao Lotus with the Star Disk, the Myriad Stellar Transformations Art will evolve into Myriad Stellar Transformations Yin-Yang Art. Asking Host for permission in order to fuse the Dao Lotus and the Star Disk.”

Zhao Hai laughed even louder, he was too happy. This special reward came unexpected. For Zhao Hai, being able to acquire a Cultivation Method was too important.

Zhao Hai quickly agreed, “Combine, combine everything! Cai’er, go and see if the scanner and the processing machine requires money to upgrade. If not, then immediately buy as many backgrounds as you can.”

Cai’er immediately complied. Then at this time, Zhao Hai’s staff vanished. Zhao Hai could also feel the a force from the Dao Lotus inside his body, it now has the energy from the Space. A great amount of energy was integrated into the Dao Lotus. Upon internal examination, Zhao Hai found that the Dao Lotus had become different compared to before. In the past, the Dao Lotus only had the eight trigrams, looking very mysterious. Now, the eight trigrams below the Dao Lotus became a Yin-Yang pond, rotating non-stop. Along with the pond’s rotation, the power of the heaven and earth seem to be sucked into Zhao Hai’s body. In the skies above the Dao Lotus was a black void littered with stars. Starlight would occasionally fall from the void and into the Dao Lotus. When this happened, the Dao Lotus’ petals seem to sway gently.

Zhao Hai felt that his spirit form became more tangible as it began show signs of breathing. At the same time, Zhao Hai felt his mental power being strengthened.

The Gold Core in his dantian had become bigger as well. It emitted golden light, baptizing Zhao Hai’s body. At this time, there was no part in Zhao Hai’s body that felt uncomfortable.

Zhao Hai closed his eyes, enjoying the baptism. Then at this time, another prompt came in, “Spiritual Artifacts detected in the Space. Level of Spiritual Artifacts is too low, promoting their level. Spirit of the book, spear, sword, hammer, staff, bow, and whip has been promoted. Because of the existence of the Artifact Spirit, item can now command themselves to battle. But they would still listen to the Host’s commands.”[1]

Zhao Hai was shocked once again. He didn’t think that there would be more surprises. At this time, the Hell King’s ship vanished and flew into the Space. Meanwhile, the Staff came back.

Zhao Hai held his staff and took a look at it. On the staff were the symbols of the twelve constellations. The head of the staff wasn’t the original skull, instead, it has turned into a lotus. This lotus had seven pistils and at the tip of each pistil was a small star. These pistils were swaying gently. Upon further inspection, one could see that the pistils were arranged into the shape of the Big Dipper and not in a circular manner.

Stellar shimmers can also be seen from the Staff, making it look very beautiful. Zhao Hai happily looked at his staff before waving it around, making the Hell King’s ship appear. The ship had become beautiful as well. There was still the image of Hell on its hull, but both sides had disks totalling to 12. Each disk had its own constellation as all of them spun around.

Below the ship, instead of seawater, a giant lotus can be seen. From what can be seen, it seems like the ship was nestled on top of a lotus. There were also occasional sprays of bluish water containing starlight. The entire ship looked like a masterpiece made in heaven.

When Laura and the others saw the Hell King’s ship, their eyes couldn’t help but shine. They didn’t expect the ship to become even more beautiful.

Zhao Hai waved his staff again, and this time the disks on the side of the ship flew out. After a flash, the twelve constellations assumed their form. They went according to their own zodiac but they can change their form at will.

Zhao Hai nodded before boarding this ship along with Laura and the others. The combat suits returned to being disks and went back to the side of the ship. There weren’t any huge changes on the ship. But now, the wind chimes of the ship had been replaced by lotuses.

Zhao Hai stood on the deck of the ship and made a command using his mind. After that Laura and the others discovered that the ship reverted to its appearance before the upgrade. This caused some of them to be confused.

After that, Zhao Hai made another command and turned the ship into a huge lotus. The ship was now gone. When he saw this, Zhao Hai nodded. The Hell King’s ship now had the staff’s ability to assume any form.

When Laura and the others saw this, they quickly understood what Zhao Hai wanted to do. Then they proceeded to inspect the lotus. The lotus still had eighteen layers. At this time, the group was standing on the uppermost layer. Splashing below the lotus was the bluish water. And on each of the lotus’ layer, a mural of Hell can be seen on the lotus petals. Also on, each tip of the lotus petals were small wind chimes.

Zhao Hai gave a satisfied nod before turning to the women and said, “In the future, we’ll be using this form of the Hell King’s ship, what do you think?”

Laura nodded as she smiled and said, “Alright, that is a great idea. It’s more attractive this way.” Lizzy and the others nodded as well. They were now looking all around to inspect their new vehicle.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Let’s go head inside. I want to see what this Myriad Stellar Transformations Yin-Yang art is.”

Laura and the others nodded before entering a room along with Zhao Hai. The insides of the room didn’t have any changes besides being much larger compared to before. After seeing what is inside, Zhao Hai and the others proceeded to enter the villa. After that, Zhao Hai called out, “Cai’er, let me have a look at the Cultivation Method.”

Cai’er nodded. Then after that, a book appeared before Zhao Hai. This book floated in the air before a small spirit came out of the cover. The figure bowed towards Zhao Hai and said, “I have seen Young Master Zhao Hai.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he immediately recovered, he looked at the small figure with curiosity as he asked, “Are you that improved book? Hmm, you are the artifact bestowed by the Divines to the Radiant Church. Now that you have levelled up, you need a new name. How about this, from now on you will be known as Compendium of Treasured Scriptures.”

The spirit bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “I thank the Young Master for bestowing me a name.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Do you have the cultivation record? Let me have a look.”

The Compendium nodded before the book opened up. After that, huge writings appeared in front of Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai carefully looked through these writings. The letters were well written and organized. The characters weren’t overly small, they were sized enough to be comfortable.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but nod. Then he proceeded to read the cultivation method, the Myriad Stellar Transformations Yin-Yang Secret Art.

As he read on, Zhao Hai kept trying to figure out the root of the method. After reading through the first part, Zhao Hai discovered an issue. According to the method, given Zhao Hai’s present strength, he could only practice the first part. Just the first part of this cultivation method was this formidable, it caused Zhao Hai to be startled.

* * *

Three of them are from the three races(spear, hammer, bow), the other three from the Radiant Church(book, staff, sword), and then the last one Zhao Hai got from the Beastman Prairie(whip).

Chapter 962: No Repulsion?

Zhao Hai wanted to turn the page, but he discovered that the pages seem to be stuck. He immediately turned to look at the spirit and said, “….Compendium, why wouldn’t it turn?”

The Compendium immediately answered, “Replying to the Young Master. This cultivation method is very special. With the Young Master’s current strength, you can only read the first part. If the Young Master wants to forcefully read the second part, then it’s possible that you would suffer a backlash on your body. This one suggests to refrain from reading the second part for now.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he nodded and said, “Alright. I’ll be fine with reading the first part.”

After he said that, Zhao Hai went his room to look into the mysteries of the cultivation method. The more he pondered, the more he felt the endless uses of the method. At the same time, he also realized how complex it was.

After some time, Zhao Hai began to practice. The contents of the first part were already understood by him. However, it was still very difficult to practice, the method was too complicated. The method was more complex than the other cultivation methods, and this was only the first part. Who knows how difficult the whole method would be.

Originally, Zhao Hai felt that he was already very strong. But when he started cultivating using the method, he understood that his strength still fell short.

The energy inside Zhao Hai’s body was originally azure-colored. But after using the cultivation method, Zhao Hai found that his energy had become bright silver. Moreover, his energy began to shine, just like starlight.

Not only did Zhao Hai’s energy transform, it became compressed as well. If Zhao Hai’s previous energy was an azure colored mist, it now had become a silvery liquid. This caused his energy to be ten times compared to before.

As Zhao Hai’s energy transformed, Zhao Hai discovered that the Plane’s repulsion had weakened. This caused Zhao Hai to be puzzled. He can confirm that he became ten times stronger, so why did the repulsion reduce?

As Zhao Hai was thinking about this, the blood in his body began to boil. This startled Zhao Hai. Then he immediately went to look into the state of his body. His energy has been fully transformed.

He didn’t know how long, but his transformation was completed. Moreover, the Myriad Stellar Transformation Yin-Yang Method’s first part had established a good route through Zhao Hai’s body. Zhao Hai let out a long breath before opening his eyes.

Upon opening his eyes, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gawk. This was because the room had gone dark. Zhao Hai turned his head to look out the window, but he discovered that it was closed.

It was at this time that a surprised voice was heard, “Brother Hai, you’re awake.” Zhao Hai turned his head to see Berry.

Zhao Hai stared, he looked confused at Berry as he said, “Berry, when did you come back? What about your people?”

Berry smiled and said, “Brother Hai, I’ve been back for two days now. I’ve already arranged things for my clan, there’s no need for me to return this time.”

When he heard Berry, Zhao Hai picked up some information, “You’ve been back for two days? Why didn’t I know about this? Also, how is the outside doing?”

Berry chuckled before she hugged Zhao Hai, “Of course you wouldn’t know, you’ve been cultivating for three days. I don’t think there’s anything significant happening outside. It’s currently night, but the stars are very beautiful.” Zhao Hai nodded, he knew that this might be because of the Space’s recent upgrade. He didn’t think too much into it as he turned to Berry and said, “What’s wrong? Were you worried about me?”

Berry nodded, “We’re quite worried. But we also knew that you wouldn’t have any problems. Sister Laura and the others already went to take a rest. Yesterday, Megan was the one who guarded you. Today’s my turn.” Zhao Hai nodded, “I’m fine, there’s nothing’s wrong. How is the Space?”

Berry smiled and said, “It’s doing well. Cai’er already divided the accelerated region among the various backgrounds. The Processing Machine and the Scanner have also been upgraded. 50 ordinary backgrounds have been bought, but the low-grade Cultivation Backgrounds haven’t. We’re waiting for you to make a decision.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to look outside and said, “Let’s go, join me outside.”

Berry nodded before going with Zhao Hai outside. After exiting, Zhao Hai breathed in. He discovered that after the Space’s upgrade, the environment had become much better compared to before.

Then he looked at the sky and saw a falling star, it looked incomparably beautiful. Zhao Hai turned to Berry and smiled, “I didn’t think that my energy would be reduced by a lot after using the new cultivation method. However, the quality has greatly increased. Because of this, the plane isn’t repelling me. It seems like I can stay here for a while longer.”

Berry became glad after hearing this, she quickly replied, “Really? That’s fantastic. Then we need to collect more things to upgrade the Space.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “Yes, we’ll collect more things for the Space. Right, how is the O’Neal family doing nowadays?”

Berry smiled and said, “They’re doing quite well. Although their base haven’t been completed, their relocation is pretty much done. Sister Lizzy and Sister Megan began directing them to the Winged Pegasus Clan over the two days you were gone. Brother Hai, you’re very tolerant towards the Winged Pegasus. It’s about time to teach them a lesson.”

Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “Now isn’t the time. If we made a move towards the Winged Pegasus Clan this early, then the Thunder Clan and the Barbarians might feel dissatisfied. Let’s use the O’Neal family to teach them a lesson.”

Berry pouted as she said, “They’re not thinking well. If they were Demons, then the Great Demon King would’ve already sent an order to destroy them.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly. Zhao Hai didn’t know what to say to the Succubus. To the Demons, the weak should surrender to the strong, it was a natural process. If you don’t surrender, then you can just wait before you get destroyed. This was the rule of the Demon realm, but this rule wasn’t suitable to every other place.

After seeing Zhao Hai staying silent, Berry said, “Brother Hai, at this point, more and more soldiers from the Devil Legion are  equipping themselves with combat suits. Their fighting strength has been promoted by a lot. Before I came back here, I went to see his Majesty the Great Demon King. The Great Demon King told me that if you don’t let the Devil Legion fight, then they might as well go to the Hell Space to exercise.”

Zhao Hai thought about this and said, “Going to the Hell Space wouldn’t have any use to them anymore. Go tell the Great Demon King tomorrow that I’ll have them participate in a fight. In any case, we will clash with the O’Neal family soon. Let’s have the Devil Legion come out and use them as exercise.”

Berry nodded, “We have already prepared the combat suits for the foreign races. We can return them tomorrow. After that, what do we do?”

Zhao Hai replied, “We’ll take the Leo Divines into the Space. Then we’ll have the O’Neal family deal with the Winged Pegasus Clan. Once we get the Winged Pegasus to the Space, we’ll direct the O’Neal family to the foreign races. I want to see which is stronger, the O’Neal family’s magic armors, or the foreign races’ combat suits. And if the foreign races are stronger, I want to see how the O’Neal family plans to deal with them. Meanwhile, we’ll use that time to sneak into the Atlanta Plane.”

Berry’s eyes shone when she heard this. Then she said, “That’s great. I’ve been curious about the Atlanta Plane. I want to see how they go about their life.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and didn’t say anything. Him going to the Atlanta Plane was mainly because of the Ascension Magic Armor, so that he could ascend.

The two spent a little while outside the villa before they went inside to rest. The next morning, when Laura and the others woke up and saw Zhao Hai, they became glad.

Zhao Hai looked at the group and smiled, “Alright, let’s eat. After the meal, you’ll go to the Space and study the Myriad Stellar Transformation Yin-Yang Art. This cultivation method is very good.”

The women nodded. Then after eating the food that Meg made, the group entered the Space to study the cultivation method. However, Zhao Hai believed that they would take a much longer time compared to him.

After Laura and the others entered the Space, Zhao Hai turned the Hell King’s ship’s appearance from the lotus to the one it had before. Then he proceeded to head towards the Libra Continent.

When Solomon and the others saw Zhao Hai, they immediately went forward to greet him. After inviting them into the ship, Zhao Hai turned to look at the group and said, “Everybody, I’ve fixed the ultimate weapons, you can now take them back.”

After Solomon and the others expressed their gratitude, Solomon said, “Does Mister have somewhere to go next? If not, then can we invite you to stay with us? We will definitely treat Mister well.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You’re too polite. However, I have something else to do. I won’t be able to stay here for long. However, I have something I need your help with.”

Solomon quickly replied, “Mister, please tell us. As long as it’s possible, we will certainly do it.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Before Elder Star and the others took their own lives, I accepted their condition. Because of this, I’d want to personally deal with the Leo Divines. What do you all think?”

Solomon hesitated for a moment and said, “Will Mister deal with all of them? If Mister wants us to let them go, then it’ll be troblesome. We cannot just let go of our years of resentment.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Rest assured, from now on, the Divine Race would disappear from the Divine Realm. This place belongs to you now.”

When Solomon heard Zhao Hai, he couldnt’ help but stare, then he said, “Mister, didn’t you make a promise to Elder Star and the others? If you don’t want to violate the oath, then you can just let us handle it.”

Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “I will go there myself. I will let them survive, but not too many. I’ll give them a spark of survival, but they won’t be in the Divine Realm anymore.”

Chapter 963: The Situation of the People In the Space

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Solomon thought about Zhao Hai’s ship that can hold a lot of people. Solomon seemed to have reached an understanding as he nodded and said, “Alright, then we’ll be depending on Mister. You can go to the Leo Continent at any time.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly before bowing to everyone and said, “Thank you very much. I will begin immediately. I’ll have to ask Patriarch Solomon to send word to your troops.”

Solomon was also aware of Zhao Hai’s mysterious ability to appear and disappear, so he just nodded. After Solomon and the others got down from Zhao Hai’s ship, Zhao Hai proceeded to vanish from the Libra Continent and reappear in the Leo Continent.

Upon appearing in the Leo Continent, Zhao Hai immediately attacked the Leo Divines. The situation with the Leo Divines wasn’t doing very well. While fighting against the foreign races, the losses they had suffered wasn’t small. Although they managed to hold the foreign races back, the price they paid was very huge.

They could only hope that their Supreme Elder would come back. However, their Supreme Elder didn’t return. Instead, Zhao Hai came, this caused huge damage to their morale.

Zhao Hai didn’t hold back against the Leo Divines. Because of this, everyone who attacked were killed off, those who behaved were sent to the Space.

Zhao Hai had done such things multiple times. The undead were also used to this. Since the undead had some sort of intelligence, they no longer needed Zhao Hai’s command during the battle.

The foreign race army had already received their Patriarch’s order, so they didn’t participate in the attack. However, they were still able to see how easily Zhao Hai managed to deal with the Leo Divines. When they saw this, their backs couldn’t help but turn cold. This was the first time they saw this kind of attack. Zhao Hai’s undead had shocked them greatly.

The one that surprised them the most was the incomprehensible number of undead that Zhao Hai had. When Zhao Hai appeared, it seems like the entire sky of the Leo Continent was covered in undead, it was an extremely terrifying sight.

The more curious foreign race members were able to witness the fate of a small town with a hundred thousand people. Zhao Hai’s undead army only took half an hour to get rid of the town. The town was left with no living entity, people or magic beasts. All of them vanished from sight.

Every time Zhao Hai emptied a city, the foreign race army would go and occupy it. However, the foreign races discovered that their speed was still not enough to catch up with Zhao Hai.

Another thing that surprised them was the fact that the undead seem to have unlimited energy. Even after attacking for an entire day, the undead still kept going on.

A day passed, the foreign races could no longer see Zhao Hai. Two days, the foreign races had seized half of the Leo Continent, yet Zhao Hai still wasn’t in sight. It seems like Zhao Hai had ended the war.

On the third day, the foreign race army had occupied the entirety of the Leo Continent. However, they still couldn’t see Zhao Hai, it looks like Zhao Hai had already left.

The foreign race soldiers were surprised. They immediately reported Zhao Hai’s disappearance to Solomon and the others. When Solomon’s group heard this, they became shocked. Now they were curious about Zhao Hai’s true strength. A single person was able to deal with a Divine Race continent in just three days. Even thinking about this made their backs turn cold.

So where was Zhao Hai? Zhao Hai was currently inside the Space. He was no longer being repelled by the Plane at this moment. Moreover, Zhao Hai discovered that the quantity of his energy has become a tenth of what it was before. However, this didn’t make his attacks weaker. This was because the energy inside his body was also ten times more potent compared to the past. In other words, Zhao Hai’s energy stayed the same despite being reduced. It would take some time before the Plane’s suppression would return.

The Stellar Transformations Art was truly formidable to be able to achieve this. Zhao Hai can clearly see that the art was much better compared to the one he practiced before.

Progreesion on any cultivation method involves the amount of energy inside one’s body. It was just like filling a barrel with water. Half of a barrel was still not enough to fully utilize one’s strength.

If the cultivation method that Zhao Hai used before was like putting water inside a barrel, then the cultivation method he used now was like filling a barrel with mercury. This made the barrel much heavier than before.

Because of this, with his barrel still not full, Zhao Hai was able to enter the Space. Zhao Hai was currently heading towards the villa, there he saw Laura and the others cultivating.

Just like Zhao Hai thought, the cultivation of the others were slower than his own. Since their bodies weren’t as good as Zhao Hai, it would take them longer than three days to refine their energy.

Although their speed was slow, Zhao Hai didn’t think of it as an issue. In the meantime, Zhao Hai observed the O’Neal family’s base in the Taurus Continent.

The O’Neal family had yet to fully construct their base. After all, their base was enormous. While to construction was happening, their scouts were beginning to look through the surrounding areas. However, they still haven’t found the spatial rifts of the three clans. Because of this, Zhao Hai wasn’t too worried about making a move.

After that, Zhao Hai shifted his attention to the Divine Space. In the beginning, the Divines had ravaged their surroundings. But now, they had started to behave. When they entered the Space, the Divines slowly began to understand that the Divine Race was over. The Divines would now live in this place from now on.

It was only after realizing this point that the Divines began to see how good the environment was. Compared to the Divine Realm, they wouldn’t need to worry about food in this place. Moreover, there were churches in various places that allowed them to exchange goods. Life was very convenient.

Additionally, there were no slaves in this place, nor were there people who collected taxes. In this war, the Nobles of the Divines Race had lost their dominance among the other Divines. Because of this, the Divines were truly free.

Also, the Divines had discovered that one couldn’t do crimes in this place. You cannot steal nor hurt another person, or else you would be punished.

The Divines had seen it with their own eyes. There was one Divine who bullied a family with only an old man, a woman, and a child. The next day, that man vanished. Then after a month, the man appeared once more. But this time, the man wasn’t looking so good. He became thin and pale. When the people asked him where he was, the man was immediately frightened, then he said that he didn’t want to recall where he came from.

Then later on, a person who stole someone’s belongings vanished for seven days. When he reappeared, his expression was the same as the previous person. When he was asked, he said that he was locked in a completely dark room. Nobody talked to him nor was there any other noise. Although food was provided to him, he stayed in place for seven whole days. The person said that being locked in that place for seven days was the most terrifying thing he encountered in his past seven years. He wasn’t willing to return to that place.

There were a lot of similar events like this inside the Space. Once a person commits a crime, they would be sent to the dark room. Some of the more serious offenders, like murderers, were killed on the spot. But besides them, everyone got punished. They didn’t know who took them, they just felt that they were transferred to the room after they did their crime. Then after being sent to the room, a voice would tell them about their crime and their punishment. After that, silence was the only thing that remained. The dark room wasn’t big but it wasn’t small either, it was about five by five meters big.

By word of mouth, the matter regarding the dark room spread throughout the Divine Space. This caused the Divines to be terrified, some people even said that they’d rather die than be sent to that room again.

However, this thing would never be accomplished. Once you enter the dark room, you completely lose your freedom. If you decided to kill yourself, then a strange force would take control of your body, making you lose all your strength. Because of this, committing suicide was impossible.

After several people were sent to the Dark Room, the Divine Space began to calm down. It almost turned into a high moral society where law and order prevailed.

What the Divines did now was to work every day and gain things to be exchanged for items that they need like daily necessities, books, and other items aside from weapons.

The Divines who entered the Space first began to get used to their current life. Some even thought that they were living a better lifestyle.

However, this didn’t mean that they had forgotten about their hatred towards Zhao Hai. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t appear inside the Divine Space. He just paid attention to them and see how they were living their life.

After seeing that the Divines were doing well, Zhao Hai turned to look at the other Spaces. They were doing very well, especially those in the Ark Space. Some novels began to be made and even some short movies which Zhao Hai was eager to see.

When the people from the Ark Continent saw Zhao Hai’s projections, they became curious about its origin. Those who liked to research immediately started this endeavor. In the end, they were finally able to see the advantages of magic formations. It was able to record light and project them to another place. Those who were keen of mind began to make stories and then show the recorded images to other people. This caused the emergence of short movies. Its initial  development was just like the movies back in the earth, they were first made without sound and colors.

But even if this was the case, it made life in the Ark Space even more colorful. Before long, magic formation research became to hot topic among the populace.

This was what Zhao Hai wanted to see the most. The researchers in Wild Dragon Island can only do so much. Now, with the entire continent helping in the research, the development of technology would surely be astonishing.

Compared to the Ark Space, the Demon Space went another direction. The Demons didn’t research magic formations, instead, they began to look into different kinds of plants.

This might have stemmed from the lack of fauna back in the Demon Realm. Due to its scarcity, the Demons began to be keen in looking into plants. Zhao Hai hasn’t seen the Demon Space for quite some time. And now, its state had given him a surprise. He didn’t expect the Demon Space to become a plant kingdom. Every Demon family had plants of different kinds planted all around their dwelling.

Zhao Hai can see that they didn’t cultivate those plants for consumption, it was just because the Demons liked them. With such plants proliferating in their surrounding area, the Demons managed to develop a new occupation, Potions Master!

There was no such occupation in the Demon Realm before because almost all of the plants there was poisonous and highly toxic. Nobody in their right mind would carelessly touch any kind of plant.

However, everything was different inside the Space. Plants were aplenty here, moreover, most of them weren’t harmful. Because of this, the Demons started to study plants and some even decided to taste everything they came across.

Zhao Hai was similarly glad to see this situation. They can research as much as they want. And because of this, Zhao Hai decided to establish a reward system. No matter which area of research, magic formations, plants, or any useful thing, as long as they discover something new, they will be rewarded. Naturally, the rewards differed between each contribution.

Zhao Hai’s decision roused the enthusiasm of the groups inside the Space. This was especially true for the Goblins. Their race was born to study magic formations. Ever since they learned how to read as well as recognize basic magic formations, almost all Goblins dabbled in the study of magic formations.

After looking at their frantic expressions, Zhao Hai became happy, he also gave more abundant rewards for the Goblins. The Goblins didn’t really care about food, drinks, nor the place they lived in. They just loved to look at magic formations, so they sunk their heads into their research.

Compared to the other groups, the Thunder Clan, Barbarians, and the Winged Pegasus were not doing as well. This was because they had just entered the Space and had not yet fully settled themselves. This was especially true for the Winged Pegasus. Since they were not willing to enter the Space, their situation was becoming more chaotic.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about their situation nor did he head there to help. He didn’t want to be seen as the type who wanted to interfere with other people’s matters. After all, the situation of the three clans was quite special.

Three days after Zhao Hai dealt with the Leo Clan, Laura and the others completed their study on the new cultivation method. Naturally, their route, energy, and physical ability still fell short compared to Zhao Hai.

Chapter 964: Atlanta Plane

After Laura finished cultivating the Myriad Stellar Transformations art, she proceeded to hand the method over to Karen. However, Karen didn’t like studying the method, he said that it’s very annoying.

Zhao Hai didn’t force Karen to study. To be honest, Zhao Hai discovered that the Stellar Art was suited for attacks. Karen didn’t like fighting and just liked to do research.

After that, Laura just handed the method over to Green. She didn’t give Grandpa Green any pointers, he could understand it on his own.

Upon seeing that Laura and the others were done practicing, Zhao Hai immediately called them over to the living room. After asking them about their experiences, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, it’s great that you’re done practicing. In the past few days, I’ve been busy observing the various groups inside the Space. Now that the time is right, we should prepare our next plan.”

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, are you preparing to deal with the Winged Pegasus Clan? I think we should start to make a move, if we don’t teach those guys a lesson, then they will continue to be a pain in the head.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I’m also losing my patience towards the Winged Pegasus. However, I made a promise to Shan. Otherwise, I wouldn’t have let them go free all this time. Let’s just start sending undead to the O’Neal family’s scouts and slowly lead them towards the Winged Pegasus Plane.”

Lizzy looked at the screen and said, “Brother Hai, did you make a move? How did the O’neal family react?”

Zhao Hai slightly frowned, “If I could describe their reaction, then i can only say that it’s strange. They seem to be very sensitive. As long as they see an undead, they will immediately pursue them.”

When Lizzy heard this, she frowned and said, “It’s not the style of the O’Neal family to throw caution out the window. What happened?” Zhao Hai also frowned, “Right, the O’neal family isn’t acting normal. However, this doesn’t have anything to do with us at this time. Let’s just lead them to the Winged Pegasus, let’s see what they do then.”

The group nodded, then ZhaoHai turned his head to look at everyone and said, “I want to take a look at the Atlanta Plane, what do you think?”

When Lizzy and the others heard this, their expression couldn’t help but change. Then Lizzy asked, “Brother Hai, do you really want to go to the Atlanta Plane? When do we leave?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “We’ll go now. Don’t forget, I gave Axe a token. We now have mapped a portion of the Atlanta Plane. We can go there directly and learn about their situation.”

Laura looked at Zhao Hai, her expression looked quite strange as she asked, “Brother Hai, you’re not planning on ascending in the Atlanta Plane, are you?”

When Zhao Hai heard Laura, he couldn’t help but stare for a moment before he shook his head and said, “Impossible, the situation between the Atlanta Plane and the Ark Continent is different. I just want to head there to find clues about the Ascension Magic Armor. I also want to confirm if the plane is under Lu Wei’s control or not, and if not, then I want to find out who the Plane Manager is. I also want to see their relationship with their lower planes.”

When Laura and the others heard Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but nod. To be honest, they also wanted to find out, after all this matter involved the state of their future.

After seeing that the others didn’t speak, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Actually, we can also play around in the Atlanta Plane. The plane has a lot of people in it. As long as we forged some IDs we can explore wherever we want.”

The eyes of Laura and the others lit up when they heard this. Although the Space’s environment was good, they still couldn’t help but feel bored inside. Moreover, there was nothing special inside the place where the Divines were transferred into. Going to a new place right now would be great.

After seeing their reactions, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “If you agree, then let’s go and take a look. What do you think?”

Laura and the others nodded. When he saw their nod, Zhao Hai smiled and then changed the monitor’s image into the Atlanta Plane.

Different from the Ark Continent or the Divine Realm where there were no magic armors, the Atlanta Plane was teeming with all kinds of mechanized suits. The uses of magic armors were numerous. These magic armors weren’t only used for battles or construction, they were also used to things like farm work, the usability of magic armors was immense.

To be honest, when he saw the Atlanta Plane, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but think about Earth. In Atlanta Plane’s Magic Armor Continent, there were things running on the ground like cars. Naturally, these cars used the same energy converters as the magic armors.

However, the energy inside energy converters weren’t from magic beasts. Instead, the energy used by the cars was stored up electric power.

Right, it was electricity. After paying attention to the Atlanta Plane’s situation, Zhao Hai discovered that people were utilizing the power of electricity. Moreover, it seems like they had been using it for a long time.

The structure of their power grid was the same as the one back on Earth. However, the power generated by their power plants weren’t obtained from burning things like charcoal. Instead, their power was gained through hydroelectric plants and wind farms. With the addition of magic formations, their power was like the one used in the Space. But their power was more advanced than the one that Karen set up.

After seeing this, Zhao Hai was very shocked. It was at this point that he can finally confirm his suspicion, the Atlanta Plane wasn’t under Lu Wei’s rule.

Zhao Hai noticed that although planes like the Ark Continent, Demon Realm, and the Divine Realm use magic formations, the level of their formations was very low. With these formations, it would be impossible to develop a decent system, or even a technomagic society.

Moreover, Lu Wei was preventing people on these planes from researching magic formations. Didn’t he order the destruction of the Goblin Race?

What surprised Zhao Hai the most was his result after carefully comparing the magic formations with magic array inside the Seven Star Heaven Lock. Although it can be said that the array inside the Seven Star Heaven Lock was more complex compared to magic formations, Zhao Hai discovered that they were two fundamentally different systems. Even if the magic formations becomes more complex, it was still different compared to the one inside the Seven Star Heaven Lock.

In the beginning, Zhao Hai thought that magic formations and the Seven Star Heaven Lock was just separated by profundity. With enough research, Zhao Hai’s magic formations would reach the Seven Star Heaven Lock’s level.

However, it seems like Zhao Hai was thinking wrongly. Magic formations and the Seven Star Heaven Lock were different. They were like two parallel lines, bound to never intersect.

Upon careful research, Zhao Hai saw that the two systems were a product of two different evolutions. This greatly surprised Zhao Hai, and this also confirms his thought that the Atlanta Plane wasn’t managed by Lu Wei.

Laura and the others gawked at the scene in the monitor. They didn’t think that the Atlanta Plane would have this appearance.

After some time, Zhao Hai turned to the others and said, “It seems like the Atlanta Plane isn’t going to be simple. Laura, pay attention to the clothes that they wear. We’ll need to make clothes that are appropriate before we take a stroll.”

Laura and the others nodded before they carefully stared at the monitor. In the meantime, Zhao Hai looked into his warehouse to see if there was anything he needed.

Besides a set of tattered clothing, Zhao Hai managed to see something useful. There was an ID card that the O’neal family’s pilot owned.

Zhao Hai looked into the ID Card. The contents of the ID card were the same as the ones back on Earth. It was quite detailed, there was the picture of the owner, his height, weight, age, place of birth. There was even a magicrystal function on the top part of the card.

Zhao Hai called the undead O’Neal family pilot who owned this card. Every ID card in the Atlanta Plane seem to have magicrystal implants. They had the same function as a bank card, it records how much money you have.

In the Magic Armor Continent, despite having plenty of Clans, there was only one bank. This bank was jointly controlled by several Great Families. Its purpose was to facilitate the trading and livelihood of the people in the Continent.

Upon hearing the function of the ID card, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but nod. This ID Card did indeed make life more convenient in the Atlanta Plane.

Zhao Hai looked at the magic armor pilot and said, “As long as a person from the Atlanta Plane has these ID Cards, then they would be fine? Do you have any other currency?”

The magic armor pilot nodded and said, “We do, there are three kinds, gold coins, silver coins and copper coins. Gold coins are equal to ten silver coins and also 100 copper coins. Ordinary people use these to make purchases. The money on the ID Cards are used by those industries right under the banks. Usually, people would take their money out of the bank first before spending it.

Zhao Hai nodded, then he waved his hand, returning the magic armor pilot to the Hell Space. After that, he took the ID Card and placed it in the scanner.

After the entire procedure finished, a prompt came in from the scanner, “Unique ID Card from a Technomagic Civilization detected. The card has special methods inside, asking Host for permission to copy. If host wants to copy the ID Card, then Host can head to the Universal Processing Machine. Copied Cards would have a certain amount of money saved inside. The Host can deposit money in these cards using gold coins from the Space.”

Chapter 965: Bank Experience

When Zhao Hai heard the scanner’s prompt, he couldn’t help but curse. This scanner was truly a miserly fellow. In the beginning, it would ask Zhao Hai for money in order to analyze things. And now, it can’t even do a simple thing like artificially giving him money in the ID card. It actually wanted Zhao Hai to spend his gold from the Space.

However, Zhao Hai also knew that there was no way for the scanner to change. He immediately went to the processing machine in order make ID cards for himself as well as for Laura and the others. He also planned to place a hundred thousand gold coins on each card.

Zhao Hai didn’t know the purchasing power of gold coins in the Atlanta Plane. Therefore, he decided to have a hundred thousand gold coins as a buffer.

Before Zhao Hai took the ID cards from the processing machine, Laura and the others went out of the villa. Upon seeing them arrive, Zhao Hai knew what they wanted to do. Zhao Hai turned to Laura and said, “Did you manage to get their style of clothing?” Laura nodded, “There isn’t anything special, they’re not that eye-catching either. Look.” Then after that, the women proceeded to draw the clothes for the processing machine to make.

After waiting for the clothes to finish, Laura and the others immediately put them on. On the other hand, Zhao Hai didn’t need to have clothes prepared for him. His own clothing can transform itself. As long as Zhao Hai willed it, he could dress like anything he wanted.

When the women finished putting their clothing on, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Let’s go and see what the Atlanta Plane is like.” Laura and the others nodded before all of them returned to the living room. After that, Zhao Hai looked for a place where nobody can see them. Then the group appeared there.

Upon arriving in the Atlanta Plane, the group immediately looked all around them. The place was good and the environment wasn’t bad. This caused Zhao Hai to be startled. He thought that since the Atlanta Plane was so developed, then their technology would have a great impact to the environment. But now, it seems like this wasn’t the case. The people from the Atlanta Plane protected their environment well.

The reason why Zhao Hai said this was because when people reach levels like him, then they would be extremely sensitive to their environment. It wouldn’t take Zhao Hai long to know whether the place was polluted or not.

While Laura and the others were curiously looking around, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, let’s get going. Don’t forget, we need to speak the Atlanta Plane’s language.”

Laura and the others nodded, then they carried on to talk using the Atlanta Plane’s language. They had already studied the Atlanta Plane’s language for some time, so they were quite familiar with it already.

The group appeared inside a small city under the O’neal family’s control. As long as they make a few turns, then they would be going along the city’s main street.

After seeing that there weren’t any banks, Zhao Hai went to a pedestrian and gave him a salute before asking, “Mister, can I ask where the bank in this city is? I’m from outside this area and I want to take some money.”

The man turned his head to Zhao Hai and saw an ordinary looking man. There was nothing special on him but there was a cloudy temperament around him, making people look at him favorably. So the man immediately replied, “The Bank is very close. You go straight this road and then turn right, in about five minutes it should be on sight.”

After that, Zhao Hai nodded and expressed his gratitude to the person before leading Laura and the others to proceed. The group inspected everything around them. They could see that this was a very busy street, both sides of the road were filled with tradesmen. It was very noisy. While Laura and the others were looking all around, people were curiously looking at them, some were in surprise.

Zhao Hai’s group was filled with beautiful women, so it was natural that they would be able to turn heads. Zhao Hai didn’t care about this, he just smiled as he received the envious looks of the people around him.

The Atlanta Plane’s people weren’t a monogamous society. Here, as long as you’re rich, you can marry as many wives as you want. Because of this, Zhao Hai’s ID card was able to record his relationship with his wives.

This was also one of the characteristics of the Atlanta Plane’s ID card. When you marry, the name of your spouse would be reflected on the ID card.

After walking for about 10 minutes, the group was finally able to see the bank. The bank looked very well decorated. Zhao Hai looked at the name of the bank, Magic Armor Bank.

Zhao Hai nodded before leading Laura and the others towards the bank. The bank was quite stylish. The entire hall was about five meters high. Its interior decorations were resplendent and rich. Inside the bank, there were rows of counters with people lining up. On the left side of the hall was a place for sitting down.

Near the right side of the hall was a room. On the side of the door, the characters for, ‘VIP lounge’ was written. There was an expensive looking soldier stationed outside the room along with two pretty female staff.

Zhao Hai went directly towards the VIP lounge. Upon seeing Zhao Hai, the two female staff bowed and said, “Welcome Mister, may we please see your ID card.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly before handing his ID over. The female staff gave Zhao Hai’s ID a look before handing it back to Zhao Hai and saying, “We’ll have to be unfair to Mister. We cannot allow you in since you’re not a VIP.”

The people inside the hall noticed Zhao Hai entering the bank along with his beautiful wives. Moreover, he even walked directly towards the VIP lounge. Upon hearing the female staff, some of them laughed.

“So he just wanted to put up an act to enter the VIP lounge. You don’t even have 1 million gold coins deposited, yet you think you’re a VIP? Look at this fool, are these women also deceived by him?”

“Right, right, these beautiful women were fooled by this man. Elder Brother, perhaps you’re richer than him.”

Upon hearing these remarks, the faces of Laura and the others couldn’t help but turn red. If not for Zhao Hai waving his hand to them, they would have began berating these people back.

Zhao Hai wasn’t angry, instead, he looked at the female staff and said, “Sister, I’m aware of the rules. I came here to upgrade mine and my wives’ ID Cards to VIP. Can the VIP lounge handle this?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the people in the hall gawked. Then some of them went to look outside the bank to see whether Zhao Hai had piles of gold following behind him. Otherwise, how could he upgrade a group’s cards to VIP?

But after looking outside, there were no cars parked that were filled with gold coins. The people in the hall had mixed reactions. Some of them had ridiculing smiles on their faces while some remained silent.

There were spatial tools in the Atlanta Plane, but these items were uncommon. They were generally under the hands of people with status. If Zhao Hai didn’t have cars filled with gold coins, then he wouldn’t be able to upgrade his group’s status to VIP. But on the contrary, if Zhao Hai was still able to upgrade his status to VIP, then this meant this his identity wasn’t simple.

When the female staff heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but stare. Then she said, “Mister, please come with me.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he led Laura and the others to enter the VIP lounge. When Zhao Hai’s group entered the VIP with the female staff, the people inside the hall couldn’t help but pay attention to the VIP lounge door. They wanted to see the result. If Zhao Hai was successful in upgrading his ID card, then the people in the bank would be respectful towards him. If he wasn’t, then the staff wouldn’t be polite, they would certainly throw him out. One must know that the influence behind the Magic Armor bank wasn’t weak. If Zhao Hai deceived them, then they surely wouldn’t be polite.

Upon entering the door, Zhao Hai immediately felt the difference. The environment inside the VIP lounge was much better compared to outside. There was gentle music playing in the background. Moreover, the chairs inside weren’t hardwood chairs, they were sofas.

Under the guidance of the female staff, Zhao Hai’s group sat on the sofa. Then the female staff offered them so beverages to drink. After providing Zhao Hai’s group with refreshments, the female staff bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, please wait here in the meantime while I go and call our manager.” Zhao Hai nodded. He thought that the Atlanta Plane was becoming more and more like Earth. This gave him mixed feelings.

Before Zhao Hai even finished his drink, a middle-aged man came over. The man was wearing very formal business attire. Although it wasn’t very gorgeous, his clothing made him look respectable and professional. The man walked to Zhao Hai and bowed, “Mister Zhao Hai, Welcome to Magic Armor Bank. I’m the bank’s manager. Might I ask how much money mister intends to deposit?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’ve made some big business this time. However, the opposite party didn’t send the money through the bank. Instead, he gave me gold bricks. Can those bricks be used as deposit in this bank?”

As soon as the manager heard Zhao Hai, he quickly replied, “Naturally. Mister can rest assured. Gold bricks can be deposited to this bank. We shall help mister convert them to gold coins. There wouldn’t be any mistakes.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s good. Where do you want me to place the gold bricks?”

The manager bowed and said, “I’ll have to ask Mister to come with me. The Mistresses can just stay here and relax.” Zhao Hai nodded before standing up and saying, “Let’s go.” The managed made an inviting gesture. Before going, Zhao Hai turned to Laura and the others and said, “Everyone, give me your ID Cards. I will deposit money to your accounts as well.”

Laura and the others complied and gave Zhao Hai their cards. After receiving the cards, Zhao Hai proceeded to follow the manager.

The manager led Zhao Hai in a respectful manner. He was now convinced that Zhao Hai wasn’t a simple character.

Chapter 966: Unusual Mood

The manager guided Zhao Hai to a room further in the bank. There weren’t anything else inside this room other than a magic formation.

Then the manager turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, please place the gold bricks inside this magic formation.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Then he waved his hand, making a big pile of gold appear inside the formation. From what it looks like, it seems to be valued at least ten million.

When the gold bricks appeared inside the formation, the formation immediately lit up with a golden radiance. After that, on the walls opposite to Zhao hai, rows of digits appeared. Zhao Hai initially didn’t understand what these digits meant. However, after the manager looked at the digits, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, all of your gold bricks value at 12.5 million gold coins. Does Mister want to verify this?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “No need, it’s accurate. Please save 1 million gold coins on each of my wives’ ID Cards. Place the remaining coins on mine.” After that, Zhao Hai handed the cards over to the bank manager.

The manager respectfully received the cards before he said, “Mister can wait for me outside. After I take care of this, I will personally deliver them to Mister.” Zhao Hai nodded before he turned around and left the room.

At this time, Laura and the others were chatting and drinking. When Zhao Hai arrived, the women turned to look at him.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’ll take a while before it’s done. After that, we’ll buy several good cars. Then we’ll play in the city.” Laura and the others nodded.

At this time, the female staff who led them in breathed out a sigh of relief. She wasn’t relieved for Zhao Hai, she was relieved for herself. She rejoiced that she wasn’t being disrespectful towards Zhao Hai earlier. She was glad that Zhao Hai was a genuine customer. If people like the female staff were disrespectful towards a distinguished guest, then they would immediately lose their job. Perhaps they might even suffer further consequences.

Losing a job as the bank staff would be a huge blow. One should know that bank workers were one of the most well-paid people in the Atlanta Plane.

After Zhao Hai sat down and took a drink, he turned to the others and said, “Didn’t you want to have good cars? We’ll buy more cars this time.”

Laura and the others smiled. The female staff couldn’t help but look at Zhao Hai’s women in envy. The female staff didn’t ridicule Zhao Hai’s way of spoiling his women. If such a person was willing to spoil her that much, then even the female staff would be happy.

Before long, the bank manager returned with Zhao Hai’s IDs. After handing the ID cards over to Zhao Hai, the manager said, “Mister, the ID cards have been updated. If Mister has anything else he needs, then we would gladly handle them.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Prepare 10 thousand gold coins, 10 thousand silver coins, and 10 thousand copper coins for me. I won’t be able to buy anything without pocket money.”

The manager immediately replied, “I ask Mister to wait for a moment. I will immediately prepare the coins.” After that, he bowed to Zhao Hai before leaving. Before long, three bags were handed over to Zhao Hai. After receiving his coins, Zhao Hai stood up.

The manager followed Zhao Hai as the group left the VIP lounge. Those who haven’t left the hall looked at Zhao Hai’s group. A lot of people knew the manager, so upon seeing Zhao Hai, they knew that Zhao Hai succeeded in upgrading his card. The people couldn’t help but look at Zhao Hai with envy.

Zhao Hai swept his gaze through the people in the hall before faintly smiling. After following Zhao Hai out of the bank, the manager proceeded to enter return to his post.

After Zhao Hai’s group left the bank, Laura turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, why did you save so much money in your card? We don’t need to buy anything, and the things here aren’t cheap at all.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Who said we won’t buy anything. We have money, so why won’t we spend it? After all, the money we spend is mine.”

Upon hearing this, Laura and the others stared. Then they quickly understood what Zhao Hai meant. They looked at each other and smiled. Zhao Hai intends to throw money away. This wasn’t the first time that he’d done this, it was quite normal.

Megan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, what do you want to buy?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I want to buy a lot of things. For example, books about magic formations and magic armors. Magic armors themselves, and also some cars. It’ll be good if we could buy energy source machines as well. As long as I like it, then I will buy it.”

Megan understood Zhao Hai’s sentiment. To be honest, after seeing the things inside the Atlanta Plane, they couldn’t help but feel envious. They also wanted to have some of the things here. At the same time, Zhao Hai would also like to provide the people inside the Space with the goods from the Atlanta Plane.

After seeing the others’ reactions, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but have a huge smile on his face, “Let’s go and find a hotel first. Then let’s think about what to do next.”

As he said that, Zhao Hai stepped into the road and waved. Laura and the others didn’t understand Zhao Hai’s action. But unexpectedly, an orange vehicle stopped in front of Zhao Hai. It wasn’t a very huge car. It had a sign ‘Taxi’ on its side.

There were three rows of seats inside the car. It looked very well maintained. Zhao Hai opened the door for Laura and the others. After they got in, Zhao Hai sat next to the driver and said, “Take us to the best hotel in town.”

As soon as the taxi driver heard this, he couldn’t help but gawk. Then his expression turned ecstatic as he quickly replied, “Alright, Mister can sit tight.” After that, the taxi drove forward. After a few turns, they stopped in front of a big hotel.

When the taxi stopped, a staff from the hotel immediately came over. Then he opened the door for Zhao Hai’s group.

Zhao Hai nonchalantly tossed a gold coin over to the taxi driver. The taxi driver repeatedly thanked Zhao Hai, but Zhao Hai didn’t care much about it as he walked towards the hotel.

The hotel staff quickly caught up with Zhao Hai and opened the hotel’s door for him. Before entering the hotel, Zhao Hai tossed another gold coin towards the hotel staff.

Zhao Hai didn’t know how popular tipping culture was in the Atlanta Plane. However, rather than being judged by not tipping, he might as well give everyone tips.

When the hotel staff received the gold coin, he immediately expressed his gratitude towards Zhao Hai. It’s evident that tipping was a custom in this place, but a gold coin was also too much.

As soon as Zhao Hai’s group entered the hotel, a female concierge immediately met him. She bowed towards Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, welcome. Does Mister have a reservation?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I don’t. We just arrived at this place today. So we haven’t had the chance.”

The female staff nodded and said, “Mister, come with me.” Then she led Zhao Hai to the reception area. The female reception staff behind the counter bowed and said, “Mister Welcome to our hotel. Do you want to take a room or do you want to dine at our restaurant?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Give me your best room. Somewhere that I can live together with my wives.”

The female staff smiled and said, “Alright, Mister can rest assured. Our best accommodation has ten rooms inside, a dining room, living room, conference room, a swimming pool, a bar, and a fitness room. It can definitely match mister’s requests.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, give me that room.”

The female staff nodded, then she said, “I’ll have to ask Mister’s ID Card.” Then Zhao Hai handed his ID card over. The female staff registered Zhao Hai’s ID card before giving Zhao Hai the room key.

After Zhao Hai received the key, the group was led  by the staff towards the elevator. When everyone had entered, the staff pressed the button for the top floor.

Zhao Hai looked at the elevator button, the top floor turned out to be 55. It was quite high. Meanwhile, Laura and the others were looking at the elevator with curiosity.

Upon entering their accomodation, the staff proceeded to introduce each room and facility. Then after receiving the tip from Zhao Hai, the staff left with a happy face.

Laura and the others looked at their room with curiosity. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and didn’t say anything. He just went to the balcony and looked at the cityscape.

The city had the flavor of a huge metropolis. Moreover, there were a lot of high-rise buildings that were constructed and being constructed. From the hotel’s balcony, one would feel like he was standing on top of the mountain, overlooking everything underneath.

At this time, after looking at the rooms, Laura and the others went to Zhao Hai’s side and said, “Brother Hai, this place is very good. Everything is beautiful.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “If you really like it, we can stay inside a science and technology background for a few days. They also have rooms like these.”

Laura and the others happily nodded. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai just smiled and didn’t say anything else. Metropolis cities just like this one were only attractive because of the people living in them. If you have a city like this but have no people, you would soon feel like you’re living inside a ghost town.

After looking at the rooms, Zhao Hai turned to Laura and the others and said, “Let’s go and eat something. Then we’ll head out and buy things.” Laura and the others nodded, then they proceeded to follow Zhao Hai. Upon arriving at the elevator, Zhao Hai looked at the elevator staff and said, “Take us to the restaurant.” The staff nodded before pressing the button with the number ‘30’ in it.

When Zhao Hai and the others came out of the elevator, the waiter of the restaurant immediately came over and settled them down on a table. Zhao Hai causally ordered some dishes before the waiter retreated.

One must say that the restaurant food of the hotel were very good. After having eaten their meal, Zhao Hai’s group went to the hotel’s lobby.

Just as the group arrived at the lobby, a man dressed in decent formal clothes came over and said, “Mister, hello. I am the hotel’s lobby manager. Does Mister have any requests for the hotel?”

Zhao Hai smiled towards the hotel manager and said, “Hi. Me and my wives would like to buy some cars. Can you help us with this matter?”

The lobby manager immediately replied, “Mister can rest assured, we know exactly where you want to be.” After that, the person next to the manager took Zhao Hai outside of the hotel. Outside, there was a limousine already waiting for them.

The hotel manager personally opened the door for Zhao Hai before asking Zhao Hai to go in. Zhao Hai’s group entered the limousine and saw that it was a really good car. The interior of the car was quite spacious. It could accommodate about a dozen people inside. There was also a refrigerator as well as an audio device.

Laura and the others were curiously inspecting the car. After some time, Laura turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, I thought that we already had good carriages back in the Ark Continent. But compared to this, they still fall short.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly without saying anything. To be honest, among everyone here, his mood was the most complex. Although it can be said that he enjoyed his time after transmigrating, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel strange after arriving at the Atlanta Plane. Even if there were no connections between the Atlanta Plane and Earth, they were still quite similar. Zhao Hai thought about his time in the Atlanta Plane and compared it with his time on Earth. Back on Earth, Zhao Hai didn’t enjoy much of his life. He was an otaku with no merit to his name. He had seen limousines on the television and has hoped to ride it one day. So while Zhao Hai was sitting inside the car, his heart couldn’t help but feel incomparably strange.

While Laura and the others explored the limousine, Zhao Hai just sat and looked out the window. His thoughts returned back to his time on Earth. The Atlanta Plane made him recall his previous life, both the good and the bad. It was at this time where Zhao Hai realized that there were some things that you would appreciate only when you lose it. Whether it be good or bad things, one would still think fondly upon it. Although there were a lot of negatives in his life on Earth, although there were no major events, it was still his original life.

Laura and the others discovered that Zhao Hai wasn’t too enthusiastic. They stopped chatting as they sat beside Zhao Hai. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Brother Hai, what’s wrong? Why do you look unhappy?”

Zhao Hai looked at their eyes and smiled, “It’s nothing. But I just thought of thanking the heavens that I run into all of you. Meeting you is the luckiest thing that happened to me.”

Laura and the others smiled. They knew that something must be in Zhao Hai’s mind. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have said this out of the blue. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Brother Hai, what happened?”

Chapter 967: Recreational Vehicle

Upon seeing their expressions, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel guilty. At the same time, he put away the extra thoughts in his mind. He understood that every move that he made wouldn’t only concern himself, he also had Laura and the others to think about.

No matter how much he missed his life back on Earth, he couldn’t go back. At this moment, he wasn’t Zhao Hai of Earth, he was Zhao Hai Buda, the Patriarch of the Buda Clan and the husband of the ladies sitting by his side.

When he thought about this, Zhao Hai immediately cleared his mind. He looked at Laura and the others and said, “I’m fine. I was just thinking about the time I was sent to the Black Wasteland. At that time, I didn’t think even dream of being in place like this.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Laura and the others sighed in relief. Then Laura smiled and said, “Doesn’t this show Brother Hai’s abilities? You relied on your efforts and bit by bit you were able to reach your current state.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “It’s not just me. I relied on the Space. Perhaps without the Space, the present Zhao Hai wouldn’t exist. It’s possible that the Buda Clan would already sunk into the annals of history.”

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and then smiled, “Brother Hai, I don’t believe other people could achieve this much even if they had the Space. Not everyone can utilize the Space to its maximum potential like you. You have been very low-key all this time. Don’t forget, the Space wasn’t this powerful in the beginning. If other people had the Space, then they wouldn’t have been as patient as you. Brother Hai, the Space is just a tool. It’s abilities are limited, and the one who determines its fate is always its user.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’m fine, there’s no need to comfort me. In any case, I’m already happy to have the Space. Right, what kind of car do you want to buy? Actually, we can’t use the cars for long. After we achieved our goal in the Atlanta Plane, we would be going back. When that time comes, we won’t be able to use them anymore.”

As soon as Laura and the others heard this, they immediately went to discuss. After seeing their chirping, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile.

At this time, their vehicle stopped. After that, their driver opened the door for Zhao Hai. When Zhao Hai went out of the car, the driver bowed and said, “Mister, this the biggest vehicle store in the city. There are a lot of cars available here. Mister can choose whatever car you like.”

Zhao Hai nodded and thanked the driver. After that, he took five gold coins and handed it over. After the driver expressed his gratitude, he proceeded to return to his car.

Zhao Hai turned his head to look at the huge car dealership. The store was very huge and stylish. What differs this store compared to others was the fact that there were no advertisements outside the store. The only thing that can be seen in front of the store was an ancient looking car.

The succinct design of the store gave of it the aura of a noble that was wearing commoner clothes. Even if the noble was wearing simple cllthing, his temperament could still be seen.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but praise the store, “Good, good. Just by its appearance, one could see that it’s very good. Go, see if there are any cars you want.”

Laura and the others proceeded to cheer and enter the huge store. Zhao Hai just smiled faintly. However, he didn’t run over and just calmly entered the store.

Just as he entered, Zhao Hai was immediately met with a store staff. The woman was wearing a dress. Although the dress made her look very bright, it wasn’t to the point being excessive. Her dress just made her exude a smart and capable appearance.

The female staff bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, welcome to our establishment. I am store staff Number 215.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Hello. It seems like you have quite the collection here.” The staff nodded and said, “Yes. Mister, please I’ll be leading you in. What do you want to buy? We have ordinary cars, commercial cars, sports cars, and recreational vehicles.”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and said, “I want to take a look at your recreational vehicles first. I want something that can travel anywhere.”

The staff immediately said, “Alright, please follow me.” After that, she led Zhao Hai to a place inside the store.

Zhao Hai looked at the store and saw Laura and the others looking at various sports cars. One has to recognize how cool and dazzling sports cars could be. They were very appealing to the eyes.

After Laura and the others saw Zhao Hai, they immediately went to him as Laura said, “Brother Hai, we like these ones. Can we buy them?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “If you want to buy it, then go ahead. I still need to look at their recreational vehicles.”

Laura replied, “Recreational Vehicles? Alright, then let’s see them first.” After that, they followed Zhao Hai as they were led by the store staff.

The store staff was a bit shaken. Laura and the others were rare beauties, and it seems like these ladies were Zhao Hai’s wives. This caused her to be surprised, this was because Zhao Hai looked too ordinary.

The female staff didn’t believe that Laura and the others were with Zhao Hai because of money. Although the women were indeed beautiful, they couldn’t just fake their noble temperament. Even if the female staff’s dress made her look capable, her temperament still fell short compared to Zhao Hai’s wives.

Although the female staff was curious about Zhao Hai, she didn’t ask nor should she care. Being too curious would just bring her trouble.

Before long, under the guidance of the store staff, Zhao Hai arrived at where the recreational vehicle was. Zhao Hai looked at it and discovered that the RVs of the Atlanta Plane were much larger compared to those back on Earth. Their RV here wasn’t smaller than a carriage. This caused Zhao Hai to be surprised.

Laura and the others were also surprised upon seeing the RV. They didn’t think that they would see a car that was as large as this.

Upon seeing this, Zhao Hai finally understood why the roads of the Atlanta Plane were wider than the ones on Earth. It seems like it was caused by the Atlanta Plane’s much higher technological level.

The female staff arrived right by the silvery bright RV and said, “Mister, please take a look. This car is produced by the O’Neal family. This recreational vehicle is divided into three floors, each floor having 125 square meters of floor space each. On the first floor, there is a miniature parking lot about 1 meter high. This parking lot would automatically descend to the ground when needed. Once you park your car, it will return to its original position inside the vehicle. All in all, the parking lot could accommodate eight cars. Each section of parking could be separated. You can descend to any parking section from the second floor and then proceed to drive. It’s very convenient.”

“Situated on the second floor are the living room, bathroom,  a fitness room, a miniature swimming pool, and other facilities. The furniture inside are all complete. All seats are made with high-grade magic beast leather. They’re very comfortable to sit on.”

“Bedroom are placed on the third floor. All in all, there are six bedrooms each with their own bathroom.”

“These are the three floors of a conventional RV. At its roof is a small courtyard where you can host small parties while on the road.”

“Windows on both sides of the car can also be opened and act as small sheds to protect against the sun. You can park your car and then proceed to enjoy a picnic.”

“The materials used to construct these RVs are all high quality copper alloys. Not only is the vehicle strong against shaking, it is also quite light for its size. There are a lot of magic formations on the vehicle, and it even uses engines made for war tanks. Because of its strong horsepower, the car could still go fast despite its large build.”

“The tires of the vehicle are made of special elastomers. Even nails would be broken when they’re being run through. The suspension mechanism is also made according to standards used for war tanks. There wouldn’t’ be any issues even if you go through a rugged mountain path.”

While the staff was explaining the function of the vehicle, they also played the functions of the car. Laura and the others were shocked to see the RV. Now they finally understood why it was named like that, it was basically a small mobile house. The carriages of the Ark Continent could only be called primitive compared to this.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai wasn’t as startled. Although it was bigger and more advanced than the RVs back on earth, their fundamental function wasn’t any different.

After the staff was done with the introduction, Zhao Hai looked at her and said, “Are there other cars like this one?”

The store staff quickly replied, “It’s the only one. Mister, this RV is the most advanced vehicle of its type. Others simply couldn’t compare to it. Moreover, this car is being promoted by the O’Neal family. They’re limited in supply.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “How much is it?” When the staff heard this, she couldn’t help but stare. Then she quickly understood that Zhao Hai was interested in the vehicle so she immediately answered, “The vehicle is priced fairly. As long as you pay 500 thousand gold coins, our company would take care of everything including licensing as well as any other modifications you have for the vehicle.”

Zhao hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, prepare one of these for me.” Then he turned to Laura and the others and said, “Didn’t you like those sports cars? Go take a look so we can have them installed in the parking spaces.”

When the store staff heard this, she immediately lit up with happiness as she said, “Alright Mister, we’ll take care of it. I’m sure the madames would be satisfied with our collection of vehicles.”

Chapter 968: Meeting Warriors At Night

When Zhao Hai left the shop, he was already inside his recreational vehicle. Zhao Hai already learned how to drive back on Earth, and driving in the Atlanta Plane was much easier. This was because; One, the roads here were very wide. Two, because the cars were equipped with automatic transmission. And third, because almost all cars had an anti-collision formation installed. As long as one uses this formation, one wouldn’t need to worry about accidents. Of course, one can choose to turn this formation off.

Naturally, Zhao Hai had this formation installed in his RV. Moreover, he had modifications made on the RV in order to make it more comfortable. And with eight sports cars in the parking compartments, Zhao Hai spent more than 1 million gold coins in total.

This purchase also made Zhao Hai realize the buying power of gold coins in the Atlanta Plane. Gold coins seem to be worth a lot.

Zhao Hai drove back towards the hotel and checked out of their room before proceeding to drive off the city. He already bought a car and deposited a huge amount of money in the bank. This might cause unnecessary attention to be placed on their group. Since Zhao Hai didn’t want any complications to occur, he decided to head off to other places.

When they went out of the city, Zhao Hai released the O’neal family pilot and then had him drive the RV. Zhao Hai already bought a map before leaving, and their next destination was the neighboring city..

Zhao Hai and the others didn’t immediately enter the Space after leaving the city. They still wanted to understand the Atlanta Plane better. The roads of the Atlanta Plane were very well maintained and were very wide. Each road could allow four vehicles like their RV to go side by side.

In the beginning, Zhao Hai didn’t understand why the roads outside the city were this wide. But later on, he got the reason from the magic armor pilot. The roads were wide so that war tanks would be able to easily make use of it.

Although Zhao Hai’s RV was very big, it still wasn’t as wide as a war tank. The roads could allow two war tanks to go side by side at most. Three would be pushing it.

Zhao Hai and the others looked at the scenery they passed by and saw that it was very good. Both sides of the roads were protected forests. Later on, they came to understand that the environment inside the Atlanta Plane was very nice. There were forests and meadows everywhere, it was quite rich in nature.

Before long, the days passed by and darkness came. Zhao Hai had the RV stop as they prepared for the night.

It wasn’t that Zhao Hai didn’t want to go to the Space to rest. Instead, Laura and the others wanted to use the RV to experience what its like to stay inside a vehicle. Naturally, Zhao Hai agreed.

Meg made their dinner in the RV’s kitchen. After finishing their meal, they went to the rooftop to look at the stars before going to their rooms to sleep.

There was no need to mention how comfortable the rooms inside the RV were. Zhao Hai was sleeping with Meg tonight. The two didn’t do anything and just slept side by side.

When midnight came, Zhao Hai was suddenly woken up. This was because he felt some people in the proximity approaching them in a fast speed. Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he got up and moved Laura and the others to the Space. He also entered the Space and looked at the monitor.

Zhao Hai saw how fast these people were approaching. Moreover, these people weren’t using magic armors. Their movement was like what warriors back in the Ark Continent did.

Zhao Hai noted at this point that the O’Neal family, as well as the rest of Magic Armor Continent,  didn’t allow warriors nor mages in their territory. They had a hostile relationship with warriors and mages. If these two people were spotted in the Magic Armor Continent, then they wouldn’t have a good time.

Not long after Zhao Hai entered the Space, several warriors appeared right outside the parked RV. When the warriors saw the vehicle, they immediately surrounded it. They carefully looked at the car before one of them sighed and said, “This is quite a good vehicle. Leader, what do we do?” These warriors were wearing black clothing and had their swords strapped to their backs. Black cloths were covering their faces with only their eyes showing.

Another warrior in their group answered, “Don’t cause any incidents. Don’t forget our goal. Let’s go.” The warriors nodded. After sparing one last envious glance at the RV, the warriors proceeded to leave.

Zhao Hai counted the warriors. Altogether, there were ten of them. They were very fast, they should have about the same strength as the Ark Continent’s seven or eight ranked warriors.

When Zhao Hai saw this, he couldn’t help but stare. With the strength that these people possessed, it was impossible for them to exist here in the Magic Armor Continent. What did they come here for?

Fortunately, the group of warriors went along the road, so Zhao Hai was able to pay attention to their actions. Before long, the group entered the city that Zhao Hai came from. In the Magic Armor Continent, cities didn’t have any walls. This allowed the warriors to enter the settlement very easily.

After entering the city, the group immediately proceeded to go about undetected before entering a house. The residents of the house seem to be expecting their arrival. They immediately let the warriors in before closing the door.

At this moment, Zhao Hai was paying attention to the warrior group. It can be said that Zhao Hai was a careful person. Before leaving the city, he took the time to explore the entire city just enough so that the Space could map the entirety of it. Now, he could see the actions of those people using the monitor.

After the group entered the house, they immediately took their hoods off. When the owner of the house saw them, he handed them a document and said, “Good, you came on time. These are your ID Cards and the address of the place where you’ll be staying. Remember your mission. Make sure to understand what the O’Neal family has been doing lately.”

The leader of the warrior group took the document and gave it a quick scan. Then he nodded and said, “You can rest assured.” Then he led the warriors to leave the room.

Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai didn’t have any interest to listen. Then Zhao Hai let out a long breath. This was an internal affair of the Magic Armor Continent, it didn’t have any relationship to him.

As for the status of these warriors, Zhao Hai didn’t need to look it up in order to guess. They were certainly assassins from a Great Family in the Magic Armor Continent. Although it can be said that this was a continent for magic armors, there were certain matters that magic armors couldn’t handle but these assassins could. Because of this, it wouldn’t be strange for Great Families to train warriors in order to serve their goals.

It was at this moment where a scream suddenly came from a room.

Laura and the others opened their doors and walked out with their night robes still on. When they saw Zhao Hai on the living room looking at the monitor, they couldn’t help but gawk. Zhao Hai looked at the women and smiled faintly, “It’s fine, everything’s alright. Go back to sleep. There was a group of warriors approaching the RV earlier. I didn’t know what they intend to do, so I took it upon myself to move you into the Space. Everything’s fine now.”

There was still a hint of fear lingering in the minds of the ladies. They went to Zhao Hai’s side before Laura asked, “Brother Hai, what happened? Why are there warriors in the Magic Armor Continent?”

Zhao Hai looked at Laura and said, “Don’t worry, it’s fine. It’s possible that those warriors are assassins from a Great Family in the Magic Armor Continent. It seems like the recent actions of the O’Neal family had been brought to the attention of these Families. Therefore, they sent people to look into what the O’Neal family was doing.”

After hearing Zhao Hai, Laura and the others quickly relaxed. Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “Alright, go back to sleep.” Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as the group returned to their rooms in the RV.

Laura and the others looked at where they were, then they proceeded to go back to sleep. They were experienced people as well. Therefore, although what happened managed frighten them, they were able to quickly recover.

The next day, Laura and the others regained their usual vigor. After having eaten their breakfast, they proceeded to depart.

Zhao Hai sat on the roof of the vehicle as he looked at the great scenery. Laura, who sat beside Zhao Hai, suddenly turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, in about three hours, we’ll arrive at the city. According to the map, the city should be called Yanking City. We should be able to buy things there.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Now we need to buy all kinds of magic armors, methods of energy conversion, and news about the Atlanta Plane. However, we could only buy magic armors available for civilians. I’m afraid military magic armors aren’t available for us. On the other hand, the method of energy conversion should be purchasable, albeit certainly not cheap.”

Laura nodded and said, “There’s another issue, purchasing all of these things without being noticed would be very hard. Brother Hai, how about this, let’s buy the books first. Then we’ll buy everything else later on.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Right, books are the key. It’s also best to find secret places where we can steal formations that aren’t available outside. The research on magic formations is the most important thing for us.”

Laura and the others nodded. It was just like in the Ark Continent where the top-ranked martial arts manuals weren’t available for the public. In the Atlanta Plane, there were special magic formations that couldn’t be gained using conventional methods. If Zhao Hai wanted to acquire those formations, then he would have to look for a place to steal them from.

At this time, Lizzy added, “Another important thing is the Ascension Magic Armor. But where do we obtain those?”

Zhao Hai also knit his brows and said, “That wouldn’t be easy to find out. Later on, we need to map more cities into the Space. That way, we would obtain some useful clues.”

Chapter 969: I Must Run A Factory

Yanking City was a large city under the O’Neal family’s rule. Although this city wasn’t the family’s capital, it was still an important industrial base for the family, making it one of the most important cities under the family’s control.

Zhao Hai’s next goal was here. Although he can easily get what he wants, he intends to attract as little attention to himself as possible. If he wanted something, then he would need to spend money. And when he’s ready to leave, he would get all his money back from the bank.

After the group arrived at Yanking City, they immediately went to look for a good hotel to stay in. Upon receiving their accommodations, Zhao Hai went outside to look at the situation. Zhao Hai already made some plans. If he wanted to buy a lot of things without attracting suspicion, then the only way for him to do so was to open a company in Yanking City.

While Zhao Hai went to inquire about the city’s matters, Laura and the others separated and drove towards several bookstores. All the books that they liked and deemed useful were bought.

Zhao Hai drove to many areas of the city in order to gain a general idea. However, it wasn’t easy to acquire any information about opening a company here. After all, he was unfamiliar with the people and the place.

When Zhao Hai returned to the hotel, Laura and the others had also come back. Aside from buying a large number of books, they also bought a lot of clothes and other stuff.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about it as he put the books away. After that, the group proceeded to enter the Space and look at the monitor. The current image displayed was the state of the Taurus Continent. Their efforts to lure the O’Neal family to the Winged Pegasus had finally bore fruit. In about two days, the O’neal family should see the Winged Pegasus Clan’s spatial rift.

Since there was nothing to worry about, Zhao Hai changed the monitor’s display to Yanking City’s map. Yanking City was an industrial city, there was an overwhelming number of large and small factories operating inside. It may be because the O’Neal family needed great production capabilities in order to make more magic armors and war tanks. Because of this, factories became more prosperous.

After seeing the state of these factories, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but knit his eyebrows as he turned to Laura and said, “I need to buy a factory here. This way, I could buy things in the name of the company. However, the business of these factories is doing very good. I’m afraid there will be nobody who’ll want to sell. From the current state, running a factory wouldn’t be an easy matter.”

Laura nodded. She had done business before, so she understood matters beneath the surface. Although businesses in the Atlanta Plane were different than those in the Ark Continent, anyone with keen business senses would know that setting up a factory at this point wouldn’t be easy.

Zhao Hai knit his brows before he said, “Let’s go. I want to ask the people in this hotel. Let’s see if they can introduce me to someone who could help us.”

Since they didn’t have anything else they could do, Laura and the others could only nod. After the group appeared outside their room, Zhao Hai immediately called for the lobby manager.

Zhao Hai lived inside the hotel’s best accommodation. Therefore, the lobby manager couldn’t just ignore his summons. Upon hearing that Zhao Hai wanted to see him, the manager immediately arrived.

.Zhao Hai looked at the lobby manager. The man’s age seem to be on the bigger side. His hair was white and he had a moustache. However, he had tidily arranged himself. When the manager entered the room, he quickly said, “Mister, do you need something?”

Zhao Hai smiled towards the manager and said, “I’m not from this place. I heard that the factory business in Yanking City is quite booming recently so I thought of doing business here. But since I’m unfamiliar with the city, I can only ask lobby manager to act as a middleman and introduce me to people I need to know if I want to build or buy a factory in the city. I wonder if manager can help me with this?”

The manager immediately replied, “Mister can rest assured, we have agencies that specialize in matters like these. I will contact the best Head-hunting agency for Mister.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Then I would have to trouble the Manager. Price isn’t an issue, but I want the person to be reliable. After this, I certainly wouldn’t mistreat the Manager.”

The manager immediately replied, “Mister is too polite. As the hotel’s staff member, I can’t accept any remuneration. I would be violating the rules. I wonder when Mister plans to see the person?”

Zhao Hai thought about it and said, “The sooner the better. But today would be too early, I’ll see them tomorrow.”

The manager nodded and said, “Good. Mister can rest assured, I will arrange a meeting as soon as possible. Once they contact me, I will immediately inform you.”

Zhao Hai nodded and waved his hand to make the manager retreat. Once the manager was out of the room, Laura turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, is getting a Professional Manager really the right decision?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Rest assured, they can do it. They are trained specifically to handle matters like ours. Do you want to go out and take a stroll? In a city like this, people don’t generally rest in the evening. The city’s nightlife should be very rich.”

As soon as Laura and the others heard this, they happily nodded. Then Zhao Hai smiled as he led Laura and the others to leave. After asking the hotel to arrange a car for them, they immediately walked out.

Zhao Hai wasn’t wrong. The nightlife of people in this city was truly colorful. What made Zhao Hai glad was the presence of a stadium here. He can now watch some matches being held.

Zhao Hai paid attention and saw that their games here was very similar to football. Zhao Hai immediately called the hotel in order to arrange some game tickets. He then led Laura and the others to see the game.

Back on Earth, Zhao Hai wasn’t able to go to a stadium in order to watch a game. In his country, football wasn’t heavily promoted. And there was no need to mention about going abroad. In this case, Zhao Hai had no way to see games in person.

Zhao Hai wasn’t a hardcore sports fan. He only knew the rules of the game and he didn’t have any teams that he supported. He just wanted to watch the game because it looked lively.

At the same time, Laura and the others haven’t seen a single sports match. Games like football were nonexistent in the Ark Continent. For those who always thought about military tactics and cultivation, games where you kick a ball was seen as a joke. Instead of playing football, they might as well spend the time training.

Laura and the others were very curious about the game. Because of this, after having their dinner at the hotel, they immediately arranged for a vehicle to take them to the stadium. What made Zhao Hai somewhat excited about the game was the fact that two rivals were the ones playing. It was the Red Coat Club, Yanking City’s team, against the team from Derby City.

The tickets they had weren’t in the VIP rooms. Zhao Hai always thought that the true way of watching a game was on the stand.

Zhao Hai’s group arrived at the stadium at about Atlanta Plane’s 8:30pm, the game would start at 9:00 pm. Laura and the others followed Zhao Hai into the stadium and upon entering, the ladies were shocked. Although the game was in half an hour, the stadium was packed with people wearing colored clothes.

People were singing their songs inside the stadium. The ladies haven’t seen something like this before, they was shocked speechless. Although Zhao Hai had seen these things in TV, being in person was still a more surreal experience.

Before long, Zhao Hai and the others had found their seats. Their location was very good, it was quite close to the field. In that short distance, they were able to see the looks of the players.

At exactly 9:00pm, the match began. The entire field detonated with cheers. One couldn’t hear anything besides the cheers towards both teams. Even if the person was right next to you, one would still need to listen carefully in order to comprehend their words.

However, once the game began, Laura and the others couldn’t feel somewhat disappointed. They were experts, and they had also seen warriors and mages traversing terrain as though it was nothing. They couldn’t feel the same was as the people watching inside the stadium.

But under the current atmosphere, they still couldn’t help but continue watching the game. It was a 90-minute game. With the intermission and overtime, the entire match took two hours to finish. Since they were early by 30 minutes, Zhao Hai’s group stayed inside the stadium for a bit less than three hours.

In these three hours, the fans of both teams never stopped cheering. Their songs were loud from beginning up to the end. Laura and the others couldn’t help but admire their spirit.

After the group returned to their vehicle, Laura rubbed her ears and said, “Too frantic. Those people are too loud. Brother Hai, you said that they haven’t learned battle qi nor had military training. How could they shout that loud for three straight hours? Every one of them are full of spirit.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Perhaps it’s because of the game’s charm. It’s difficult for people like us to understand them. To them, football is just like religion.” Laura thought for a moment and said, “Brother Hai, is it possible for the people inside the Space to play this game? The Space is severely lacking in entertainment.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It won’t be easy. There are a lot of races inside the Space. I’m afraid that there would be some disparity in each team. How would Goblins play against the others? I think we should just abandon this idea.”

Laura couldn’t help but agree. Zhao Hai just smiled and didn’t say anything else. One of the reasons he wanted to see that match was to introduce Atlanta Plane’s lifestyle to Laura and the others. He wanted them to see a lifestyle different from the Ark Continent.

Atlanta Plane was very similar to Earth. Zhao Hai wanted to make Laura and the others understand the plane’s culture so that they may share something similar with Zhao Hai.

Nothing noteworthy happened that night. The next morning, as the hotel’s staff were delivering breakfast, the lobby manager led someone to Zhao Hai’s room.

The manager bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, this is the Professional Manager that the Headhunting Agency has recommended. He can help Mister with what you want.”

After the manager’s introduction, the Professional Manager immediately bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, Hello. I’m called Bluewell. Being able to serve Mister would be a great honor.”

Zhao Hai inspected the man. He looked like he was in his 30s. He wore appropriate clothing and had his hair properly combed. The man’s eyes seem to sparkle.

Zhao Hai looked at Bluewell and said, “Mister Bluewell, nice to meet you. Please have a seat.” Bluewell was very polite as he took a seat and sat down. He didn’t have any hesitations in his actions which made Zhao Hai very satisfied.

As an Agent, being someone who seemed easy to talk to was a sign of professionalism. If one was cautious with their actions, then that Agent was no good.

The hotel manager didn’t leave and just stood there. The manager understood that Zhao Hai had yet to accept the Agent Bluewell. It can be said that Bluewell was still at the interview stage. If he was unable to satisfy Zhao Hai, then the hotel manager would have to find another person.

Zhao Hai looked at Bluewell and said, “Mister Bluewell, did the manager tell you about my request?”

Bluewell immediately replied, “Yes Mister, the manager already informed me that you wanted to purchase a factory in Yanking City, or maybe build your own.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “What would Mister Bluewell suggest?” Bluewell replied, “Mister, if I may frankly speak. I think Mister purchasing a factory in Yanking City wouldn’t be a wise decision. Factory business is doing very well in Yanking City. Nobody would be willing to let go of their factories. And even if they did, they would do so at a very high price. Therefore, purchasing a factory at this time would not be worth it.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he had also thought of this point. Therefore, he waved his hand, telling Bluewell to continue. After seeing Zhao Hai’s response, Bluewell went on, “However, I think it’s possible to open a factory by yourself. Yanking City had always been an industrial hub. There are a lot of factories here. Not only the O’Neal family, other families also run factories in this place. Mister can open a factory here, but I don’t know what kind Mister wants to build.” Zhao hai looked at Bluewell and said, “What can you suggest?”

Bluewell replied, “My suggestion is, if Mister has the money, then Mister should open a medium sized factory. Not too big nor not too small. Big factories in the City are under the control of the O’Neal family vassals. If you want to run a big factory, then you need to cooperate with them or else you would be under the O’Neal family’s pressure. On the other hand, if you run a small factory, then I’m afraid making a sizable profit would be very difficult. Therefore, running a medium factory would be appropriate.”

Chapter 970: Believe Me!

Zhao Hai calmly listened to Bluewell’s words. Bluewell’s explanation was very concise, there was no point that Zhao Hai didn’t understand. He even said the rules of the city’s businesses.

Such rules can be reflected at any place. Yanking City was an industrial hub, the factories here were very profitable. This was something that almost the entire Magic Armor Continent knew. Moreover, almost all of the industrial hubs have some connection to war departments.

Take Yanking City for example, how could the O’Neal family just let go of its control over it? Can they rest assured when outsiders settle here? Impossible. It was equivalent to letting others take the sword that you use to fight.

Because of this, all large factories in Yanking City were controlled by the O’Neal family. Even if they weren’t under the family’s control, they would handled by loyal vassals of the family. Only through this arrangement could the family be relieved.

After Bluewell finished speaking, he looked to see Zhao Hai’s reaction. He found that Zhao Hai was calmly sitting in front of him. It seems like Zhao Hai was pondering over his words. Bluewell couldn’t help but feel nervous.

Although Bluewell was an professional manager, he wasn’t a formal member of the Agency. He was someone who had the ability but hasn’t had the chance to showcase it. Because the Agency knew about his skills, they kept his contact number. Once someone looks for an agent for help, then they would give Bluewell the opportunity to show his skills.

Naturally, this opportunity wasn’t given to everyone. If the client didn’t have the calibre to face Bluewell, then they wouldn’t send him over.

This time, the hotel manager was the one who called the Agency. The manager’s hotel was a very famous institution in Yanking City. Since the agency didn’t want to offend the hotel, they sent Bluewell over.

Bluewell always wanted to find opportunities to show his ability. So after being briefed by the agency regarding Zhao Hai’s situation, he immediately settled himself and went to see Zhao Hai.

After having thought through everything, Zhao Hai turned to Bluewell and said, “Mister Bluewell, let me ask. If I ask you to help me open a factory, how much money would I need?”

When Bluewell heard Zhao hai, he couldn’t help but turn ecstatic. He clearly prepared this answer as he immediately opened his mouth and said, “A minimum of three million gold coins and a maximum of five.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Mister Bluewell, I’m very satisfied with your answer. I can give you five million gold coins to help me open a factory. I will not directly operate this business and will leave all of that to you. I’ll also give you a tenth of the factory’s shares. Although I won’t meddle in the business, I’ll have ask your help to buy me things through the company from time to time. Is this alright with you?”

Bluewell was shocked. He understood what Zhao Hai just said. Zhao Hai would give him five million gold coins to open a factory, of which 10 percent of the shares would be named under him. Everything the company does would be under Bluewell’s care, Zhao Hai would just gain the dividends.

Was there such a good thing? Bluewell felt that he was inside a Manager’s dream. Even if one was a manager and in a high position, one would still be an employee. However, this wasn’t the case with Zhao Hai. Bluewell was a shareholder of the company. Ten percent wasn’t a small number, this was basically a meat pie that fell from the heavens!

Bluewell looked at Zhao Hai, his eyes shining as he said, “Mister, are you sure about this?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I never joke about these matters. If you agree, then we can immediately sign an agreement. I will send you the money and leave everything else to you. What do you think?”

Bluewell looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Alright, Mister can rest assured. You can trust me, this Bluewell will dedicate his life to Mister.”

Zhao Hai laughed, then he turned to the hotel manager and said, “Manager, please help us find a lawyer. I need to sign a contract with Mister Bluewell.’

The manager nodded. Then he looked at Bluewell enviously before he turned to leave. After the manager left, Bluewell turned to Zhao Hai and asked, “Mister, why did you trust me?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I didn’t trust you. I believed in myself and my eye for people. Moreover, to be honest with you, 5 million isn’t a huge amount to me. But if you dare betray me, hehe, then I will make you understand the feeling of wanting to die instead of living!”

When Bluewell heard Zhao Hai, his eyes couldn’t help but shrink. Then he nodded and said, “I understand. Mister, you can rest assured, I will not let you down.” Zhao Hai smiled and said, “As long as you don’t deliberately swallow the money in the factory, whatever you do is fine. If the factory goes bankrupt, and it isn’t because of your mismanagement, then I wouldn’t blame you. Just do normal business and make money.”

Bluewell smiled faintly and said, “Just like Mister, I’m also confident in myself. You can be relieved with the five million that you gave me. I promise that in less than a year, you would be able to get your investment back. After getting my dividends, I will give everything to you.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “You are really confident. Since you believe in yourself so much, then I will give you 5% shares after one year. We’ll include that in the contract.”

Bluewell looked at Zhao Hai and suddenly sighed, “I’m starting to doubt if you are really an heir to a Great Family. Otherwise, you wouldn’t be nonchalant about your money. Of the 5 million, you’re giving me 500 thousand, and if you add the 5%, that is 750 thousand gold coins in total. Even small families would have a hard time earning that much money in one year.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Money, you won’t gain it if you don’t gamble. And if this 15% share could buy your loyalty, then wouldn’t that be worth it?”

Bluewell looked at Zhao Hai, then he laughed and said, “If more people think like Mister, then Professional Managers would be more relaxed.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Not all Managers are like Mister Bluewell!” Then both of them laughed.

After some time, the two calmed down, but the two of them seem to have developed a sense of understanding with each other. Bluewell looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister I haven’t asked you yet. What do you plan to buy through the factory?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and finally said, “I want to buy a set of energy conversion equipment and maybe some magic armors, some civilian ones. Having military magic armors would also be great.”

Bluewell nodded and said, “That won’t be difficult. Energy converters are widespread and can be easily purchased. Besides, with our factory, purchasing them wouldn’t be difficult. As for civilian magic armors, you can buy as many as you want. You can also buy military magic armors, but the amount would be limited.” Zhao Hai stared, then he became happy as he asked, “Good, but what levels of military magic armors can I buy?”

Bluewell replied, “You can buy magic armors below God-rank. However, you can only obtain them from black markets, and their price would be more expensive.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Money is not an issue. As long as you can buy them then it’s alright. But remember, don’t let these matters affect the factory. We don’t want to kill the goose that lays golden eggs.”

Bluewell nodded and said, “Mister can rest assured, I know how to be discrete.”

After he said that, the hotel manager suddenly appeared along with a person who looked refined. From the introduction made by the hotel manager, Zhao Hai found out that the person was from a famous law firm in the city. He came here specifically to arrange Zhao Hai’s contract.

Zhao Hai didn’t waste any breath as he immediately expressed the agreement with Bluewell. After the lawyer wrote the contract, Zhao Hai looked at it and wrote his name upon seeing that there were no problems. This time, he only signed the name ‘Zhao Hai’ instead of ‘Zhao Hai Buda’

When he forged his ID card, he only used ‘Zhao Hai’ as his name and not ‘Zhao Hai Buda’

After the contract was written, Zhao Hai got one copy, Bluewell got one, and another went to the law firm for documentation. Now, Zhao Hai’s agreement with Bluewell was official.

Zhao Hai led Bluewell towards Magic Armor Bank and directly entered the VIP lounge. This time, nobody stopped Zhao Hai from entering. After looking at Zhao Hai’s ID Card, the staff immediately welcomed him in.

Upon entering the VIP lounge, the bank manager immediately approached Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, I am the lounge manager. Is there anything I can do for you?” Zhao Hai looked at the manager before handing his ID card over and saying, “Get 5 million from my card and give them to this Mister right here.”

Bluewell also handed his ID card over. The manager took the two cards and left the VIP lounge. The number of transactions that the manager handles wasn’t a lot, and 5 million was quite a lot of money. However, the manager had seen a lot of things, so he wasn’t surprised at all.

Before long, the manager came back holding the two ID cards. Then he handed it over to Zhao Hai and Bluewell. Then the manager said, “Mister, it’s done. Is there anything else you need?”

Zhao Hai didn’t reply, instead, he turned to Bluewell and said, “Alright, I’ve already given you the money. Everything else is up to you. You go first, I still have other matters to attend to” Bluewell nodded before he gave a bow and leaving the lounge.

Chapter 971: Making a Mistake

After waiting for Bluewell to leave, Zhao Hai turned his head to the manager and said that he had some gold bricks to deposit.

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the manager immediately said, “Mister, please come with me.” After that, Zhao Hai went along with the manager.

When Zhao Hai arrived inside the room, he discovered that it was the same as the one in the previous city. It seems like all Magic Armor Banks have similar rooms like this.

Zhao Hai proceeded to put 20 million gold coins worth of gold bricks into the formation. The manager also confirmed that they were worth 20 million. After having the value deposited into his ID card, Zhao Hai proceeded to leave.

After returning to the hotel, Laura said, “Brother Hai, are you really sure about giving Bluewell 5 million gold coins in order to open a factory?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Why not? In any case, we would recoup the money sooner or later. Also, opening this factory would only give us benefits right? And before, we made a huge mistake, it is time for us to correct it.”

When Laura and the others heard this, they couldn’t help but stare. Laura looked at Zhao Hai with a puzzled expression as she asked, “Brother Hai, what mistake?”

Zhao Hai replied, “We made a serious mistake. We thought that after we ascend, it would be impossible for us to return here. However, that only applies to ordinary cultivators. On the other hand, we have the Space. Even if we cannot return, what about the races that are under us? Couldn’t they just return to this place? Is there no material here that the Upper Realm need?”

As soon as Laura and the others heard this, they were immediately surprised. Then their faces seem to show their enlightenment. Indeed, just like Zhao Hai said, they made a mistake.

People from the Cultivation Realm couldn’t return to the lower realms because they were affected by the laws of the heaven and the earth. But to Zhao Hai, this simply wasn’t an issue. It can be said that the Space itself wasn’t something that the heavens can affect. Therefore, after Zhao Hai ascends, as long as they still had the Space’s map, they could return at any time.

Whether it was the Ark Continent, Demon Realm, Divine Realm, or the Atlanta Plane, all of them had good things present. Most importantly, these things would belong to Zhao Hai alone.

In these places, not to say about anything else, how much gold do they have? With more gold, Zhao Hai’s Space could do more things. How much influence could this get in the Cultivation Realm? How much influence would Zhao Hai have? There was no need to express it.

Laura and the others took a deep breath. Then Laura turned to Zhao hai and said, “So what Brother Hai is saying is, the factory would be a preparation for the future?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “The situation with the Magic Armor Continent is special, the Atlanta Plane is special as well. If this lower plane has some way of blocking the underworld, then our 5 million gold coins would be a chess piece that we leave behind. For us, this only brings advantages.”

Laura nodded, “That is indeed a good way to use 5 million. On the contrary, I think it’s too cheap. I don’t know what kind of person this Bluewell is, I hope that he doesn’t betray us.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “He wouldn’t dare. He is only an ordinary person of the Atlanta Plane. He might be intelligent, he might be good at business. However, in the face of absolute strength, all of those cleverness would be a joke. If he dared to play with me, then I could easily kill him.”

Laura also nodded. Just like what Zhao Hai said, not to say about Bluewell, Zhao Hai wasn’t even afraid of the O’Neal family. If Bluewell dared to betray Zhao Hai, then his life would be gone in a blink of an eye.

Zhao Hai looked at the ladies and said, “The Divines have been destroyed by us. It looks like the foreign races wouldn’t join us. And now we’ve left a seed in the Atlanta Plane. Things here have almost been taken care of. Now we’ll go to the underworld. Before, I didn’t dare to go all out against the Skeleton King. But now it’s different. My strength is still the same as before yet am no longer suppressed. We’ll go to the Underworld and see if we can leave something behind there.”

Laura nodded and said, “Indeed. The Underworld is too mysterious. That Skeleton King looks like he isn’t at the apex of the Underworld. Brother Hai, what do you think?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I also feel the same. This is the reason why I’m very interested with the Underworld. As long as we get the Ascension magic armor of the Atlanta Plane, then there’s nothing else we need. At that time, we can go to the Underworld and see what it looks like.”

Laura nodded, then she said, “We also need to pay attention to the Winged Pegasus Clan’s situation. The O’Neal family would discover them by tomorrow. When that time comes, another war would start.”

Zhao Hai thought about it and said, “Alright, let’s call Shan over to the Space.”

When Laura heard this, she chuckled slightly before she turned away to manage things.

Shan has been unhappy in the past few days. His people weren’t cooperating with him. Although they had reached an agreement to enter the Space, the Winged Pegasus were always looking for reasons to drag on. Those who did this the most were the Elder and senior members of the clan. These people disobeyed Speaker Fang, not to say about Shan. Everytime he faced those people, Shan couldn’t help but get furious.

However, Shan didn’t want Zhao Hai to come and handle the matter. He knew that if he called Zhao Hai over, then it’s possible that Zhao Hai would be disappointed and may never involve himself with the Winged Pegasus anymore. For the Winged Pegasus, this would surely be a huge disaster.

Although he was very disappointed with his people, Shan endured for his race. He still had hope for his clansmen.

What made Shan feel depressed was the fact that nobody cared about his efforts. And instead of being grateful, his clansmen even disliked him. It would be impossible for Shan to be happy in this situation.

Shan’s situation now was similar to the time before Zhao Hai killed Yifei. It seems like Zhao Hai killing Yifei caused the Winged Pegasus to resist more. The Winged Pegasus opposed Shan in every decision he made. Even Speaker Fang didn’t enter these people’s eyes, much less Shan.

This day, Shan was inside Speaker Fang’s room, discussing how to solve their clan’s matters. It has been a few days since Zhao Hai left the Winged Pegasus territory, yet there were no movements from their part. The two were getting more and more anxious, but they weren’t strong enough.

At this time, Shan suddenly felt his messenger fish acting up. Shan’s expression changed, he looked at Speaker Fang and forced a smile, “Mister is looking for me. It seems like he’s been discontented with our progress.”

Speaker Fang stared before he smiled bitterly. To be honest, he was also discontented at their current state. In these few days, less than 100 households managed to enter the Space. These households were people who had good relationships with the two of them. As for the others, they simply weren’t willing to move.

Shan took his messenger fish and heard Zhao Hai’s voice, “Shan, Speaker Fang, please go to the Space, I have something to tell you two.”

Shan looked at Speaker Fang, then he took his command token out as the two entered the Space. Upon entering, they discovered that they were standing inside a huge lotus. The two couldn’t help but gawk, but they soon recovered when they saw Fei’er and Ding.

After seeing the two, Zhao Hai immediately said, “Come here and take a seat.” After giving a salute, Shan and Fang walked towards the room where Zhao Hai was.

This wasn’t Zhao Hai’s room inside the ship, instead it was the ship’s reception room. Zhao Hai had some small dishes prepared as well as some bottles of liquor. After the group had a sip of their wine, Zhao Hai turned to Shan and smiled, “How are things going? Are you having hard times recently?”

Shan looked embarrassed at Zhao Hai, he didn’t know how to respond. They certainly weren’t having a good time. Zhao Hai looked at Shan’s expression and faintly smiled, “Don’t worry much about it, I don’t blame you. When I killed Yifei, I’ve already expected this to happen. Don’t be too hard on yourself. I asked you here today because I have something to tell you. In about two days, the O’Neal family’s scouts would discover the entrance to the Winged Pegasus Clan’s Plane.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Shan and Speaker Fang’s expression changed. The two stared at Zhao Hai while Zhao Hai returned their gaze.

Suddenly, Fei’er clapped hard as he said, “Shan, this is good news. You can use this opportunity to compel your people to enter the Space. They didn’t want to enter the Space because they think Mister is lying about the magic armors. Now that the magic armors are coming, those people would know that they’re real. When the time comes, they won’t oppose to moving to the Space. However, things wouldn’t be easy in the beginning. Your people would surely try to face the magic armor. Only after knowing the strength of the magic armors would they be willing to follow your words. You need to be mentally prepared.”

Chapter 972: Can the Underworld Cooperate?

Shan and Fang’s expression were somewhat ugly. They didn’t want to deal with their clansmen using this method. Zhao Hai saw their reaction and couldn’t help but feel disappointed. They were too indecisive, failing to forgo the right thing over a small sacrifice. The most important matter was survival! Shan and Fang were thinking in the mindset of a hero. Not to say being a hero, they didn’t even have the strength to be one.

Yes, Zhao Hai’s plan would kill people. But don’t forget that these people died in order to save a lot more people.

Shan clearly knew this, yet they were still hesitating. Up until this time, they still wanted to bring all of their people into the Space. Who knows if it was because of their naivety, or were they just being stupid.

Zhao Hai shook his head and sighed. Then he looked at Shan and said, “Shan, if given the opportunity, would you kill one person in order to save ten thousand?”

Shan started when he heard this. He himself wasn’t an indecisive person, he even had Zhao Hai kill Yifei before. But these days, his people were not cooperating with him, he was not trusted and was even loathed. This caused him to be mentally affected. Because of this, he wanted to prove himself and bring all of his people into the Space.

It’s possible that Shan didn’t discover this point and was just a subconscious action. Because of this, Shan held some resistance towards Fei’er’s words.

But now that he heard Zhao Hai, he was startled, it seems like he was awakened. Zhao Hai looked at Shan and smiled, “Shan. Don’t forget about your goal. If you hesitate, more people would die. If you don’t agree to the plan, then that’s also fine. I happen to be close to finishing my matters before I ascend. Once I leave, I won’t have any relationship with the Divine Realm anymore.”

Shan stood up, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister can rest assured, I know what I should do. I ask Mister to forgive me for my previous actions. I’ve been lacking in my management.”

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “Shan, you, Fei’er and Ding are the people I like the most in your three clans. The future of your tribes will be handed to the three of you. Let me tell you the truth, there are races other than your clans that I also need to take care of. When I encounter something later on, I won’t have any time to spare for you. I’m not worried about Fei’er, his people have more or less settled themselves. There won’t be any problems for them in the future. At the same time, Ding’s people are doing well. After all, everybody moved in. Even their Patriarch agreed. What I’m most worried about is the Winged Pegasus Clan. They seem to have some dislike towards me. If you can’t manage them, then they would be a potential danger. I don’t want such danger inside my Space. Do you understand?”

Shan bowed and said, “I understand. Mister, feel relieved, I’m clear about what I need to do.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Speaker Fang and said, “Speaker Fang, you’re a great elder of the Winged Pegasus Race. You’re a high-ranking official. And sometimes, you need to be imposing in order to suppress those who disobey you. At this time, Shan’s prestige is still insufficient. He would need your help to manage the future development of the Winged Pegasus Race.”

Speaker Fang stood up, his face showing his guilt as he said, “I’ve been unfair to Mister. I apologize for disappointing you.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “It’s not too late to change. You go back and prepare.”

Shan and Speaker Fang nodded. Zhao Hai waved his hand and sent them back. After the two were sent off, Zhao Hai turned to Fei’er and Ding and said, “Fei’er, Ding, you need to settle your people as soon as possible. Have you seen the churches? You can exchange for things you need there. I’m currently not in the Divine Realm. I went to the Atlanta Plane to see the O’Neal family’s territory. Therefore, I won’t have much time to go see you inside the Space. It is up to you to take care of your people.”

When Fei’er and Ding heard Zhao Hai, they paused for a moment before they said, “Mister, rest assured. There won’t be any problems.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then said, “You won’t suffer any problems in the Space. Here, your lives would only get better and better. Alright, I’ve already told you everything you need to know. I won’t be coming to the Space often so you have to solve your problems on your own. I won’t care about how you handle things from now on.”

Upon hearing this, Fei’er and Ding’s hearts couldn’t help but be moved. They understand that Zhao Hai just gave them his stance. He will not meddle with their clan and would just let them develop on their own.

In the past, Fei’er and the others were worried upon entering the Space. This place was purely Zhao Hai’s domain. If Zhao Hai wanted to do something to them, then they simply won’t have the opportunity to resist.

Zhao Hai drank a few more cups of wine with the two before sending them off. After his visitors left, Zhao Hai returned to his villa where Laura and the others were already waiting for him.

Zhao Hai turned to look at the monitor. The image currently projected was from the O’Neal family’s magic armor troops. They’ve already discovered the rift to the Winged Pegasus Clan.

There were garrison troops stationed on the rift. These troops were reinstated after the nine Supreme Elders retreated. The Winged Pegasus Clan being unwilling to enter the Space was precisely because the nine Supreme Elders already went away.

When the O’Neal family’s people discovered the Winged Pegasus, they didn’t immediately approach. For the O’Neal family, this was a huge discovery. They knew that the family was looking for a large army. Now they had found one.

Most importantly, there was a spatial rift here. The magic armor pilots knew what this meant to the O’Neal family. They even started to suspect that their God was giving special care towards the O’Neal family.

After making their discovery, the O’Neal family’s troops retreated. When he saw their reaction, Zhao Hai slightly smiled. Then he turned to Laura and said, “The O’Neal family is really careful, but this care is the right move. I’m afraid the Winged Pegasus would be faced with huge troubles.”

Laura nodded, “Right, the Winged Pegasus will have huge problems. When we deal with their problem later on, we can proceed to our next plan.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Right, when we solve the Winged Pegasus, we shall proceed to lure the O’Neal family over to the foreign races. Hahaha. To be honest, the O’Neal family is too pitiful. They’re actually doing free labor for us.”

Laura and the others chuckled. At this time, Cai’er suddenly appeared and told Zhao Hai, “Young Master, something is happening to the Underworld’s Dark Mist.”

Zhao Hai quickly changed the monitor to show the dark mist. The moment the image changed, Zhao Hai and the others immediately saw the Underworld’s dark mist violently tumbling. It looked like an angry devil as it whistled and rumbled.

Zhao Hai frowned when he saw the dark mist. He didn’t know what was happening but he knew that this wouldn’t happen for no reason. There should be a reason for this development.

Before long, the answer to Zhao Hai’s question appeared. A team of skeleton soldiers came out along with a bone carriage. Zhao Hai felt relief when he saw this. He knew this group, he had fought with them before.

But then, Zhao Hai became shocked. Behind this team of skeletons was another group.

This new group looked somewhat special. These people were all zombies with thin bodies and pale bones. Their long nails and sharp fangs showed their status.

Just like the skeletons, this group of zombies were also accompanied by a carriage. However, this carriage was actually a zombie carriage. What pulled it were zombies while the carriage itself seemed to be a huge zombie head, complete with its sharp fangs.

The body of the carriage was black, probably made with some unknown beast’s skin. It looked like it wasn’t heavy. It also glowed a green light. When Zhao Hai saw this carriage, his first feeling was that this carriage was made out of corpse skin. This thought scared him a little.

And then, another group of people were trailing behind the zombies. Upon seeing the third group, Zhao Hai immediately thought of the Lich race!

Zhao Hai thought of them because they looked the same as the legendary Lich clan. They seem to have no physical body, they just floated as dark mists. Occasionally, one could see a hand coming out.

In the middle of these Lich was an especially large dark mist. This mist wasn’t smaller than the carriages of the skeletons and the zombies. It seems like this was where the Lich King was.

Zhao Hai frowned when he looked at these three groups. Lich, zombies, and skeletons were the most famous types of undead. However, why would they appear here? What do they want to do?

At this time, the three groups stopped. Then the Skeleton King as well as the Zombie King walked out from the their carriages. The Zombie King was a huge zombie. His height was about two meters, his skin was golden yellow. His muscles were visibly withered, akin to a rotten branch. He had big red eyeballs, 20 centimeter fangs and even longer 50 centimeter nails.

From the lich group, the huge dark mist seem to distort space before it turned into a person wearing a magic robe. In the person’s hand was a book. He had white hair as well as a very neat beard. If one looks at his upper part, then one could see a great literary elder. Unfortunately, his lower body showed his identity. His body didn’t continue on, it was just dark mist.

After the three had come out, the Skeleton King suddenly opened his huge mouth and screamed. Zhao Hai was sure that there wasn’t any sound being heard. Instead, the scream contained spiritual energy and spread all throughout the area.

The Zombie King also did the same and opened its mouth and roared. It was a horrific scream that drilled into the mind of a person.

Those who were looking at the screen were able to hear this roar. Zhao Hai felt uncomfortable while Laura and the others covered their ears. At the back of the undead group, the Lich King knitted his brows.

A moment after the two undead roared, the Lich King said, “Old Bones, Big Tooth, can you not scream? You might not notice, but your voices are too loud and ugly, it’ll scare people. If we want to see civilized people, then we should use civilized means.”

After he said this, the Lich King looked at his surroundings and suddenly said, “Is the Expert who fought the Skeleton King here? If you can hear me, please come out to see us. Rest assured, we came here with no evil intentions.”

Zhao Hai’s group was astonished at what the Lich said. Zhao Hai didn’t expect the Lich to be like this, he couldn’t help but feel strange. And the strangest thing about this was the Lich talked just like Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Laura and said, “Laura, why does this Lich talk a bit like me?”

As soon as Laura and the others heard Zhao Hai, they thought about the Lich’s manner and chuckled. The politeness of this Lich was indeed like Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but shake his head as he said, “I didn’t expect a Lich to have the same temperament as me. Hehe, I’ll go see why they want to meet me.” Then Zhao Hai’s figure moved and appeared in front of the three groups.

Naturally, the Lich didn’t expect Zhao Hai to come out just as he talked. The Lich gawked before he gave Zhao Hai a slight bow, “Lich Kampala has seen Mister.”

Zhao Hai also gave a small bow and said, “I’ve seem Mister Kampala as well as the other two Kings. I was careless last time and wasn’t able to introduce myself, I am Zhao Hai.”

The Skeleton King looked at Zhao Hai, then using his spiritual force he said, “Guli!”

The Zombie King also turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Jiang Zheng!” His voice was somewhat hoarse. It seems like every word took him extreme effort to dictate.

Zhao Hai slightly bowed once more and said, “May I know why you came looking for me? I shouldn’t have anything to do with you. Although I sparred with Mister Guli last time, that was just a matter of learning.”

Lich Kampala looked at Zhao Hai and smiled faintly, “We came looking for Mister in order establish a cooperation.”

When Zhao Hai heard Kampala, he couldn’t help but stare. He looked at the three and asked, “Cooperation? What could I do to cooperate with you?”

Chapter 973: Gu?[1]

Kampala looked at Zhao Hai, then he slightly smiled and said, “I looks like Mister is different from ordinary people. When others see us, they would immediately shout ‘kill them!’. However, Mister didn’t. This makes me surprised.”

Zhao Hai looked at Kampala and chuckled a bit, “This isn’t strange, I’m a Dark Mage so I deal with the undead almost everyday. I’m also used to people yelling ‘kill him’ to me.”

After the three undead heard this, they couldn’t help but stare. Kampala looked at Skeleton Guli and said, “Old Bones, is Mister really the one you fought before? Why didn’t you tell us that he’s a Dark Mage?”

Guli also looked at Zhao Hai and tilted his head. He couldn’t understand what was going on. Zhao Hai just smiled faintly and said, “There’s no need to doubt my identity. I’m a Dark Mage but I’m also a Warrior as well as a Divergent Ability user. Moreover, I can also use magic from other magic branches. This isn’t strange, when you reach my level you would be able to transform your energy to another type. Couldn’t you do it as well?”

The three shook their heads, the Lich looked at Zhao Hai and smiled bitterly, “Mister might not know, but there is only one type of energy in the Dark World and that is dark energy. Because of this, both warriors and mages only use this type.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he replied, “You still haven’t expressed why you called me over.”

When Kampala heard Zhao Hai, he immediately answered, “Mister, we came this time to offer a sincere cooperation. But before we tell you, we’ ll have to little talk with Mister first. Can Mister agree to this?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Of course I agree. Everyone, there’s no need for us to keep standing here. Let’s go take a seat.”

After he said that, Zhao Hai waved his hand, making four stone chairs appear on the ground. Shortly after Zhao Hai went down, Guli and Jiang Zheng sat on the stone chair. On the other hand, Kampala just fluttered which made Zhao Hai slightly smile.

When the group had sat down, Kampala looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, we came here for cooperation because of the spatial rift. The spatial rift is our hope.”

Zhao Hai looked puzzled at the Lich. The Lich returned Zhao Hai’s gaze and smiled bitterly as he said, “Mister, you might have any ideas about the undead living in the Underworld. In fact, at the very beginning, the undead of the Underworld didn’t fight, nobody perished. After all the undead appeared, they just peacefully wandered around the Underworld. This is because we know that we have endless life, so why should we fight? We could live for thousands or tens of thousands of years, or even much longer. Even if we practice a bit every day, we would eventually become masters. Because of this, nobody fought and nobody cultivated voraciously.”

Zhao Hai blankly stared at Kampala. He suspected that this Lich might have gone crazy, the Undead were peaceful? How could darkness lifeforms know peace? It wasn’t like the ghost stories? But to think about it, the Lich was itself a ghost. If he said it, then it might be true.

Kampala looked at Zhao Hai and saw his disbelief. Kampala lightly sighed and said, “Mister, you might think that I’m talking nonsense. But what I said is true. The three of use are one of the longest living undead in the Underworld. I can’t remember how old I am. The only thing I remember is that when I woke up I was a young Lich. i went about the underworld looking for people like me and learned from them. I lived happily, these two did as well. Guli started out as a grey skeleton, Jiang Zheng also started out as a low-level zombie.”

While speaking about this, Kampala had the look of recollection. This was because he could remember the good times. He looked like an old man thinking back to his younger days.

After some time, Kampala sighed. Then he turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “I also don’t know when it started, but undead with memories started to be born. These new undead began to fight against the other undead. These undead killed others and absorbed their energies. This way, these new undead accelerated their cultivation.”

When Zhao Hai heard Kampala, his eyes shone. He looked at the Lich and asked, “You mean that in the beginning, the undead of the Underworld can’t remember anything? They’re just like newborn babies?”

Kampala had a surprised look at Zhao Hai as he said, “Isn’t that natural? Haven’t I told you? Right, I forgot to say it. But this isn’t strage. Shouldn’t undead have no memories to begin with?”

Upon being asked by Kampala, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. But then he began to recall that Kampala was right. Undead weren’t born with memories already in them. Even those summoned by mages won’t have memories of their past life. Only high-level creatures would have memories. It might be because of heaven’s intervention since summoning high-level undead would cause a mage to make a large sacrifice. Naturally, this didn’t include the Space since it was a cheat itself.

After he saw Zhao Hai nod, Kampala continued, “Those undead with memories destroyed the Underworld’s peace. They put an end to the undead’s peaceful life. They wantonly slaughtered the undead and absorbed their energy. Finally, the undead began to resist, making the Underworld a huge battlefield.”

Kampala sighed, then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “You could never imagine how terrible this war is. And because of the battle, more and more powerful undead emerged. What surprised us the most was the sudden emergence of a temple. This temple is surrounded by undead. The undead with memories are the most faithful believers of this temple.”

Kampala looked Zhao Hai in the eyes and said, “It might be fine if it’s just that. However, we discovered that those experts who attacked the temple were all killed, on the other hand, those who came to worship the temple were spared and turned into the temple’s followers. They became fanatics, it’s as though they were under someone’s control.”

Zhao Hai was continually surprised at Kampala. He didn’t think that the undead would be this insightful. It seems like Zhao Hai was still underestimating Kampala and the others.

Kampala seems to ignore Zhao Hai’s expression as he went on, “We aren’t willing to be controlled therefore we united in order to resist the temple. However, their numbers are continually growing. Their power is getting stronger and stronger as well. Fortunately, for every ten undead born in the underworld, only two or three of them would be those with memories. This allowed us to supplement our strength. Otherwise, we would have already perished.”

After talking about this, Kampala looked at Zhao Hai and said, “But even so, we are still being pushed back. Our territory became smaller and smaller. In order to escape elimination, we have no choice but to expand outward. Several times we began attack a plane similar to the Underworld, but we didn’t expect the inhabitants to be very powerful. We were repelled in the end.”

Zhao Hai gawked, then he guessed that the plane Kampala was talking about was the Demon Realm. In the past, the Demon Realm was under attack by undead creatures.

Kampala continued, “After being repelled, our days became even more bleak. But at the same time, we discovered a secret. The reason why the Underworld became like this was because someone was controlling everything behind the scenes. This person was the one who built the Dark Temple. We don’t know who he is, but he is very strong and he wants to be the only God of all undead. Most importantly, he wants the creatures of the Underworld to be as strong as possible. Then he would choose the most powerful undead and take them away from the Underworld to be his most loyal slaves!”

Zhao Hai suddenly thought about a chinese legend. Someone used a jar to raise poisonous insects. These insects would kill each other and the last one alive would be the most powerful insect.

Upon hearing Kampala, it seems like they were in the same state. They were raised inside this jar while being urged to kill each other. Those who killed would become more powerful and the survivors would be the most powerful undead.

Kampala stopped for a moment before he continued, “Although we don’t know where he took those undead, we are very sure that they were taken away. Those undead must have been taken in order to fight stronger enemies. We don’t want to live like that, so we resisted.”

Zhao Hai nodded. To be honest, he really admired the tenacity of Kampala’s group. However, Zhao Hai still didn’t understand where the cooperation would fit into this matter.

It was at this time where Kampala looked at Zhao Hai, his facial expression changed as he said, “Just as we thought that there was no way out, a spatial rift suddenly appeared in the Underworld. That spatial rift brought us great hope.”

As he looked at Kampala, Zhao Hai couldn’t bear it anymore as he asked, “Mister Kampala, until now, I still couldn’t understand the reason why you want my cooperation. Can you get to the point?”

* * *

Means poisonous insects, decided to keep it as is since it has been used in other novels

Chapter 974: So We Cooperate

After hearing Zhao Hai saying this, Kampala couldn’t help but be embarrassed as he laughed and said, “I’m really sorry Mister Zhao Hai. You should know that I’m already old, I have a lot of things to talk about. I apologize.”

Zhao Hai sighed and waved his hand, indicating to the Lich to continue. Kampala immediately followed up, “We found this new land, but there was nobody here. In any case, this didn’t have anything to do with us. All we need is a new place where we can safely live in.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Then you’re lucky. Moreover, there’s no need for my help. The Ark Continent is huge. You can seize it for yourself at any time. There’s nobody here, so you can do whatever you like.”

Kampala smiled bitterly and replied, “We thought like that in the beginning. But then we thought that something was still wrong. We can hide here for a while, but not for long. After all, our enemies still exist. They would be able to discover this place sooner or later. And when they come out of the spatial rift, we would have no other place to escape to.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he also thought about this point. Kampala and the others weren’t stupid. Although this seems easy to think about, most people would overlook this point. They would rather enjoy the safety of the moment rather than think about the incoming future danger.

Then Kampala said, “But what we didn’t expect was Mister taking a batch of Lich with him and agreed to transfer them to another place. For us, this is great news. But unfortunately, after Mister took the group of Lich, you vanished from sight. This caused me to be disappointed.”

When Zhao Hai heard this, he couldn’t help but stare. Then his expression changed as he asked, “Mister Kampala, how did you know that I took a group of Lich with me?”

Kampala proudly replied, “The answer to Mister’s question has to do with the Lich Race’s abilities. Although the Lich don’t have physical attacks, our spiritual force is very strong and we’re the most skillful in using it. When Mister received the Lich, they passed this information over to me. Therefore, I came to know about it. I’ve waited at the place where Mister appeared for a long time. It’s a pity that Mister didn’t appear again.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he suddenly frowned and said, “Wait, Mister Kampala. There’s something wrong with what you said. The Lich I took last time seem to be born with memories. According to you, they should not be in your side. They said that there was still peace in the Underworld, yet you said that there is fighting. What is going on?” Zhao Hai’s eyes were cold as he looked at Kampala.

Kampala sighed and said, “For those people, the Underworld is certainly peaceful. Mister, in the Underworld, not all undead with memories are bad. Some of those undead chose to have an ordinary life. Therefore, they formed an alliance and chose to take a neutral stance in the war. They also took care of other undead who chose to not participate. And since they are strong, no side wants to provoke them. I have a relationship with those Lich that Mister took in, so they decided to tell me the news.”

Zhao Hai nodded, this reason was justified. Then he said, “Mister Kampala, how do you want to cooperate with me?”

Kampala looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, we want to ask you to provide shelter for us. I don’t know if Mister will agree to this?”

When he heard this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but raise an eyebrow, “Mister Kampala, this doesn’t seem to be a cooperation? Does this cooperation just involve me providing shelter for you?”

Kampala smiled awkwardly and said, “Mister. In fact, in the beginning, we want to work with you to deal with those undead. However, we also know that Mister wouldn’t want to wade in those turbid waters, so we didn’t bother asking you this. If Mister accepts us, then it can be regarded as cooperation as well since we will be working for you.”

Zhao Hai gawked, then his expression turned strange as he looked at Kampala, “Mister Kampala, I want to ask why you’d want to work with me to deal with those undead. Do you think I would have that ability?”

Kampala nodded and said, “I believe you have the strength. When you and Old Bones fought last time, it’s clear that you weren’t going all out. Meanwhile, Old Bone used his whole strength. Also, when you took those Lich, I sensed that your ship isn’t normal. The Lich who had a relationship with me even said that he can feel the aura of the Divine Realm from that ship. Because of this, I felt that Mister has the ability to deal with those undead.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think that those Lich that he took were this sensitive. It seems like the Lich were truly skilled in spiritual force, it wasn’t just an exaggerated fact.

When Kampala saw that Zhao Hai was staying silent, he couldn’t help but feel uneasy. He was really afraid that Zhao Hai would refuse him. Zhao Hai looked at Kampala and slightly smiled, “What would happen if I cooperate with you in dealing with those undead?”

Kampala was startled by what he heard, he stared for a moment before he said, “Mister, are you saying the truth? Will you really help us deal with those undead?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and replied, “Right. I want to help you deal with those undead. What do you think? Do you agree?”

Kampala, Guli, and Jiang Zheng looked at each other and could see the surprise on their eyes. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to agree to dealing with the enemy undead.

Kampala looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, why would you want to help us deal with those undead?”

Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “It’s nothing special, I’m just interested in that Dark Temple. I want to see the person behind the scenes.”

Kampala stared, he looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Mister, are you serious about this?”

Zhao Hai slightly smiled, “Of course I’m serious. However, we need to plan this matter carefully. How about we have a few of your friends over and then we’ll discuss. What do you think?”

Kampala asked, “Mister, how are our old friends? Are they doing well?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “They’re doing very well. They’re currently enjoying their time researching magic formations. Except for researching, they don’t need to do anything else. There are no battles, they’re living comfortably.”

Kampala stared at Zhao Hai for some time before he finally said, “Can I see them?”

Zhao Hai knew it’ll come to this point, so he said, “I need to talk to them first to see if they’re willing to come out. They’re currently immersed in their research.”

Kampala lightly frowned and said, “Studying magic formations? Are you sure?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “They aren’t researching ordinary magic formations. Mister Guli should be acquainted with those iron-men. He met them when he came out last time. Those metallic beings are driven by ordinary people and they use complicated magic formations. It’s very deep and mysterious. I had the Lich research those formations. Since the research isn’t easy, they finally found something interesting to do. Because of this, they immersed themselves and placed massive amounts of time towards research. They’ve already reached quite far in their study.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Kampala couldn’t help but nod. Back in the Underworld, the undead simply had nothing to do. If they don’t busy themselves, then they would bore themselves out. In the past, even Kampala was looking for something to do, otherwise he’ll die of boredom.

On the other hand, Guli paid great attention to what Zhao Hai said about the magic armors. He clashed with the O’Neal family before. Although he didn’t suffer any losses, he also wasn’t able to overpower the enemy. Guli’s recollection of that battle was still very profound.

Zhao Hai looked at the group and said, “Everyone, please wait a moment. I want to see if they’re willing to come out.”

For Kampala and the others, time was something they didn’t lack. So they nodded before Zhao Hai’s body flashed back into the Space.

Judging by what he heard so far from Kampala, they didn’t want to be his subordinates. Just like the Thunder Clan and the others, they want to maintain a cooperative relationship with Zhao Hai. However, it was not to the point of being Zhao Hai’s subordinate.

Because of this, Kampala wanted to see the Lich that Zhao Hai took into the Space. However, one must know that those Lich submitted to Zhao Hai. They were willing to become Zhao Hai’s subordinates.

What Kampala didn’t know was that Zhao Hai didn’t like cooperative relationships. For these ‘partners’, Zhao Hai would not be afraid to be impolite. He would certainly make plots against them to make them his own subordinates. On the other hand, regarding his true subordinates, Zhao Hai would give them the same respect that a friend deserved.

When Zhao Hai entered the Space, Laura and the others immediately welcomed him. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Brother Hai, do you really want to deal with those new undead? From what I could hear, the one behind the Dark Temple should be someone from the Culitvation Realm. If that person isn’t Lu Wei, then we would make more enemies in the Culitvation Realm.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I know. Actually, I just said that in order to settle their hearts. After they enter the Space, things would be easier to discuss. And to be honest, I don’t want to ascend in the Underworld. It simply isn’t a good place. They only use dark energy. Also, the one who controls it wanted the undead to kill each other in order to get strong subordinates. Such person wouldn’t be a good friend. If we ascend from there, even if we don’t go against him, he would still fight us. Don’t forget, the ascendants from the Underworld are chosen by that person. Whether he can stop us ascending or not is still left unknown.”

Chapter 975: Charles!

Laura frowned as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, if this is the case, then we can only ascend in the Divine Realm or in the Atlanta Plane.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s still early for us to ascend, so there’s no need to worry about that. We’ll take a look at the Ascension magic armors of the Atlanta Plane first. If it exists, then that would be good. But if it doesn’t, then we could only ascend in the Divine Realm. To be honest, I’d rather ascend in the Divine Realm and meet Lu Wei rather than ascending in the Underworld.”

Laura nodded, “The Underworld is full of dark energy. I believe the person who manages it isn’t good. Brother Hai’s decision is correct.”

Zhao Hai added, “I agreed to helping Kampala and the others because I want to learn more about the Cultivation Realm. So there’s no need to worry about it.”

At this time, the Lich who were taken by Zhao Hai to the Space had arrived. When Zhao Hai went back to the Space, he immediately told Rockhead to call the Lich over.

The Lich quickly arrived, they didn’t waste any time as the group bowed to Zhao Hai. Then their head Lich said, “We’ve seen the Young Master. May I ask what the Young Master needs? If there’s no problem, then we ask the Young Master to send us back to Wild Dragon Island. We still need to study magic formations.”

When Zhao Hai heard the Lich, he smiled faintly and said, “There’s no need focus too much on studying magic formations. I called you over today because an old friend wants to see you. His name is Kampala and he’s outside. When you meet him, tell him about your situation inside the Space.”

The old Lich stared for a moment before he nodded and said, “So it is Kampala. He’s a Lich that is always going against the Dark Temple. He’s very strong and quite knowledgeable. It would be a great thing if he can join us in researching magic formations.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly as he replied, “That would be good, but there’s no need to think about magic formations all the time. Go out and see Kampala’s group with me.” Then he waved his hand as he took the Lich outside.

Kampala was anxiously waiting for Zhao Hai to return. They weren’t afraid of the passage of time before, but now that they were waiting for something significant to their future, they couldn’t help but be nervous.

As undead, Kampala and the others never knew the definition of anxiety. But now, they became acquainted to the feeling. However, they had no way of finding Zhao Hai nor could they urge him to hurry up. They could only wait with anxiety.

It was at this time that Zhao Hai came back. Along with him were the Lich group that he had taken in before.

When Kampala saw these Lich, he quickly went forward with happiness as he greeted the old Lich, “Charles, you really did come out to see me!”

The Charles that Kampala called out was the head of the Lich group. Zhao Hai didn’t bother Charles and Kampala, he just let them be as he stood on the side.

Charles looked at Kampala and said, “Kampala, what matters do you need to see this fellow? Is there a problem that really needs my help? Really, I don’t want to talk nonsense. The Young Master taking you back is your blessing. And if you go, you can still see me. Do you know how busy I am right now? I’ve already cracked half of a magic formation, and now I’ve been interrupted by you.”

Then Charles turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, please take me back. I’ve almost cracked a magic formation, I really couldn’t leave for long. If this fellow doesn’t enter the Space, then leave him here to die. Young Master, I really need to go back now.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile as he looked awkwardly at Kampala. Then he turned to Charles and said, “Alright Charles, you need to have a chat with Kampala. Really, if he didn’t call your name, then I wouldn’t have known.”

Charles gave an embarrassed smile before replying, “Young Master, that isn’t strange. Even I’ve gone close to forgetting my name. Besides Kampala, no other person calls me by my name.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, you two are old friends, so you need to have a  good chat. I wouldn’t disturb you anymore. Right, take this. You should know how to use it. You entertain Kampala and the others. I don’t know how to entertain them.”

Charles looked at the thing that Zhao Hai handed over, it was a command token. Naturally, Charles knew what this token did, so he quickly bowed and said, “Thank you Young Master.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly before his body vanished.

When Zhao Hai vanished, Kampala immediately looked at Charles and said, “Charles, what are you doing? For your Young Master, you just ignored our countless years of friendship?”

Charles looked at Kampala and said, “Kampala, let me say something for you. What kind of days have you been experiencing in the Underworld? I’m sure you know it yourself. The Young Master taking you in would be a blessing for you. Sigh, I have a lot of things to do. And now you disturb my magic formation research.’

Kampala could see that Charles wasn’t lying, however, he still couldn’t help but be shocked as he said, “Charles, your Young Master has left. So there’s no need to go on with this attitude. Why do you need to speak in that tone?”

Charles looked at Kampala, then he suddenly laughed and said, “Kampala, do you think that the Young Master told me to talk like this? No, you’re mistaken, a huge mistake. The Young Master has given us absolute freedom and didn’t control us. He just let us help him in studying magic formations. You wouldn’t imagine how profound the world of magic formations are. If you don’t see it with your own eyes, then you wouldn’t believe me. There are a lot of things that magic formations could do in order to improve our world.”

Kampala looked at Charles as though he saw a monster. He said, “Charles, do you remember the time where we first met?”

When Charles heard this, he couldn’t help but stare. He knit his brows as he asked, “Kampala, are you unwell? Why would you ask me this?”

Kampala’s expression turned cold as he asserted, “Just answer my question.”

Charles looked at Kampala’s face, then his expression couldn’t help but change. His face sank as he said to Kampala, “Are you suspecting me? Good, good. You’re an idiot. You actually doubted my ability? Compared to me, you’re just an idiot, a full-on idiot.”

After hearing the curses coming from Charles’ mouth, Kampala’s expression eased up. Then he looked at Charles and said, “So it is really you. But what is going on with you?”

Charles replied, “What did you say? Are you stupid? Our Lich race is the most spiritually gifted race. You actually suspected me of being controlled? You’re being an idiot. Right, what did you tell the Young Master? Did the Young Master agree to let you into the Space?”

Kampala looked at Charles, he didn’t know whether he should laugh or cry at his words. Then he said, “Don’t joke with me, Charles. Do you really think I’d go into the Space? I just wanted to work with Zhao Hai. He will give us shelter and we help him do things. We are equal.”

When Charles heard Kampala, his expression changed, “You idiot! Did you really say that to the Young Master?”

Upon seeing the drastic change in Charles’ expression, Kampala asked, “Is there something wrong? We’ll treat each other as equals, I don’t want to be his slave.”

Charles clenched his teeth as he scolded, “You utter fool. Do you really think that you’re smart, that you know everything? Do you know the Young Master’s strength? Do you really think that the Young Master was going all out when dealing with Guli? You’re too naive. Let me tell you. Not only did the Young Master conquer the Ark Continent, but he also took the Demon Realm in. At the same time, he eradicated the Divine Race, a race that is similar or even stronger than the Demons. That ship that you saw before was an item from the Cultivation World that the Young Master has snatched from a cultivator. The one in charge of the Underworld’s Dark Temple is also a Cultivator. When the Young Master fought with Guli last time, he didn’t even use a tenth of his power. This is because using more power would push the limits of the plane, causing the Young Master to ascend. And he didn’t want to leave this place in the meantime.”

The reason why Charles knew about this was because he was told by Zhao Hai. And through his mouth, Zhao Hai would be able to express his strength to Kampala and the others, making them feel how powerful Zhao Hai was.

Zhao Hai was very clear that although Kampala said that the previous Underworld was calm, all of those times had long passed. After many years of fighting, Kampala and the others had already bathed themselves in the spirit of battle.

Regarding these types of undead, winning them over by pure discourse was the incorrect way. The only method was to make them respect your strength, only then could they submit.

Sure enough, upon listening to Charles, Kampala’s brows furrowed. Naturally, he doubted Charles, he didn’t believe that Zhao Hai would be that strong.

At this time, Jiang Zhen suddenly said, “Charles, we’re old friends and you have saved us in the past. However, I just cannot believe what you are saying. It seems like Zhao Hai is casually using his own strength, isn’t he afraid of ascending?”

Charles turned to Jiang Zhen and said, “Don’t get too close to me, smelly zombie. I just lazily saved you in order to give Kampala face. You’re underestimating the Young Master. You don’t know, but the Young Master just underwent a huge battle and had conquered the entire Divine Realm. After doing that, he managed to gain a secret technique. This technique can compress the energy inside one’s body. At this time, the energy inside the Young Master’s body is a tenth of what it was before. But even so, his energy’s purity has been improved by ten times. A plane’s rules on ascending pertains to the quantity of energy and doesn’t take into account how pure the energy is. Because of this, the Young Master is no longer worried about suddenly being pushed out and ascending. However, even if he fought you right now, he still wouldn’t need to exert his full force in order to defeat you. At this point, I’m afraid that even the Young Master’s undead would be able to take care of you. There’s no need for him to make a move.”

The reason why Charles spoke to Jiang Zheng was because he knew that Jiang Zheng was also testing him.

When Kampala saw how highly Charles thought about Zhao Hai, he frowned as he asked, “Zhao Hai shouldn’t be that strong. You say he also has an undead army? We also have undead subordinates. Why would we be afraid of him?”

Charles stared upon hearing this, then he laughed and said, “Kampala, I really don’t want to belittle you. But how much undead do you have right now? And how strong are they? If you have truly strong undead, then you wouldn’t have asked Young Master for help.”

Kampala gawked, then his face changed as he snorted and said, “I should have enough to deal with Zhao Hai.”

Charles couldn’t help but laugh louder as he replied, “You really aren’t willing to give up. Let me tell you for your own good. The Young Master has undead surpassing 1 billion. Moreover, each of their strength surpasses a gold skeleton. I couldn’t even calculate how strong all of them are. Now, are you still confident?”

Kampala, Guli, and Jiang Zheng gawked upon hearing Charles. Their expressions failed to mask their disbelief, then Kampala said, “You’re saying that Zhao Hai has more than 1 billion undead? How is that possible?”

Charles sneered and said, “Why would that be impossible? You’re looking at Young Master as though he’s an ordinary person, this in itself is incorrect.”

The three stayed silent, they were now beginning to believe Charles. After seeing their expressions, Charles smiled faintly and said, “I’ll lead you to a place. There, you will understand everything.” Then he took the command token out and stroke it gently. Before long, a spatial rift appeared by his side.

Chapter 976: The Underworld’s Three Big Powers

Kampala looked at the spatial rift before finally deciding to enter. And just as they entered the spatial rift, the Space immediately issued a prompt!

In fact, Charles talked a lot with Kampala because he was allowed to by Zhao Hai. And Zhao Hai also agreed in order to get Kampala and the others into the Space.

Zhao Hai initially wanted to use the Space to directly absorb them. However, it did not succeed. The Space sounded out saying that Kampala and the others were intelligent lifeforms and cannot be forced.

Although Kampala and the others couldn’t be directly absorbed into the Space, they could be deceived in entering. As long as they enter the Space, and by the fact that they were undead, the Space could immediately subdue them.

Sure enough, when Kampala and the others entered the Space, the Space immediately issued a prompt. This prompt was nothing more than the detection of special robots and things like subduing them. Zhao Hai discovered that even if the Space said that they were subdued, then this didn’t mean that they would be fully subservient. This was probably a type of law present inside the Space. Being its own independent space, it had its own laws that would always cater to Zhao Hai’s needs. Anything unfavorable to Zhao Hai couldn’t exist inside.

As Kampala and the others surrendered to the Space, Zhao Hai immediately took them into the Space’s villa. Upon entering the villa, Kampala and the others immediately gave Zhao Hai a salute, “We’ve seen the Young Master.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he waved his hand. After doing that, something about Guli and Jiang Zhen changed. Guli grew flesh, blood, and skin; turning himself into a powerful robust man. On the other hand, Jiang Zheng’s flesh and blood turned into a normal person’s. His skin radiated as though it was ancient bronze. His stature was very thin, his fangs and nails shrank. He looked more like a ordinary man. Meanwhile, Charles and Kampala kept fluttering in the air.

Zhao Hai smiled at the three and said, “Sit down and tell me about the situation of the Underworld. I truly want to deal with the man in the Dark Temple.” Then he turned to Kampala and said, “Kampala, what you said about the Underworld, is it really as you say?”

Kampala nodded and said, “Yes Young Master. If we look at the surface situation, then there are three forces in the Underworld. The first one is the Dark Temple which is now the master of most of the Underworld. Moreover, they’re not just thinking about the Underworld, they are also planning on invading other planes. They’re very difficult to deal with.”

“The second force is us. What people call us is the Rebel Army. We’re resisting the rule of the Dark Temple.”

“The third force is the one Charles and the others belong to. They’re know as the Free Alliance. They are a loose alliance of people who do not want to participate in the war.”

Zhao Hai got to the point, “How many are you in your group? Now that you are in mine, would they disagree? Charles, you too, you’ve been with me for some time. Will the people of your group look for you?”

Kampala shook his head and said, “Young Master can rest assured. Our group is basically a simple collective. We only exist in form and category. Nobody commands anyone and nobody is anyone’s subordinate. It’s probably because of this that we are no match against the Dark Temple.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “That’s good. Later on, bring your men into the Space. If you want to practice, you can do that in the Hell Space. If you don’t, then I can arrange for what you want to do. At this moment, I don’t have the time to deal with the Underworld. After I deal with everything else, I will head to the Underworld.”

Kampala nodded, “Alright. Young Master, the spatial rift to the Ark Continent is located inside my territory. Because of that, others are still unaware of it. If the people from the Dark Temple see it, they will definitely attack the Ark Continent. You need to make preparations.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Rest assured. As soon as they appear in the Ark Continent I will make sure that they wouldn’t be able to return. Kampala, you go out with me first. Call your people over to enter the Space. After that, you can decide on what you want to do.”

Naturally, Kampala didn’t have any objections. And this wasn’t because he was obeying Zhao Hai right now. Even if he was asked this question before, he would still not hesitate to agree. He missed the life before the war. A life like that was what he always wanted.

Just as Kampala said, the spatial rift was placed in his domain. All of the undead here were his subordinates. With one command from Kampala, all of the undead entered the Space.

Upon seeing these undead, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be startled. There were human-shaped undead as well as beast-shaped ones, the human-shaped being the majority. Moreover, their strength wasn’t bad, the number was nothing to scoff at either. This was out of Zhao Hai’s expectation.

But after taking the undead into the Space, Zhao Hai immediately put them back and let them roam around the dark mist. This way, once the other forces notice the spatial rift, Zhao Hai would be informed.

.Kampala already told Zhao Hai that the undead creatures of the Underworld were very sensitive when it came to the Dark Mist. Although there were a lot of Dark Mists in the Underworld, as long as it expands to the Ark Continent, the other undead would eventually find out. When that time comes, they would surely come.

Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about this matter. He had Kampala’s people go back into the Dark Mist just for monitoring. They weren’t there to block the enemies from attacking the Ark Continent.

After taking care of Kampala’s matter, Zhao Hai returned to Yanking city. Bluewell was still busy with the factory so Zhao Hai was currently idle. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t have any matters to attend to after returning.

During the day, Zhao Hai brought Laura and the others all throughout the city. They bought everything they saw that was interesting. As for the remaining time, they made sure to understand the underlying matters of the Atlanta Plane. At the same time, Zhao Hai was also paying attention to the Winged Pegasus Clan’s situation.

Soon after the O’Neal family discovered the spatial rift to the Winged Pegasus, they began to act. However, it was clear that the O’Neal family were being very careful. They didn’t immediately begin their attack. Instead, they made sure to have everything prepared before they commence.

Zhao Hai didn’t find anything wrong with the O’Neal family’s movements. Everything was under his expectations. The better they handle things, the more pressure the Winged Pegasus would feel.

Time unknowingly passed for three days. On this day, Zhao Hai just had his breakfast and was preparing to leave with the ladies. But then, Bluewell suddenly arrived. Bluewell was dressed nearly. Although his eyes were blood red, his hair was combed well and one could see the vigorous energy coming from his body.

Upon seeing Bluewell’s appearance, Zhao Hai immediately said, “What happened? You seem to be very happy.”

Bluewell passionately nodded as he said, “Yes Mister, I’m very happy. The company’s registration went very smoothly. Presently, the company has been registered.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “That’s good. The next step is to choose the location of the factory. Do you have any ideas?”

Bluewell smiled faintly and said, “I’ve already chosen a place. Although it would need a bit of effort to set up the place, it would be a good location once everything is done.”

Zhao Hai smiled and replied, “Alright, let’s go and have a look at it.”

Bluewell nodded, then he led Zhao Hai and the others to leave the hotel. Zhao Hai didn’t let the hotel arrange a vehicle for them. Instead, they rode Zhao Hai’s RV towards the southeastern part of Yanking City.

Before long, Zhao Hai and the others reached the outskirts of Yanking City. At this place, a river flowed through Yanking City. The surface of the river was very wide and it was the most important aquatic location of the region. It can be said that Yanking City’s big factories were centralized nearby this river, taking full advantage of its transport capabilities.

Zhao Hai went all around the city in the past few days, so naturally he was well acquainted with this river. He even rented a ship and went upstream. Although it was for the sake of playing around, it also doubled as a tour to see the factories in the city.

One has to recognize that the factories of Yanking City were really good. After a few days of observation, Zhao Hai was sure that these factories were working for the O’Neal family, producing a large number of magic armors for them. Parts of magic armors as well as energy converters were going out of this place. All of which were very important for the O’Neal family.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t make a move on them. The O’Neal family still had great use for him. Even if he wanted to deal with the O’Neal family, he would have to wait until later on.

After seeing where Bluewell was taking him, Zhao Hai gently furrowed his brow and said, “Bluewell, are you leading us to Wolf Fang Mountain?”

Wolf Fang Mountain was located south of Yanking City’s East District. It was different compared to the densely forested mountains. Wolf Fang Mountain was famous as being a huge chunk of stone. Moreover, it had a strangely structured stone forest that interlaced with one another. Although the mountain was on the edge of the river, it would take a lot of resources before it could be used.

Bluewell nodded and said, “We’re heading towards Wolf Fang Mountain. Moreover, I’m planning on opening our factory there.”

Upon hearing Bluewell, Zhao Hai knit his brows, “I have seen Wolf Fang Mountain. If we want to transform the mountain, then wouldn’t we need to pay a lot of money?”

Note: I’l be going back to the old format. This one is more tiring to do xd

Chapter 977: Wolf Fang Mountain Is Yours

Bluewell smiled faintly and said, “Actually, everyone has been deceived by the mountain’s outside appearance. I’ve analyzed Wolf Fang Mountain and discovered that we wouldn’t need too much money in order to transform it. Compared to its geological value, the cost could practically be ignored.”

Zhao Hai asked, “Deceived? Tell me.”

Bluewell answered, “As you know, I’m quite the ambitious person. And just like the opportunity you gave me, I also looked for opportunities in Wolf Fang Mountain. In the end, I’ve reached an astonishing conclusion. Wolf Fang Mountain isn’t as awful as it seems on the surface.” After he said that, Bluewell took a blueprint from his bag, then he laid it down on the table.

Zhao Hai glanced at the blueprint and found that it was a map of Wolf Fang Mountain. Moreover, this map was a bird’s-eye view.

Bluewell pointed at a dot on the map and said, “Mister look. Although the structures of Wolf Fang Mountain looked chaotic, but in fact it followed some rules. If we remove some stones from this place, clean it up and build our factory, we can establish a pathway here. This way, Wolf Fang Mountain would become a proper location. We don’t need to care about the other rocks.”

Zhao Hai looked at the place Bluewell pointed to. At the same time, he tried to picture it inside his head. He found out that if they clean up the rocks that Bluewell pointed out, then a factory would be constructed in Wolf Fang Mountain. The remaining rocks wouldn’t provide any obstructions whatsoever. On the contrary, they would become natural decorations for the factory.

Zhao Hai turned to look at Bluewell and said, “Alright. How is the money? Is it enough? If you lack money, then don’t hesitate to approach me.”

Bluewell smiled and said, “It’s enough. You don’t have to worry. At this moment, Wolf Fang Mountain is yours. I bought Wolf Fang Mountain under your name. The entire mountain only cost us 100 thousand gold coins. It is too cheap.”

This caused Zhao Hai to raise an eyebrow, he looked at Bluewell and asked, “Why did you buy the entire mountain?”

Bluewell smiled and said, “Mister, you don’t know but there is a regulation in Yanking City which states that those who buy land here would have tax concessions. Also, once our company develops in the future and others see it, what would happen to Wolf Fang Mountain? But since we’ve bought the entire mountain, they would have no way to come here anymore.”

Zhao Hai nodded, Bluewell had thought this matter through, then he said, “Then let’s do it according to your plan. Remember, if you need money, don’t hesitate to ask me. Alright, let’s head back. You go take a good rest. I’ve already left everything about the factory to you. I don’t want you to be exhausted. When that time comes, I would have a hard time finding someone to replace you.”

Bluewell smiled faintly and didn’t say anything else. To be honest, the recent days have been the most tiring he’s ever had. However, it was also the happiest days in his life. He finally found an opportunity to use his abilities. This feeling made him feel intoxicated.

Zhao Hai looked at Bluewell’s expression and smiled, “I have nothing else to say. Men aren’t like women. Being overly caring about you would be too excessive.”

It might be unthinkable, but these few words could already express Zhao Hai’s concern.

Zhao Hai was such a person. He already settled on Bluewell and didn’t want Bluewell to disappoint him. Because of this, he would naturally care for Bluewell’s health. After all, Bluewell wasn’t from the Ark Continent. His cultivation wasn’t as advanced as Zhao Hai and the others.

After the group returned to their hotel, Bluewell proceeded to leave. On the other hand, Zhao Hai returned to the Space. This was because Cai’er just told him that the O’Neal family had began to make their move.

Zhao Hai sat on his sofa while looking at the O’Neal family army in the monitor. The O’Neal family’s army could be described as a mighty wave of iron and steel. Their war tanks and cannons were travelling end to end. Not to say about the Winged Pegasus, even the Divines would feel pressure in face of this army.

When he saw the O’Neal family’s army, Zhao Hai actually smiled. Then he turned to Laura and said, “What do you think? The O’neal family’s army is starting to move. How long do you think the Winged Pegasus would last?”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “I reckon the Winged Pegasus garrison wouldn’t be able to defend the spatial rift for even a day. You should be aware of how strong the O’Neal family’s magic armors are. A magic armor army could face a Divine Supreme Elder with their combat suits on. Additionally, the O’Neal family also has their war tanks and powerful cannons, all of them are capable of strong attacks.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, keep a comprehensive record on the O’Neal family’s actions. We’ll take a look at it and see how strong their army truly is.”

Cai’er complied. For Cai’er, taking record was a very simple matter. As long as the made intention with her mind, then it was already enough. But as for the analysis of the O’Neal family’s army, Cai’er wouldn’t be able to do it, she would need the Universal Scanner’s help to do so.

Zhao Hai looked at the O’Neal family’s army and made some calculations. Then he said, “Alright, they should arrive at the Winged Pegasus Clan’s defensive line by tomorrow. Let’s go take a rest and see how it plays out after we wake up.”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “Alright, I also want to see how the O’Neal family plans to attack.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I’ll also head back to the Space and see what how Guli and the others are doing.”

After receiving Guli and the others, Zhao Hai asked them to lead all of the undead in the Space. What surprised Zhao Hai was the fact that they didn’t dare to make commands towards Qinfeng and Mingyue.

Zhao Hai knew Qingfeng and Mingyue’s identities, he just didn’t know how strong they actually were. Apparently, they’re powerful enough that the ancient undead couldn’t command them.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t take this to heart. It didn’t matter whether Guli and the others could command them or not. As long as they are loyal to him, then it’s already fine. Besides Guli and Jiang Zheng commanding the undead, Kampala was with Charles researching magic formations. After looking at Kampala’s appearance, it seems like he was also entranced by research.

Then Zhao Hai went to the Hell Space to see Guli and the others. Since they had good experience, they were able to easily adapt to life in the Hell Space. The environment was the same as the Underworld, so cultivating here would be similar to cultivating in the Underworld.

Zhao Hai also asked Guli and the others if they had something else they wanted to do, or would they be like Kampala, researching magic formations. Unfortunately, they didn’t want to do anything else.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t force Guli and the others. In fact, what these undead wanted to do was to cultivate. For Zhao Hai, this was also good. The stronger they are, the more advantageous it would be for him.Therefore, Zhao Hai had no reason to disagree.

Everything looked very normal, Wild Dragon Island’s research was also progressing smoothly. Because of this, Zhao Hai felt great relief.

The next morning, Zhao Hai and the others got up early. Today, they didn’t stay inside the hotel. Instead, they rode their RV and went outside. After finding a place with little people, they stopped and then entered the Space. They were going to see a play.

Before long, the O’Neal family’s army train could be seen. It was quite obvious that they had stopped for the night to take a rest. This morning, they would be able to arrive at the Winged Pegasus Clan’s defensive line.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Laura and said, “Let’s call Shan and tell them about the situation. Let them prepare.”

Laura nodded, then she took her messenger fish out as Zhao Hai said, “Shan, Shan, can you hear me?”

Shan’s voice was quickly heard, “Mister, I can hear you. What do you need?”

Zhao Hai held the messenger fish as he smiled faintly and said, “I don’t have anything I need, I just want to tell you that by 9 o’clock in the morning, the O’Neal family would arrive at your spatial rift. You need to prepare well.”

Shan went silent for a while, then after some time he said, “Alright, Mister. Rest assured, I know what to do.”

Zhao Hai gave an affirmation before he took his messenger fish down. Then he turned to Laura and said, “Laura, do you think that me not helping the Winged Pegasus Clan is the right decision? Why do I feel that Shan’s mood sank when I hung up?”

Laura nodded, “It’s true. But Brother Hai, you don’t have to worry about it. You should know the situation with the Winged Pegasus Clan. If you help them all the time, then they won’t be able to learn.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “This is their last opportunity. If they still hesitate, then I’m afraid I’d have to give up on them, including Shan.”

Lizzy suddenly interjected, “Big Brother Hai, I think we should also tell the situation to Fei’er and the others. In any case, we could probably trust them now.”

Zhao Hai though for a moment before he shook his head, “Forget it, let’s not tell them for now. Even the Demons don’t know much about the secrets of the Space.”

Lizzy nodded and didn’t say anything else. As for the secrets of the Space, the less people know, the better. Although these people were already inside the Space and couldn’t leave, Zhao Hai still needed to keep the Space’s secrets to his own.

Sure enough, just like Zhao Hai said, the O’Neal family arrived at the Winged Pegasus Clan’s spatial rift at about 9 o’clock in the morning. The huge army’s advance caused dust to fly dozens of meters in the air. Naturally, it was impossible to hide their movements from the garrison troops of the spatial rift. All a sudden, the atmosphere of the defensive line turned anxious.

The O’Neal family also didn’t intend to hide their advance. They knew that they couldn’t approach silently. Therefore, they made a huge approach towards the defensive line. Instead of being silent, they might as well exert the strongest pressure they can!

Chapter 978: Start of the Attack

Pressuring people using brute force might be the stupidest method, but sometimes, it was the most effective approach. If one describes this method in just a few words, then it would be ‘If one’s sword is big enough, then one wouldn’t need to make a move!’

There was once a discussion with regards to ancient weaponry. There were a lot of weapons in the old times, and debates happened as to which one was the most powerful. However, it was an undeniable fact that heavy weapons were the most mighty! Take a mace for example, no matter what shield one uses to defend, the person behind it would still be broken upon meeting a heavy mace.

The O’Neal family was using this exact method. They were using the brute aura of their formidable military. They didn’t use any tactics for war, they were straight-up instilling pressure on the enemy. They wanted to make it known that they were unstoppable.

In face of absolute strength, schemes and tactics were no more than clown tricks. Naturally, the O’Neal family was clear about this point. This time, they showcased their enormous force in order to deal with the Winged Pegasus Clan.

Zhao Hai was looking at the monitor since he was still interested in what the O’Neal family wanted to do. At this time, Megan suddenly sighed and said, “I think I now understand why the O’Neal family didn’t pursue the undead upon seeing them. And why they are showing their huge firepower today.”

Zhao Hai was confused at what Megan said, so he asked, “Oh, why is that?”

Megan smiled faintly and said, “After thinking about it, it is because of you, Big Brother Hai. When you first met Axe, you didn’t tell him the real situation of the Ark Continent. Because of this, Axe always thought that there’s nothing wrong in the Ark Continent. Additionally, you told them that the continent’s strongest person was only 9th rank. This caused them to be certain on their invasion. But when they came to the Ark Continent, they discovered that the Ark Continent was already devoid of people. Then they found out about the Dark Mist as well as the Demon Realm. Since the Dark Mist is full of undead, they couldn’t just go in. And then, there is also nobody in the Demon Realm. Not to say friends, there weren’t any enemies to speak of. At this moment, they are very eager to find people to understand what happened in the Ark Continent. So when they discovered the Winged Pegasus, they couldn’t just let go of the opportunity.”

When Zhao Hai and the others heard what Megan said, they all nodded. They also thought that Megan was right. Megan looked at the group and continued, “Also, in the process of fighting the undead, the O’Neal family wasn’t able to gain any advantages. This greatly affected their morale. Therefore, they are badly thirsting for a taste of victory in order to increase the family’s morale. This time, they need to be successful in dealing with the Winged Pegasus, they are not allowed to fail.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That is very reasonable. But this is much better. Hahaha. I want to see the reaction of the Winged Pegasus when they see the O’Neal family’s attack.”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “I reckon the O’Neal family would use the same tactic they used to enter the Taurus Continent. Their cannons would attack first before their war tanks and magic armors go in at the same time.”

Zhao Hai agreed, “Although this method is too straightforward, but you have to recognize that this is the most suited method for the O’Neal family.”

The others nodded. At this time, the O’Neal family had already set-up the nearly thousand cannons that they brought. They didn’t hide anything as they postured outside the Winged Pegasus Clan’s spatial rift. Even those positioned in the spatial rift’s defensive line could see the actions made by the O’Neal family.

Despise, this was contempt shown towards the defenders. The Winged Pegasus defenders became angry. Before long, a team of ten thousand Winged Pegasus Cavalry rushed out from the defensive line and proceeded to attack the O’Neal family’s cannon positions.

There were a lot of soldiers in the defensive line who had seen the O’Neal family before. They were clear about how powerful these cannons were. So in this attack, besides teaching the O’Neal family a lesson, they wanted to destroy those cannons.

However, even if intentions were good, reality was cruel. To go against the small team of Winged Pegasus Cavalry, the O’Neal family sent 500 of their magic armors. These magic armors went straight towards the cavalry. The Winged Pegasus were surprised to see that the speed they were so proud of didn’t seem to be a problem for these huge metallic men.

The 500 magic armors were like 500 arrows that were fired towards the Winged Pegasus Cavalry. But since the Winged Pegasus Cavalry had rich battle experience, they immediately made a response. They began their counter-attack by taking out the blood lightning javelins that they acquired from Zhao Hai.

However, the cavalry still lacked experience when dealing with the magic armors. They still lacked the perfect timing. Just as they took their javelins out, the magic armors didn’t wait and immediately fired their bombs. The bombs directly hit the team of Winged Pegasus riders. Almost immediately, almost a thousand cavalry units were killed off. This shows how overbearing the bombs were.

Just as the Winged Pegasus were plunged in chaos, the magic armors rushed towards them. Energy beams shot out in succession. Every time an energy beam flashed, a Winged Pegasus would die.

The two actions made by the magic armor team took several thousand lives from the ten thousand unit troop. The Winged Pegasus army almost immediately collapsed.

At this time, it can be said that the Winged Pegasus soldiers had been lax. Shan and the others wanted the clan to move. However, those in higher position of the clan were afraid that Zhao Hai would clean them up. Therefore, the ordinary people were left with not knowing what to do.

However, it was clear that they were disobeying. They said that they would walk but they were actually going slow to the point of never moving. Moreover, the ongoing contradictions between Shan and the higher-ranked winged Pegasus caused the undercurrent of the clan to turn chaotic. This caused the army to be confused. In this case, how could the soldiers possible do their best in order to fight the enemy.

Because of their low fighting spirit, the army weren’t very willing to fight. Therefore, they could only wait to be slaughtered by the united O’Neal family army.

In the clash between the ten thousand Winged Pegasus and the 500 magic armors, the Winged Pegasus Clan suffered 7 thousand losses while the O’Neal family didn’t even lose one. This contrast was truly disproportionate.

After repelling the attack of the Winged Pegasus clan, the cannons have also finished being set-up. A thousand cannons were on standby, waiting for an order to fire.

And with Axe’s command, a thousand cannons howled as they fired their projectiles towards the Winged Pegasus clan’s defensive line.

A thousand cannons indiscriminately attacked the area in and around the defensive line. One could imagine how lethal the attack was. The entire defensive line of the Winged Pegasus was almost erased from the map.

The cannons didn’t just stop after one volley, instead they continued until they fired ten times. The Winged Pegasus Clan’s defensive line was cleared after the fifth volley. At this point, it was already impossible for the Winged Pegasus clan to resist.

After ten rounds of cannon fire, the defensive line of the Winged Pegasus clan had completely changed in appearance. The high walls have fallen and craters could be seen everywhere. Bodies of dead soldiers were strewn everywhere. Even those who were lucky enough to survive couldn’t help but stare at the battlefield with a dull look. They were completely terrified.

However, this wasn’t the end. The O’Neal family’s war tanks and magic armors proceeded to advance.

At this time, the mentally-weakened Winged Pegasus soldiers have already turned around and ran away. There were also those whose mind had completely collapsed. They began running around the battlefield. The scene was just like the end of the world.

Zhao Hai looked at the defensive line and sighed, “I didn’t think that it would be this quick. The Winged Pegasus retreated in less than three hours. Three hours, in that span of time, the defensive line was destroyed.”

Laura and the others sighed as well. In fact, this event made it clear to them how strong the O’Neal family really was. Such fighting strength was truly terrifying.

Zhao Hai turned his head and said, “Laura, report this matter to Shan. Meg, please make us some food, it’s time for lunch.”

Meg nodded before she turned around and went to the kitchen. On the other hand, Laura took out her messenger fish and told Shan about the defensive line’s situation. Upon hearing this, Shan was extremely shocked. If not for Zhao Hai being the one who said this, he wouldn’t have believed it.

It didn’t take a long time before the O’Neal family’s army seized the defensive line. They didn’t immediately advance towards the rift. Instead, they set up a defense and repaired the destroyed structures.

To be honest, Axe didn’t expect their operation to be this smooth. They didn’t think that the enemy would fall this quickly.

Although their attack towards the Taurus Continent also went smoothly, Axe understood that it was because their enemy gave up on the place. Therefore, that accomplishment could be said to be negligible.

But this time, the enemy even clashed with their army. There was a large number of enemies in the defensive line as well. However, this huge number of troops had actually been eliminated by them.

Axe was somewhat surprised regarding the Winged Pegasus clan. He didn’t expect these people to be weak! They were too weak!

They were able to fight some of the undead that they met before. Whether it was in attack or defense, these undead were much stronger than the Winged Pegasus Clan. Axe always thought that the Winged Pegasus had the same combat power as the undead. However, it turned out that the Winged Pegasus clan was much worse than the undead.

George stood next to Axe. He looked at the battlefield with an excited expression. He found that he was really lucky. He didn’t think that the attack would go this smoothly. Also, he didn’t even think that Axe would be heading today’s attack.

Although Axe was the O’Neal family’s Young Lord, he didn’t have any military achievements nor did he participate in previous wars. Because of this, his commanding skill wasn’t very good. Now that the O’Neal family had focused its efforts on this place, it’s understandable if the family didn’t assign Axe to lead the advance army. But who would’ve thought that the O’Neal Patriarch would actually appoint Axe as the chief commander of this battle. This exact decision made it possible for George to gain face in front of Axe.

Although George made a very good battle plan back during their initial entrance towards the Taurus Continent, that battle plan was ultimately rendered useless. Although this was still an important event to Axe, George thought that he could do better. He thought that if there were enemies at that time, then he would be able to decimate them all.

And in this attack, the plan that he did went very successfully. This was the reason why George was excited.

While George was indulging in his happiness, Axe suddenly said, “George, well done. Your battle plan is very effective. Good, very good.”

George quickly replied, “I thank the Young Lord for the praise. However, I don’t dare to take all of the credit. This subordinate’s accomplishment is all because of the Young Lord. If the Young Lord didn’t allow me, then i wouldn’t have been able to make the battle plan.”

Everybody liked to listen to flattery, especially someone as young as Axe. Because of this, upon hearing George, Axe couldn’t help but laugh. At the same time, he repeatedly patted George’s shoulders.

When Zhao Hai heard Axe and George’s dialog, he turned to Laura and said, “This George is truly talented. He has the making of a good official.”

Laura smiled and said, “I wonder how they would react if they know that everything is because of Brother Hai’s arrangements.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “I believe their expressions would be splendid. Right, Cai’er, those Warriors we met in the O’Neal family’s territory, did you pay attention to them? What are they doing now? If there are any troubles in the O’Neal family’s backyard, then I think we should help them to deal with it. After all, having these free workers is very good.”

As soon as they heard Zhao Hai, Laura and the others chuckled. Cai’er also smiled and said, “Young Master, rest assured. As long as the Young Master needs it, I can get the recordings over the last few days and have it analyzed.”

Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “Forget it, let’s leave them be for now. The O’Neal family didn’t become a superpower of the Magic Armor continent by being easily dealt with. We don’t have to worry about them in the meantime.”

Chapter 979: Shan’s Anger!

Shan stared as he sat opposite Speaker Fang. Winged Pegasus Fang was also able to hear the dialogue between Zhao Hai and Shan. When Speaker Fang heard it, his expression changed. He didn’t expect the enemy to progress this quickly.

Boom! Shan crushed the table in front of him. Shan raged with his blood red eyes, he said, “Too much, it’s too much!”

Speaker Fang smiled faintly and said, “It’s a bit too much. Mister Zhao Hai is clearly on the scene, yet he didn’t spare any help. It’s too much.”

Shan looked at Speaker Fang and said, “You say that Mister is too much? Didn’t he already gave us a warning? Didn’t he already arrange an escape route for us? All the things that Mister did, aren’t they all good for us? If I were Mister, I would have long ignored our clan. How could it be possible for Mister to be excessive? The ones who are being too excessive are those people from the clan. Look at them, they really think that Mister regards them as important. Without Mister, let’s see what would happen to those bastards. They are the reason why the Winged Pegasus reached this point and lost too many people!”

Speaker Fang didn’t think that Shan would say so. However, he quickly changed his mind. As Shan said, Zhao Hai had already arranged everything for them. It’s just that they didn’t go into the road that Zhao Hai prepared.

Shan looked at Speaker Fang and said, “Speaker, did you ever think that if we go on like this, then Mister would get angry at us? If Mister decides to give up on the Winged Pegasus Clan, then what kind of situation would we be in?”

When Speaker Fang heard this, he couldn’t help but stare. Then his expression changed. He was very clear about what would happen if Zhao Hai decides to give up on them. Even without the O’Neal family, the Winged Pegasus would still be in a terrible situation. After all, the Winged Pegasus wasn’t a very strong race. If Zhao Hai did leave them behind, then once the foreign races decides to do something to them, then the Winged Pegasus would have no way to fight back.

Don’t talk about the foreign races, even the O’Neal family outside was too strong for the Winged Pegasus Clan. They simply had no way to resist the magic armors. In this case, the only thing they could do was to follow Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai’s method might be overbearing, but one has to recognize that his intention was sincere. If they didn’t accept his goodwill, then that would be their problem.

Shan looked at Speaker Fang and knew that his thought had gone through. Shan said, “Speaker, what we need to do right now is to send our clan to the Space as soon as possible. But before we do that, we need to have our people feel gratitude towards Mister.”

Speaker Fang looked confused at Shan, “Why? Mister didn’t request our people to feel that way towards him. As long as our people enter the Space, then it would be fine.”

Shan coldly snorted and said, “Speaker, you’re being naive. Mister is intimate with the Thunder Clan as well as the Barbarians. This is because the remaining Thunder Clan members are close to Fei’er. Fei’er chose to go against his Patriarch and bring his people into the Space. At the same time, all of the Barbarians willingly entered the Space, which was something Mister wanted to see. Because of this, he would certainly look at the Barbarians in a positive light. On the other hand, what did the Winged Pegasus Clan do? Among the three clans, the one being the most arrogant towards Mister is us. Later on, we agreed to move towards the Space but we broke this promise. Let me ask you, if you were Mister, would you still forgive those guys? Does the Winged Pegasus Clan have any use for Mister? Is there any reason for Mister to save us?”

Speaker Fang didn’t make any noise. He knew that Shan was telling the truth. However, he still wanted to know why the people needed to be grateful towards Zhao Hai.

Shan took a deep breath before continuing, “Our people have already offended Mister. The two messages that Mister said could be taken as warnings. If our people keep offending him, then it wouldn’t be easy for us to ask him for help. But Mister is a person who heavily values sentiment. As long as our people feel grateful and respectful to Mister, he surely wouldn’t be cruel enough to overlook our distress. Also, Speaker, don’t forget, we will be entering Mister’s Space. If our people are still disrespectful, then Mister might destroy our clan. I’m afraid we need to change our people’s minds.”

As soon as Speaker Fang heard this, his expression truly changed. He was very clear about how true Shan’s words were. If things were just like how Shan said, then if their people don’t respect Zhao Hai, then even if they enter the Space, they would still be destroyed by Zhao Hai sooner or later.

After thinking about this, Speaker Fang let out a long breath as he nodded and said, “Alright, let’s go according to what you say. How do you want to do it?”

Shan sneered and said, “Didn’t these people think they are strong? Didn’t they believe that Mister is deceiving them? Alright, then let’s have them taste the O’Neal family’s cannons. Perhaps they might regret their decisions in time. They will come to understand how much Mister has done for us.” Speaker Fang gawked when he heard this. But in the end he still nodded. He can understand Shan. It seems like Shan has decided to deal with those people who weren’t obedient.

Speaker Fang looked at Shan and said, “So what do we do next?”

Shan smiled faintly and asid, “Let’s turn the tables around. We’ll wait here. Aren’t they strong? I still remember what they said. I will learn from their actions. Since they decided to drag on, then I will also delay.”

Speaker Fang knit his brows and said, “But if we do that, a lot of people will die.”

Shan coldly snorted and said, “It’s a disaster that they brought onto themselves. To be honest, I’m tired of calling them my clansmen. I intended to help them since they are my people, but what did they do? When I needed their cooperation, where were they? I just want our people to be safe. If they aren’t taught a lesson, then they will never know what the real world is.”

Speaker Fang sighed. He didn’t say anything. He also knew the suffering that Shan experienced. To be honest, even his own heart was being suffocated. His clansmen really did go too far.

Shan looked at Speaker Fang and then turned his head and gave a command, “Come clean the room and bring a new table in.” Someone outside the door immediately responded. Then two people came in to clean the place as well as bring a new table. After which they promptly left.

These two people were Speaker Fang’s loyal subordinates. They were now the only ones that Shan can trust. Only these people were willing to work for Shan.

At this point, the clan had blocked Shan out completely. His clansmen wouldn’t listen to any of his words, nobody even came to talk to him. Moreover, their people didn’t even provide Shan with any living supplies. If not for the stockpiles in the mansion, Shan would have already starved.

Upon facing this situation, even if Shan was a well-tempered person, he would still be angered. His purpose was for the betterment of the clan, but they actually treated him in such a matter. How could Shan not be angry.

After the place has been tidied up, Shan suddenly turned to Speaker Fang and said, “Speaker, let’s go to the Space. I’m sure Fei’er and the others have been eating well. In the past few days, we’ve been eating quite poorly. We haven’t had proper sleep as well. I’ve almost turned mad by our clansmen. Now let’s see who has the right to be angry next time.”

Speaker Fang also wanted to relax. In any case, things have already developed to this point, doing anything else would be useless. Because of this, Speaker Fang quickly nodded and said, “Alright, let’s go. I hope Fei’er left some good wine for us. I have to say, Mister’s wines are very delicious.”

When Shan heard this, he couldn’t help but laugh. Then he took his command token out and waved his hand before entering the Space.

At this time, Fei’er was incomparably relaxed. The Space’s environment was fantastic. Even if you lie down at home all the time, nobody would stop you. As long as you find some food outside, you will never be hungry. Moreover, the Space had its own way of dealing with criminals. This caused the people inside to be free of worry.

Originally, Fei’er thought that nothing would change upon entering the Space. If he wanted to manage the clan, then he would still have to spend a lot of effort. However, he found that he was overthinking after entering the Space. The environment here was good, far from his imagination. It was precisely because of this environment that Fei’er’s life had gone smoothly. He suddenly found that managing the clan had become much easier.

Although Fei’er can’t taste the feeling of power now, it wasn’t important to him. What Fei’er wanted to see was his people living good lives like this. This kind of life was really good for his people.

Inside the Space, people wouldn’t have to be afraid of having ambition. In fact, having ambition was very good. If you want to live as an emperor, then you can as long as you exchange enough things to the churches. You can get anything that you want. There were even things that they haven’t seen or heard about before.

Fei’er’s life was very simple. He would cultivate everyday, then he would either collect food, research magic formations, study potions and so on. Everyday was spent in ease, but it was very fulfilling. Fei’er was very satisfied with this life.

The only sole worry that Fei’er had was Shan. Fei’er can understand Shan’s situation, so he couldn’t help but worry.

Fei’er thinks that Zhao Hai understood as well. Zhao Hai let the Thunder Clan into the Space when they were about to be killed off. Moreover, he kept his promise of not interfering. But with how the Winged Pegasus did things, what would Zhao Hai’s reaction be? Because of this, Fei’er felt nervous about Shan’s situation.

Chapter 980: Fenglei’s Regret

Fei’er was currently inside his room reading. Then suddenly, someone’s voice came in from outside, “Fei’er, are you in? Let’s have a drink.”

Upon hearing that it was Shan, Fei’er immediately put his book down and opened the door. After seeing Shan and Speaker Fang outside, Fei’er quickly said, “You actually have time to come here? Come in, quick.” Then he invited the two over to his house.

Shan looked at Fei’er’s house and smiled faintly before he said, “It’s quite nice. It seems like you have been living well these days.”

One couldn’t blame Shan for saying this. The house where Fei’er lived was truly good. His house was like villa, but it wasn’t very big. The entire house seem to have five to six rooms, it was well made.

Upon hearing Shan, Fei’er couldn’t help but smile and said, “I used gold coins to exchange for this house. Inside the Space, as long as you pay enough gold coins to the church, you can have any house you want.”

Shan inspected the place curiously. The house’s setup was very good, it had a good natural flow to it. Not only was its shape beautiful, its interior decoration was also attractive. It gave people a sense of belonging without losing its refined taste.

One must know that achieving this point wasn’t easy. Fei’er and the others were members of the Thunder Clan. With their tall figures, one would need to make a lot of considerations in order to make their dwellings.

After Fei’er invited the two to sit down, he looked at Shan and said, “Shan, why did you have time to come here? Did something happen to your clan? Do you need any help? If needed, I can lend you a hand.”

Shan shook his head and said, “It’s fine, there’s no need for you to make a move. I came today in order to ask you for a drink and to share some food.”

When Fei’er heard Shan, he couldn’t help but smile. Then he quickly said, “Having a drink is certainly not a problem. But I thought you came here because something happened? How about telling me?”

Shan smiled faintly and said, “The O’Neal family’s magic armors are already outside our spatial rift. They had repelled our defensive line and war would soon break out.”

If somebody else saw Shan telling these matters with a smile, then they would certainly think that he has gone crazy. Generally, people wouldn’t smile as they recall their clansmen being destroyed. However, Fei’er could understand. He clearly knew the state of the Winged Pegasus Clan and understood why Shan was like this.

Just in the recent past, Shan went to the Space and asked Fei’er to help him prepare some fresh vegetables. The reason for this was because the Winged Pegasus Clan refused to give him any food. When Fei’er heard this, he couldn’t help but get shocked.

He didn’t expect Shan to be this miserable. He actually can’t regularly eat food. This also caused Fei’er to be angry at the Winged Pegasus Clan.

Fei’er, Shan, and Ding share a very good relationship. These three were friends who went through life and death. After hearing their friend going through such experience, Ding almost sent his people to attack the Winged Pegasus Clan. Fortunately, Fei’er was able to stop him.

After hearing Shan talk now, Fei’er immediately understood. He looked at Shan and said, “So the day you wanted will finally come soon? Then it surely is worth a celebration.”

Shan laughed and said, “Let’s get Ding as well. I also wanted to hide from my people, so I entered the Space. Didn’t they want to not see me? Then I won’t care about them anymore. If they think they’re strong enough, then let them handle the problem themselves.”

Fei’er laughed and said, “Good, good. You finally know what to do. You call Ding while I prepare the food. My food here isn’t delicious, I’ll have to go to the church and exchange for good ones.”

Shan looked at Fei’er in surprise, “You can also exchange for food?”

Fei’er laughed, “In addition to being unable to exchange for living people, there are really few things that you cannot exchange for.” After he said that, Fei’er left the house.

At the same time, Shan took his messenger fish out and called Ding. Just like Fei’er, Ding had also been quite relaxed in the past few days. Although the Barbarians were a militant race, this didn’t mean that they always want to court death. Barbarians weren’t stupid, it was just that their temperament was too simple.

Now, inside the Space, the Barbarians, Winged Pegasus, and the Thunder Clan were well mixed in. The three clans were former comrades who fought side by side. Recently, their lives have been better. Naturally, nobody discriminated anybody. Because of this, the place where the Barbarians lived was very near to Fei’er’s house.

Not long after Fei’er returned with some food and wine, Ding arrived. Ding was happy for Shan upon knowing what was happening to the Winged Pegasus Clan. The group were merry as they drank and ate. It seems like they didn’t know of what was currently happening to the Winged Pegasus Clan.

……..

The Winged Pegasus Clan were frightened after the attack of the nine Supreme Elders. So now, they arranged a lot of monitoring points behind the defensive line. As soon as the defensive line was attacked, these scouts immediately sent news back to the family. Those scouts were equipped with messenger fishes. Therefore, the news of the defensive line’s destruction was immediately transmitted back. In no time, the higher level figures of the family received the news.

When they came to know of the situation, they were really shocked. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai’s words to be true. Someone truly wanted to invade them.

It was just like Shan said, these people didn’t want to see him. Every time Shan opened the matter of moving to the Space, these people would just stay there as though nothing was wrong.

It can be said that Shan was being treated worse than a puppet. At the very least, nobody was being hostile to a puppet. On the other hand, Shan and Speaker Fang were being treated with hostility. They weren’t treated like a member of the clan.

The Winged Pegasus Clan’s Vice Speaker, Fenglei, was currently inside the hall. There were also a lot of Winged Pegasus members present. These people were high ranking members of the clan. Some were the senior council members while some were great generals. There were also city lords present. It can be said that these people were the decision makers of the Winged Pegasus Clan.

Fenglei was the iron official of the Winged Pegasus Clan. If it weren’t for him keeping Speaker Fang back, then Speaker Fang’s influence wouldn’t have reduced so much. And after Yifei was killed by Zhao Hai, it was Fenglei who proposed delaying. He was also the one who made sure that Shan was ignored.

Fenglei looks to be in his fifties. His hair was a little white but his face wasn’t wrinkled. The whites of his hair seem to add some touch of maturity into him. But in his calm expression, one could see a hint of arrogance.

At this time, Fenglei’s face sank as though it was a drop of water. He looked at the people in the room and said, “Everyone should have already received the news. Just like what Zhao Hai and Shan said, there is an invading army just outside our spatial rift. And in only three hours, they managed to break through the 200 thousand troops we stationed in the defensive line. What opinions does everyone have?”

The people inside the room looked at each other. They really didn’t know what to say. The fighting strength of the opposite party was beyond their expectation. In three hours, 200 thousand people were killed. Even the nine Supreme Elders weren’t able to do this.

Fenglei looked at their eyes and couldn’t help but flare in anger. Then after that, a flash of fear appeared. He was afraid of the O’Neal family’s invasion, and he was also afraid of Zhao Hai.

However, he still didn’t think about asking the foreign races for help. This would mean that he was also asking Zhao Hai. Fenglei clearly understood that he had greatly offended Shan. If he wanted to ask Zhao Hai for help, then it would be very difficult to do so. Not to say about Zhao Hai declining to help, but even if Zhao Hai did make a move, then this meant that Fenglei’s great days would be gone. He was even afraid that he wouldn’t be able to keep his life after this ordeal.

At this moment, Fenglei began to feel regret. He regretted that he guessed wrong. He regretted that he didn’t listen to Zhao Hai and didn’t enter the Space. At this point, he didn’t know what he should do.

Chapter 981: Confrontation

Axe stood calmly on top of a war tank as he looked at the place on the other side of the spatial rift. It was like another world. Although he couldn’t see any people, he could affirm that this place wasn’t any smaller compared to the Ark Continent.

Although his expression was calm, Axe’s heart was actually excited. Another plane, it was another plane. Up until now, how many planes did they manage to find? These many planes, even the other families in the Atlanta Plane wouldn’t  have met this many planes. Most importantly, all of these planes would be under the O’Neal family!

Axe was extremely moved at this thought. Then he took a deep breath to stabilize his heartbeat. However, he still couldn’t hide the excitement in his eyes.

George was standing right beside Axe. Upon looking at Axe’s appearance, George couldn’t help but be influenced by it as well. To be honest, even he didn’t expect this expedition to be this huge. George knew very well what this meant for the O’Neal family. Moreover, he made great contributions to this matter.

George looked at Axe and said, “Young Master, let’s go back in. The wind is getting strong.”

Axe turned to George and smiled, “George, if we conquer this place, how much bigger would our O’Neal family become?”

George smiled and said, “If we conquer this place, then I can affirm that the O’Neal family would become the most powerful family in the Atlanta Plane.”

Axe laughed, “Good, good. It’s just as you said, our O’Neal family would truly become the most powerful family in the Atlanta Plane.”

George responded to this with a smile. After some time, Axe calmed down. Then he looked at the Winged Pegasus plane and coldly snorted as he said, “This place now belongs to the O’Neal family. No matter who lives here, they only have one road, either they surrender or they die!”

George replied in a serious tone, “I ask Young Master to feel relieved. This subordinate is willing to break their bones in the name of the O’Neal family!”

Axe gave a satisfied nod, then he said, “George, you must do well. The future development of the O’Neal family would surely be huge. The family would need loyal people to establish vassal clans. If you do well, then your family would certainly occupy your own plane.”

George’s face was flushed with happiness as he bowed to Axe and said, “Yes, Young Master. This one will surely be loyal towards the Young Master and the O’Neal family.” George chose his words carefully. He said ‘Young Master’ before the O’Neal family. This meant that he would be loyal to Axe first before the family.

Loyalty to the O’Neal family didn’t really mean that they would be loyal to Axe. Axe was still not the Patriarch of the O’Neal family. This meant that those who swore loyalty to the family wouldn’t generally be loyal to Axe. What Axe needed the most at this time were subordinates that were loyal to him.

Moreover, George had also changed how he addressed Axe. In the past, he called him ‘Young Lord’, now he called Axe ‘Young Master’. This was also a sign of his status undergoing a change.

Upon calling him ‘Young Lord’ this meant that George was under the influence of the O’Neal family. This meant that he still wasn’t completely under Axe. Now that George was using ‘Young Master’, this implied that he had fully incorporated himself into Axe’s camp. George would join Axe in all of his ups and downs.

Axe was evidently happy, he patted George’s shoulder and said, “Good, good. Let’s go back and discuss how to take this plane.”

George nodded, then together with Axe, they jumped down from the war tank. Then they entered the commanding war tank specifically prepared for Axe.

A Commanding War Tank was actually just like a war tank but with no magic armors inside. It was designed to be a place where the commander would stay in. It was like the RV. Although it wasn’t as comfortable as a recreational vehicle, it was clearly safer.

When Axe returned to his war tank, George also followed behind him. At this point, George had become one of Axe’s most trusted men. And with George’s great talent, he quickly became important to Axe.

Upon returning to their war tank, George immediately poured Axe a cup of water. Axe looked at the half-completed map on the table and gently frowned, “George, look at this map. This only shows the area we managed to scout. In these areas, we discovered that there were monitoring stations. But now, they had retreated. From what I can see, it seems like the other side knew that we’re already here. What do you think?”

George looked at the stretch of map and said, “Young Master, we don’t know much about this place. But the thing we’re sure of is that those people aren’t very strong. We’re fully capable of dealing with them. So the next step we should do is to not care about what they are doing, instead we should think about what we should do.”

Axe raised a brow and said, “Oh, explain it to me.”

George nodded and said, “Yes, Young Master. Our O’Neal family is very strong, much stronger compared to the opposite party. However, we need to be careful. After all, this is the enemy territory. If we care too much about what they are doing, then we might be led by the nose. What I’m saying is, we shouldn’t worry about what they are doing. Instead, we should follow our plan, step by step, and don’t rush to attack. Even if the enemy keeps annoying us, we still have to go one step at a time. This way, we will squeeze them in and before long they would have to come out and fight us head-on.”

Upon hearing this, Axe frowned, “But with this method, we would take more time in dealing with them. It’s a very stupid method.”

George nodded and said, “Young Master, it is indeed a very stupid method. But Young Master, we don’t know anything about our enemy at all. We don’t know what their real combat power is. We don’t know their fighting methods and even their strongest weapons. The only thing we are certain of is that they seem to be following the Warrior discipline and they also have flying mounts. For us, this information is too small. If we make a risky attack, then we may suffer. And if we lose too much, then I’m afraid that it would be disadvantageous to the Young Master.”

When Axe heard this, he couldn’t help but stare for a moment. Then his expression changed as he nodded and said, “You are right. The plan that you said, although it is stupid, but we can also minimize the losses that we suffer. It is the safest way of going forward. Alright, then let’s do it as what you said.”

But George didn’t have a happy expression, he looked at Axe and said, “Young Master, but if we do it this way, then you would be under a lot of pressure. Since this method is slow, then it might seem like you aren’t interested. Those who are in the military wouldn’t easily agree to use this method.”

Axe’s voice turned cold as he replied, “Even if they don’t agree, they still have to do it my way. In any case, I’m still the chief commander of this army. George, just go about your matters with confidence. You don’t need to worry about other things. Just make sure that the battle plan is perfect.”

George nodded, but he was still worried as he said, “Young Master, I don’t think it would be good to be too stiff with those people. The Young Master is going to be the leader of the family in the future. If too many people in the army are against you, then it would be very unfavorable to your position.”

When Axe heard George, his eyes couldn’t help but furrow. Then he nodded and said, “Right, that’s correct. It seems like I shouldn’t be too strict. Alright, George, let me handle this. You can do your thing.”

George nodded before giving a salute and leaving. He knew that he was still only a subordinate of Axe. He just said what he needed to, even if he could do more. If he involved himself too much, then not only would he fail to win Axe’s favor, he might even make Axe think that he wanted to control him. That would be troublesome. There were only specific matters that George can get into, he shouldn’t overstep his bounds.

Axe looked at George’s departing back and nodded. He appreciates how George handled matters and how George was clear about his status. This was why he got Axe’s favor.

Just as George said, although Axe needs talents, he would also need the support of the family’s Elders as well as the Patriarchs of the vassal clans. It was impossible for Axe to rely on people like George. George and the others might be talented, but they had no real power. And in the future, power was what Axe would need the most.

Axe stood in front of the glass window as he looked outside. He sighed lightly, he understood that he had been too naive before, he didn’t understand anything. Every day, he would only indulge himself in risks. After he came in contact with the Clan’s management, he discovered that running it wasn’t an easy matter.

……………………………..

Fenglei looked at the silent people who were inside the room. He couldn’t help but be disappointed as he said, “What? You don’t have any ideas?”

Fenglei didn’t want to get angry, he was afraid of being angry. At this moment, the Winged Pegasus could be described as dispersed. These people used to be loyal to Yifei and were dissatisfied when Zhao Hai killed the Patriarch. Because of this, these people were currently on Fenglei’s side. If Fenglei starts to show his temper, then these people might side towards Shan. After all, Shan was a Patriarch candidate. Therefore, Fenglei could only endure in front of these people.

At this time, a Councilman said, “I believe we should talk to Shan. Have him ask Zhao Hai to act.”

Just after the Councilman said this, everyone in the room looked at him like he was an idiot. A general forced a smile and said, “You want to let Shan ask Zhao Hai to act? Have you been asleep? You should know how Shan is doing these past few days. Don’t be stupid. Do you really think that Shan would ask Zhao Hai for us? Even if Shan invites Zhao Hai, why would Zhao Hai even help us?”

The Councilman looked at the General in anger as he said, “If you don’t like my idea, then why don’t you come up with a better one?”

The General coldly replied, “I might not have any ideas right now, but I certainly wouldn’t come up with such a disappointing one. It would only turn us even more passive and make our deaths come even sooner.”

The Councilman sneered and said, “So we won’t die if we don’t follow my idea? I really don’t know what the Winged Pegasus military is doing right now. You keep posturing here and there, yet you actually don’t have any teeth.”

As soon as the General heard the Councilman, his expression couldn’t help but change. He looked at the Councilman and said ,”What did you say? People like you are just good at using your mouth. Who is currently fighting in the front lines right now? It certainly isn’t you guys. You only know how to sit in this place and blabber your mouth. During times like these, all of you are useless.”

What he said offended every Councilman inside the room. Even Fenglei’s expression wasn’t attractive to look at. After all, he was the Vice Speaker, a Councilman himself.

However, Fenglei wasn’t actually able to retort at this time. If he helped the Councilmen, then he would offend the Military Men. If he offended the Generals, then these Generals might be compelled to side with Shan. If that time comes, then he’s finished.

But he also couldn’t offend the Councilmen. It was at this time that another Councilman pointed at the General and shouted, “Zhanshi, what are you saying? Are really looking down on us? You need to explain yourself.”

Zhanshi coldly snorted and said, “Get lost. If you think I’m wrong, then let’s go outside and fight. Let’s see who’s the real grandfather!”

The room became even livelier as the Councilmen kept berating Zhanshi for his actions. However, Zhanshi wasn’t easy to deal with and had started to berate back. In the end, it became a fight between Councilmen and the Generals. The actions of these two groups plunged to room into great mess.”

Fenglei wished for them to stop several times. However, it came to a point that he couldn’t do anything. He didn’t have enough prestige to suppress the scene. The current situation made Fenglei’s face ugly to behold.

Boom! The loud bang stopped the room. Everyone turned to look at the source and discovered that it was Fenglei. Fengeli was currently looking at them with his pale face. The table in front of him was already turned into splintered blocks.

Fenglei’s cold eyes scanned the room before he said, “Why are all of you arguing? We’re here to solve problems, now look at what all of you are doing. Infighting is the last thing we want right now. We are currently facing a great enemy and stopping their invasion is the most important thing right now.  I don’t want to get angry, but all of you wouldn’t stop unless I make a sound!”

Although Fenglei was very angry, he didn’t actually utter any harsh words. At the same time, the room turned peaceful. Everyone stopped shouting inconsiderately.

However, nobody was still able to present an idea to relieve Fenglei’s headache. At this time, a nearby Councilman suddenly said, “I think we should look for Shan. Even if he couldn’t ask Zhao Hai to help, through Shan we could still invite the Thunder Clan and the Barbarians over.”

Chapter 982: Zhao Hai’s Action

When the Councilman’s words were heard, the people inside the room were stunned. Then everyone began to discuss the issue. The proposal wasn’t immediately refuted because many people felt that the idea was feasible.

It might sound laughable, not asking Shan for help in persuading Zhao Hai, yet agreeing to having Shan ask help from the Thunder Clan and the Barbarians. Although it might sound contradictory, it actually wasn’t.

To state it clearly, the Winged Pegasus were afraid of Zhao Hai, but not Shan. If not for Zhao Hai, Shan wouldn’t have reached his current position.

At this time, a General suddenly said, “But will Shan agree? Moreover, what is stopping him from talking to Zhao Hai right now?”

Fenglei’s eyes narrowed as he said, “Rest assured, Shan wouldn’t. It had been so long yet he still failed to bring our people into Zhao Hai’s Space. What face does he have to talk to Zhao Hai? If we ask him to talk to the Barbarians and the Thunder Clan in order to save our people, judging by Shan’s character, he will definitely do it. As long as we can solve the clan’s situation, Shan certainly wouldn’t tell Zhao Hai about this matter.”

As soon as the people in the room heard this, all of them stared for a moment before looking at Fenglei’s smiling face. There weren’t any mistakes in Fenglei’s words. With Shan’s character, he would surely place importance on the clan’s matters. As long as he invites the Thunder Clan and Barbarians, then the Winged Pegasus clan won’t be afraid of dealing with the O’Neal family.

Fenglei looked at the people and said, “One or two people doing this surely wouldn’t be good. If everyone goes and pressures Shan, he will definitely go no matter what.”

The people in the room nodded. Then Fenglei stood up and loudly said, “Everyone, let’s go look for Shan. Let’s see if he can help.”

Then after he said that, Fenglei stood up and left the room first. At the same time, the other people quickly followed-up. Everyone went to Speaker Fang’s mansion to find Shan.

Before long, the crowd arrived right outside Speaker Fang’s mansion. At this time, there were no guards outside, the entire mansion appeared cold and static. The originally bright and lively mansion now looked like a bleak and haunted place.

Fenglei knew where the study was, so he immediately led everyone over there. Upon arriving outside the study, the group saw two Winged Pegasus guards. Fenglei recognized these two men, they were the most loyal subordinates of Speaker Fang. Their presence dictates that Shan and Speaker Fang was also here.

When the two guards saw Fenglei and the others, they couldn’t help but look at each other. However, they didn’t make any noise. Upon arriving by the door, Fenglei immediately said, “Tell Shan that I’m here.” From the expression on Fenglei’s face, one could see that he didn’t have even an inch of respect towards Shan and Speaker Fang.

When the two guards saw Fang’s expression and heard his words, a flash of anger went by their eyes. Then then one of them proceeded to reply, “Vice Speaker is unlucky, the Master is currently not in his room.”

Upon hearing that the title of ‘Vice Speaker’ was emphasized, Fenglei’s expression couldn’t help but change. But he immediately recovered as he looked at the guards and said, “Is he really not in?”

The two nodded. Then Fenglei coldly snorted as he went to push the door of the study. Normally, the two would stop Fenglei’s action. But today, the two didn’t actually move, they just allowed Fenglei to push the door open to see that there was nobody inside.

Upon seeing the two guards not moving, Fenglei’s expression changed. Then he turned to see the empty room in front of him.

Fenglei’s temper almost flared up, then he calmed himself as he turned to the two guards and said “Where did they go?”

The guards looked at the study and shook their heads at the same time. A flash of cold light appeared in Fenglei’s eyes. He knew that this was a life and death matter of the Winged Pegasus Clan, so he stopped being polite as he looked at the two guards and said, “Tell me where Shan went, or else you can’t blame me for being impolite.”

The two looked at Fenglei before one of them shook his head and said, “The Young Patriarch and the Master were just discussing inside the study a moment ago. But then they suddenly disappeared. We didn’t see them come out, it’s possible that they went to Mister Zhao Hai’s Space.”

When Fenglei heard this, his expression changed. What he was most worried about was Shan talking to Zhao Hai about this matter. Therefore he immediately said, “What did Shan say before leaving?”

The two guards shook their heads once more, then one of them said, “We’ll be unfair to Sir Vice-Speaker, we really don’t know. What we knew is that the Young Patriarch angrily smashed a table and then had us change it to a new one. After that, they disappeared. We aren’t really sure where they went.”

Fenglei didn’t suspect the guards of lying. With how the study room was made, even if one stands outside the door, it would still be impossible to hear what was going on inside. Therefore, it was normal for the two guards to not know anything.”

At this point, Fenglei’s face had an ugly expression. He looked at the two and said, “If your Master comes back, then immediately go and inform me.” After the two gave a simple nod, Fenglei and the others turned around and left.

When Fenglei’s group left, the two guards couldn’t help but smile. Since they were loyal to Speaker Fang and Shan, these two didn’t suffer any less discrimination. It was good that their families had already entered the Space. They had also entered to take a look. Upon seeing that the Space had a good environment, the two of them felt relief.

Because they had been extremely ostracized in the past few days, the two of them were really fed up. So after seeing Fenglei and the others retreating, the two of them couldn’t help but feel extremely good.

Fenglei and the others’ faces were very ugly upon leaving Speaker Fang’s mansion. When they returned to the hall, nobody spoke a word. Their faces were very difficult to look at.

Fenglei looked at the eyes of those present and said, “It seems like Shan is already aware of what happened in the front lines. I just don’t know what he is doing inside Zhao Hai’s Space. In the worst case scenario, Zhao Hai already knows the family’s situation and is ready to intervene. The best case is if Zhao Hai already knew but is not prepared to intervene. We just don’t know  which is which.”

Those present didn’t say anything. They were truly unaware of the current situation.

Fenglei scanned the people inside the room and continued, “Since this is the case, then let’s just assume that Zhao Hai already knows about the family’s situation. No matter what, the only thing we can do right now is go back and support the battle until Shan shows himself. But until that time, we have to block the enemy with our own effort.”

As soon as the people inside the room heard this, their expression changed. But nobody said anything as they gave Fenglei a salute before leaving the hall.

Fenglei was also clear that it was impossible to block the O’Neal family just by using the Winged Pegasus Clan’s strength. What they could do right now is to do their best in the battles and then find a way to ask Shan to invite the Thunder Clan and the Barbarians for help. If they do well, then maybe they can invite Zhao Hai.

Fenglei was clinging to his power and influence, but he was still sane. He knew clearly that the Winged Pegasus Clan had met their biggest crisis. If this wasn’t properly dealt with, then the clan would be in danger of being exterminated. If they weren’t eliminated by Zhao Hai, then they would be eliminated by the O’Neal family.

At this moment, Fenglei discovered that his authority wasn’t that important to him. Whether it was Zhao Hai or the O’Neal family, if they want to control the Winged Pegasus Clan, then they would first deal with the clan’s high-level members as well as those who opposed them. The more influential the person was, the more likely they would be dealt with first. So if the two parties wanted to control the Winged Pegasus clan, then Fenglei wouldn’t have a good time.

After thinking about this, Fenglei gave out a sigh. He finally understood the truth. In the face of absolute strength, these small plays that he was doing was merely him courting death.

……….

At this time, a spatial crack suddenly appeared in front of Speaker Fang’s two guards. Then Shan’s voice was heard, “You two come in here. It isn’t safe there anymore. You two can stop guarding the study.” The two stared before they obediently entered the Space. But after going through, they discovered that Shan wasn’t on the other side.

The two looked at each other before they shrugged their shoulders and returned to their home. To be honest, they were already used to the mysticisms of the Space, so they stopped questioning everything that was happening inside.

Just like the two guards, the other people who were loyal to Speaker Fang and Shan had also been invited back into the Space.

Naturally, this wasn’t an ability that Shan’s command token could do. Instead, it was Zhao Hai who did it. Zhao Hai had been looking at the Winged Pegasus Clan’s situation. After seeing Fenglei and the others’ expressions, Zhao Hai knew that he had to act. Therefore, he immediately took Speaker Fang and Shan’s loyal people back into the Space.

The reason Zhao Hai did this wasn’t because he was afraid of them betraying Shan and Speaker Fang. Zhao Hai discovered that as long as a person entered the Space, then even if they went back out, they seem to still be disinclined to put the Space in a disadvantageous position.

Zhao Hai didn’t know if this situation was the Space’s doing, but he knew that it had something to do with it. In any case, Zhao Hai wanted these people back into the Space because he didn’t want them to have an accident.

Just like Shan said, Zhao Hai was a person who heavily valued sentiment. As long as a person was on his side, then even if the person makes a huge mistake, he would still be inclined to forgive them. This was also the case for the Divines.

The Divines have already been sent into the Space. In the beginning, Zhao Hai was full of hatred towards them, he even wished to eliminate them all. But after his feelings calmed down, Zhao Hai didn’t make any action, he couldn’t bear to make a move on them.

Chapter 983: Winged Pegasus Clan’s Final Hope

Another reason why Zhao Hai took those people back into the Space was because he didn’t want to receive any threats. Zhao Hai dislikes being threatened. And if Fenglei and the others reach a dead end, then it wouldn’t be difficult for them to take those people as hostages. When the time comes, not only would Zhao Hai be troubled, Shan and the others would be as well.

Zhao Hai didn’t want to intervene in the current matters of the Winged Pegasus Clan. He wanted to see if the Winged Pegasus would enter the Space if they were forced to into a corner.

If the Winged Pegasus Clan were like the Thunder Clan, being annihilated yet still not entering the Space, then Zhao Hai would give them his admiration. However, he still wouldn’t help them.

If they want to be heroes, Zhao Hai wouldn’t stop them. They would have Zhao Hai’s respect, but not his sympathy.

The second day after the O’Neal family attacked the defensive line, The O’Neal family began to advance into the Winged Pegasus Plane. Their speed of advancement wasn’t very fast, but it was steady. They left the Winged Pegasus Clan with no chance to counter-attack.

The Generals of the Winged Pegasus Clan were doing the same attacking tactics as Zhao Hai. They were doing guerilla warfare.

However, the Winged Pegasus were quick to discover that their methods were simply useless against the O’Neal family. The magic armors were quicker than them. Moreover, the skies didn’t have any obstructions unlike the ground. If they want to get rid of each other, then speed was paramount. If the Winged Pegasus couldn’t grasp the speed advantage, then they would just be courting death in front of the O’Neal family.

The next day went along this situation. The Winged Pegasus launched sneak attacks that resulted in no benefits. The civilians could only retreat and fall back city by city.

When this situation was recalled over to Fenglei and the others, their expressions were difficult to look at. Guerilla warfare was the final hope of the Winged Pegasus Clan. If this tactic was unusable, then they can only fight using normal methods. But in these base battles, the Winged Pegasus clan would still suffer losses in front of the cannons and war tanks of the O’Neal family.

The next day quickly arrived, the O’Neal family was still taking city after city. But each place they visited didn’t have any people present.

This time, Axe wasn’t thinking of enslavement. They knew too little about the Winged Pegasus Clan. Therefore, Axe was planning on killing them all!

Axe’s plan might be too much, but to Axe it actually wasn’t. They want the land but not the people. If they keep the Winged Pegasus alive, then they would have to station people here in order to keep the Winged Pegasus Clan in check. This would slash numbers from the O’Neal family’s army. Therefore, Axe was intent on cleaning the place up, not even chickens and dogs would survive.

Axe wasn’t afraid of the Winged Pegasus Clan’s retaliation. To be honest, he even hopes for the Winged Pegasus Clan to send out powerful soldiers their way. This would make Axe assured that the Winged Pegasus were at least decent. If the Winged Pegasus can provide good resistance, then Axe’s heart would be settled. Axe could still remember the undead that they faced in the beginning. Their fighting strength was exceptional.

Although those undead were very strong, in the life and death moment of the Winged Pegasus Clan, they actually didn’t appear. For Axe, this situation was a significant hidden danger.

Axe knew that those undead were controlled by a person. If he couldn’t see those undead here in the Winged Pegasus plane, then this means that the person was hiding all along. That person’s threat to the O’Neal family was too big.

Although the attacks of the family were formidable, it was impossible for pilots to stay inside their magic armors all the time. And once they go out of their magic armors, the strength of the pilots would decrease by several folds. In this case, if an army of undead suddenly appeared during the time when pilots were not inside their magic armors, then the O’Neal family would suffer a huge disaster.

Axe was no longer the naive boy who had just gained an army to command. After the past few days, he had matured and was now able to think about problems ahead. Therefore, Axe greatly valued information regarding those undead.

………………

Upon receiving more information, Fenglei and the others immediately went back to Speaker Fang’s mansion in order to look for Shan. However, they were unfortunate since, not only Shan, but even the guards on the study room were gone. Upon seeing this, Fenglei’s heart turned cold. He didn’t know what Shan was doing. However, this also meant that Fenglei and the others could no longer use those people to threaten Shan.

It was just yesterday that they found out about Shan and Speaker Fang entering the Space. Upon returning to the hall, Fenglei thought about various ways on how to solve their problem. The only thing they need to do right now was to have Shan contact the Thunder Clan and the Barbarians for help.

That evening, Fenglei finally decided on catching everyone loyal to Shan and use them as a bargaining chip. But now, it seems like that method couldn’t be used. Everyone who was still loyal to Shan, as well as those who were on Speaker Fang’s side, had vanished. Now, Fenglei had no means to threaten Shan.

In the face of this outcome, Fenglei didn’t know what to do. Then he suddenly discovered that if Shan couldn’t help them, then the Winged Pegasus Clan would be finished.

In the past, Fenglei and the others felt that Shan was just spouting nonsense in order to scare them. But now, they found out that it was actually true. If they don’t enter Zhao Hai’s Space, then the Winged Pegasus Clan would likely be annihilated.

However, this realization came too late. Fenglei knew that counting on Shan at this time would be impossible. But there was still another choice, the foreign races.

After thinking about this, Fenglei immediately took his messenger fish. This fish was connected to a foreign race member that he was previously acquainted to. As Fenglei held his messenger fish, he said, “Elder Ness, Elder Ness, are you there?”

This Elder Ness was a Beastman race elder who was also the Elder in charge of keeping in contact with the Winged Pegasus Clan. He was Fenglei’s last hope in order to save the race. Just as Fenglei was about to repeat his call, Elder Ness’ voice was suddenly heard, “Speaker Fenglei? What’s the problem?”

When Fenglei heard Ness’ answer, he couldn’t help but let out a long breath. Then he quickly replied, “Elder Ness, good day. This Fenglei has something to tell you. A new race has appeared in the Divine Realm. They use some sort of iron giant to fight. These iron giants are very strong. They can fly in the sky and their attacks aren’t lower than any God-rank expert. At this time, they are attacking the Winged Pegasus Clan. I hope that the foreign races would help us. As long as you save us, then the Winged Pegasus Clan would pay any price.”

The Winged Pegasus Clan paying any price wasn’t something that a Vice-Speaker like Fenglei could say. But now that Shan and Fang weren’t present, Fenglei had no choice.

When he heard Fenglei, Ness paused for a moment. This caused Fenglei to become uneasy. After a while, Ness said, “Fenglei, I seem to remember Zhao Hai having a good relationship with the Winged Pegasus Clan. Why didn’t Mister Zhao Hai help you this time?”

Fenglei couldn’t help but smile bitterly, he didn’t expect the other party to bring up the matter of Zhao Hai. Moreover, it seems like the other party was respectful towards him. This caused Fenglei to feel awkward.

He tried his best to say that he didn’t want to be ruled by Zhao Hai. However, it seems like everyone has a good relationship with him. For the Winged Pegasus, this was a huge blow.

Naturally, Fenglei wouldn’t speak the truth. He immediately said, “Elder Ness, this is what happened. Our Winged Pegasus Clan has a person named Shan, he’s the only one who can reach Mister Zhao Hai. However, he’s not in our family this time and went to visit the Barbarians and the Thunder Clan. Since we couldn’t find him, then we couldn’t look for Mister Zhao Hai for help. Therefore, I want to ask the foreign races to help us go through this ordeal.”

Fenglei’s words were nothing less than smooth, moreover, he spoke with great care. He never made his request as the Patriarch of the Winged Pegasus Race, so even if the foreign races agree to help and drive off the O’Neal family, the Winged Pegasus Clan still has the chance to withdraw from the agreement since the request bore no authority They could just say that the Patriarch didn’t give his agreement to the request, this should buy them time.

As soon as Ness heard Fenglei, he turned silent. Then after some time he said, “Speaker Fenglei, I couldn’t decide on this matter myself. The clan would need to have a discussion. Please wait for some time.” Right after that, Ness didn’t speak anymore.

Fenglei’s heart couldn’t help but sink. He was afraid that Ness wouldn’t care about them. If this was the case, then the Winged Pegasus Clan is finished.

But what Fenglei didn’t know was that his request had caused a debate among the Foreign Races. The Foreign Races was almost divided into two sides, those who wanted to offer support and take the opportunity to absorb the Winged Pegasus Clan, and those who didn’t want to help in order to prevent offending Zhao Hai.

The worries of the Foreign Races were within reason. This was because they understood the situation with the Winged Pegasus Clan. At the same time, they also knew about their relationship with Zhao Hai.

Chapter 984: The Foreign Races’ Decision

Solomon, Leir, and Yerd were currently inside the Beastman Race’s palace. There were also other tribal groups present inside the room. The people in this room were the decision makers of the three races. If someone were to come here and kill everyone present, then the entire Foreign Races would certainly fall into anarchy.

But the reason why these people were here was for discussion. They will decide on whether they should send troops to help the Winged Pegasus Clan. For the foreign races, the implications of this decision were quite heavy.

Solomon looked at the people inside the room and said, “Everyone should already know why we’re here. So, how do we decide on this?”

Whispers were quickly heard inside the hall, everyone was discussing amongst themselves. However, nobody actually talked out loud. Everyone was just sitting there talking with those close to them.

When Solomon saw this situation, his eyes couldn’t help but contract. He didn’t think that this simple thing, when connected to Zhao Hai, would turn into a complex situation.

Solomon turned to Leir and the Yerd and said, “How about you two? What do you think about this matter?”

Leir smiled faintly and said, “Let’s listen to what everyone says first. I still can’t decide on what to do with this matter.”

Yerd didn’t make any noise but she nodded, indicating her intent. She didn’t want to express her view at this time.

Solomon already expected this response, but since this matter needed to be resolved, he looked at the two and said, “You two, why are you making this difficult? Why don’t you just say what is on your mind?”

The people under them had also noticed the actions of the three leaders. Therefore, the discussions began to turn quiet until everyone was now turning their attention to the three.

The smile on Leir’s face disappeared and a trace of anger flashed by his eyes. He didn’t think that Solomon would force them to this point. He discovered the Solomon had become more and more overbearing in the recent days. It seems like he looks at Leir as though he was his subordinate. With Leir’s temper, this was completely unacceptable.

Leir was a Dwarf who were good-natured people and liked to handle things in a low-key manner. But no matter what, Leir was still a Patriarch, holding the same status as Solomon. How could Solomon treat him in such a manner.

Leir looked at Solomon and said, “How about we send people to find Bingya and the others first? Once they come here, then they may give us a better suggestion. After all, they had been with Mister Zhao Hai for a long time. They should understand Zhao Hai’s temperament more than us.”

When Leir said this, nobody objected. They knew that Leir was on point. Now that Zhao Hai had dealt with the Supreme Elders, the people didn’t regard Bingya and the others as important as they used to be. However, it seems like their opinion was still very important.

Bingya and the others have been with Zhao Hai for a long time, so they should have a good understanding about Zhao Hai’s style. Because of this, their opinion should be significant to the discussion.

Solomon didn’t say anything. To be honest, he didn’t really care about Zhao Hai right now. They had already obtained the 12 Ultimate Weapons. Although one had been taken away by Zhao Hai, it wouldn’t affect their strength too much. Solomon believed that their present strength was already enough to deal with Zhao Hai. Don’t forget, Zhao Hai didn’t dare to face the nine Supreme Elders. At that time, Zhao Hai wanted to ask the foreign races for help.

By looking at this point, it was enough as long as five to six Supreme Elders collaborate to deal with Zhao Hai. There’s no need to say about 12 Supreme Elders. These 12 ultimate weapons would certainly deal with Zhao Hai. Killing Zhao Hai with this number shouldn’t be impossible.

Because of this thought, Solomon advocates to support the Winged Pegasus Clan. He wanted to use this opportunity to seize the Winged Pegasus. For Solomon, Zhao Hai was no longer worth worrying about.

Leir’s thoughts were the direct opposite to Solomon’s. He wasn’t in favor of sending support. Leir knew a lot about Zhao Hai from Ryder. He came to know that Zhao Hai had means to know what’s currently happening to his people. Therefore, it’s impossible for Zhao Hai to be unaware of what was currently happening to the Winged Pegasus. If Zhao Hai knew about the Winged Pegasus Clan’s situation and didn’t make a move, then this means that Zhao Hai has his own plans. Because of this, Leir believes that they shouldn’t dispatch troops, lest they disrupt Zhao Hai’s plan.

Leir didn’t want to do wrong with Zhao Hai. He believed that Zhao Hai had helped them so much and had even given the ultimate weapons to the Foreign Races. With this sincerity, the Foreign Races should be supporting Zhao Hai.

Meanwhile, although Yerd was still on the fence, she was leaning on the decision of sending troops. The Elves had always thought that they were the most noble race between the heaven and the earth. They had been suppressed by the Divines all these years which made the Elves feel aggrieved. Now that the Divines had disappeared, then it was natural for them to show their strength.

Yerd’s idea about Zhao Hai was similar to Solomon. In her mind, they now have the power to deal with Zhao Hai. Even if Zhao Hai couldn’t be killed, he would still have problems facing 12 Supreme Elders. Most importantly, Yerd was thinking that Zhao Hai was about to ascend!

Zhao Hai informed them that he was about to ascend. Although this shows Zhao Hai’s strength, it also represented his weakness. This meant that Zhao Hai couldn’t stay at this plane for too long. As long as they drag Zhao Hai on for a while, then their shackles on the Foreign Races should disappear once he ascends.

Because of this information, Yerd agreed to sending troops. However, she still needed to be careful and wanted to listen to Yehta’s opinion.

Before long, three people came in from outside. These were the three people who went to look for Bingya, Ryder, and Yehta. When these three people came back, Solomon’s spirit couldn’t help but shake, he immediately said, “Did Bingya and the others arrive? Make them enter quickly.”

Among the three people, a beastman immediately replied, “Answering to the Patriarch. I didn’t find Captain Bingya. I went to his home and found out from his neighbor that after returning, his family suddenly moved out. As to where, nobody knows. Also, it wasn’t only them who moved out, those with close relationship to them were gone as well.”

Solomon stared before his expression changed. Then he turned to the Dwarf and the Elf, but their report was the same, Yehta and Ryder had also moved out at fairly the same time as Bingya. Moreover, just like Bingya, the people who had close relationships with them were gone. They didn’t even leave behind any clue.

When he heard the reports, Solomon’s mood sank, then he roared, “Absurd! They certainly ran with Zhao Hai, I’m sure of it!”

Leir’s expression had also turned frigid. However, he wasn’t angry, instead he was worried. This was because he found out that things were more serious than he thought. Zhao Hai seems to know something, thus prompting him to make such an arrangement.

This information made the people inside the hall look at each other. They didn’t know what to say. At this moment, Solomon turned to everyone and said, “Forget it. Everyone, let’s talk about what to do with the Winged Pegasus Clan.”

Upon hearing the whispers once more, Solomon actually frowned. To be honest, he disliked this sound, he disliked discussion. However, he couldn’t change the situation..

After a short time, a Beastman suddenly stood up and bowed to Solomon, “Your Majesty, I think we should dispatch troops. At this moment, the most powerful group in the Divine Realm is the Foreign Races. The Winged Pegasus Clan is our ally, so we should send troops to help them. At the same time, we could also absorb the Winged Pegasus, this way they won’t provide a problem for us in the future. We shouldn’t be passive in this matter.”

This was a Fox Beastman. The Fox tribe were famous for being sly. His words were representative of their nature. He first said that they were now the most formidable force in the Divine Realm. Although the Winged Pegasus were their ally, his words wanted to remind those present that they were now the rulers of the Divine Realm. It was time for them to expand.

After that, he also said that they should absorb the Winged Pegasus Clan. In other words, since they weren’t part of the Foreign Races, then they might become their enemy in the future. Because of this, they need to make a move towards the other party first.

Although it was only a short string of words, it relayed many things. One could see from this point where the reputation of the Fox tribe being sly came from.

His words caused another burst of murmurs inside the room. After the Divines were dealt with, the Foreign Races found themselves with a inflated sense of confidence.

At this time, a Dwarf stood up and said, “I don’t agree to sending troops. Everyone should be aware that the Winged Pegasus, the Thunder Clan, and the Barbarians were Mister Zhao Hai’s first allies. Mister Zhao Hai had already taken the Thunder Clan and the Barbarians to another place, meanwhile, the Winged Pegasus Clan had been dragging on and refused to go. Because of this matter, Mister Zhao Hai even killed the Winged Pegasus Patriarch. It’s impossible for Mister Zhao Hai to be unaware of the Winged Pegasus Clan’s situation. It’s also not possible for Mister Zhao Hai to not make a move despite knowing about this matter, this simply isn’t his character. This only means that Mister Zhao Hai intended to refrain from sending troops, he has his own plan. If we rashly meddle in his business, then we might offend Mister. This wouldn’t be good for the Foreign Races.”

The Dwarf said a lot of words, he also pointed out the downside of meddling in this situation. From what he said, it can be seen that they had some connections inside the Winged Pegasus Clan, making them aware of the clan’s matters. They knew that something must have happened between Zhao Hai and the Winged Pegasus Clan. If they dispatch troops at this time, then they might greatly offend Zhao Hai. There were a lot of people in this room that didn’t want to offend Zhao Hai. This was because they had firsthand experience with Zhao Hai’s fighting prowess.

At this time, another Beastman stood up and said, “What are we afraid of? Don’t forget, we now have the Divine Realm’s 12 ultimate weapons. This is an unprecedented degree of strength. So what if we offend Zhao Hai? He wouldn’t be able to do anything to us.”

This statement gave no consideration nor face to their previous alliance with Zhao Hai. However, there were a lot of people inside this hall who had the same idea in their mind, especially the Beastman and the Elves.

Then as a retort, another Dwarf stood up, “What are you talking about? Don’t forget how much Mister Zhao Hai has helped us. But now, you’re thinking about dealing with Mister Zhao Hai. You are being ungrateful!”

The Beastman coldly snorted and said, “Ungrateful? Did Zhao Hai really help us to deal with the Divine Race? Don’t forget, he also has great hatred towards the Divine Race. Then after that, he only gave us the 12 ultimate weapons, the most important part, the Star Disk, he kept for himself. And why do you think he did this? It’s because he didn’t regard us as an ally from the beginning. Why should we be hospitable to such a person? Why would we be ungrateful if we decide to deal with him?”

The Dwarf replied, “No matter what, if not for Mister Zhao Hai, our Foreign Race wouldn’t have conquered the Divine Realm. It would have been impossible for us to obtain 12 Ultimate Weapons. At the very least, we should feel some gratefulness towards him. We shouldn’t be thinking about dealing with Mister Zhao Hai.”

The Beastman sneered and said, “Is gratefulness really more important than the improvement of our race? This time, we’ll be sending troops to the Winged Pegasus Clan in order to absorb them into our fold. This will strengthen the Foreign Races. With such a good opportunity, why shouldn’t we send troops? Zhao Hai dealing with the Divines can be said to be his good will toward us. However, that wasn’t completely because he wanted to help us. He dealt with the Divines because he has enmity with them. If he really dealt with the Divines completely because of us, then I will be grateful. But now, hehe.”

The Beastman said exactly what was inside Solomon’s mind. Just like he said, they had no sense of gratefulness towards Zhao Hai. This was because, in their minds, Zhao Hai dealt with the Divines because they offended him. Him helping the Foreign Races was just a fortunate secondary result.

Chapter 985: Shan Moves

Solomon, Leir, and Yerd were just sitting there as they listened to the ongoing argument. One could see from both sides of the argument that the Beastmen were on the side of sending troops to the Winged Pegasus Clan. Meanwhile, the Dwarves opposes the idea. This was also in line with the ideas of both Patriarchs of each race. On the other hand, the Elves stayed quiet. But from their expression, it seems like they were more inclined to the idea of sending troops.

Leir looked at his people and couldn’t help but sigh deep inside. The Dwarven temperament is too straight. Because of this, they would always owe something to other people. Even the straightforward Beastmen had taken advantage of the Dwarves. After all, the Beastmen had people like the Fox tribe, meanwhile the Dwarves did not.

In Dwarven culture, grace was grace while enmity was enmity. Zhao Hai dealt with the Divine Race, and in the process helped the Foreign Races. Therefore, how could the Dwarves not acknowledge this contribution? This made Leir feel that the Beastmen were too shameless in their current action.

Solomon also felt terrible. Although Leir didn’t express any opinions about this matter, the attitude of the Dwarves showed Leir’s temperament. It seems like Leir didn’t want to dispatch troops.

Solomon had some understanding with regards to Leir. He knew that Leir was very fond of Zhao Hai. It was because of this that Leir didn’t want to participate in this action towards the Winged Pegasus Clan.

Yerd was also looking at the argument happening below. She couldn’t help but frown since she knew the implications of this scene. At the same time, she can see the Beastman  race’s dominant behavior. Although she resented such attitude, Yerd understood that the Foreign Races couldn’t afford an internal fight. Once they split, then they wouldn’t be able to dominate the entire Divine Realm.

The current Divine Realm no longer had the Divine Race, the strongest party occupying it right now were the Foreign Races. But if some internal discord happens within the Foreign Races, then the three races would be diverged. In this case, they wouldn’t be able to suppress all of the vassal races.

Additionally, the vassal races had just separated themselves from the control of the Divines. If the Foreign Races wanted to suppress them and rule them at this time, then they would need unsurpassed strength. The vassal races surely wouldn’t give up the freedom that they just gained.

It can be said that there was currently a power vacuum in the Divine Realm. And the Foreign Races were the best contender of occupying this void. Because of this, the Foreign Races needed to stay together.

After thinking about this and seeing that it was still noisy, Yerd made a soft cough. Although it wasn’t very loud, everyone in the hall actually heard it. Almost at the same time, everyone inside the hall turned silent.

Yerd’s identity was special with her being the Elven Race’s Queen. At the same time, she was also the least spoken person among the three leaders. She seldom expresses her opinion. Generally, it would be Solomon or Leir who talked while Yerd would listen and would say some words during critical times. Regardless of Solomon or Leir, to them, Yerd’s opinion was very important.

This time, Yerd actually intended to speak first. This was beyond everyone’s expectations, which in turn made the entire hall extremely quiet.

After looking at everyone, Yerd said, “Everyone, arguing wouldn’t solve anything. In my opinion,  we should send troops to the Winged Pegasus. This is also an opportunity to test Mister Zhao Hai’s attitude. He said that he would leave the Divine Realm since he would ascend. If this is the case, then he wouldn’t care about us sending troops. Otherwise, he would be lying. It’s possible that he’s the one who sent the attack to the Winged Pegasus Clan using these magic armors. These things didn’t appear in the Divine Realm before. His attacking strength is formidable, so he may pose a threat to the Divine Realm. Our Foreign races need to survive. Therefore, we need to understand our enemies. And we need to dispatch our troops in order to do so.”

Yerd spoke her thoughts one by one. As soon as he heard Yerd, Leir couldn’t help but frown. He knows that sending troops this time was inevitable.

Then Yerd turned to look at Lier and said, “We need to dispatch troops and solve this matter at the shortest time. Therefore, I want four Supreme Elders to act along with 20 million troops. Among these four elders, two will come from the Elves while two will come from the Beastmen. The Dwarves doesn’t need to send anyone. After all, we still need enough experts to defend the foreign race territory.”

Yerd’s words made Solomon’s eyes turn bright.  He immediately understood why Yerd did this. Solomon was very much in favor to Yerd’s approach.

Although Solomon loved being powerful, he wasn’t a fool. He knew about the foreign races’ situation. At this time, the Foreign Races couldn’t afford any internal dispute. And it was for this reason why he didn’t immediately say that they should send troops. Instead, he initiated a discussion between all three races.

However, Solomon didn’t expect Yerd to be so formidable. Solomon thought that his plans would be ruined, but who would’ve thought that Yerd would provide a solution. Moreover, it was the best approach they could follow right now.

The Foreign Races would dispatch troops. And since the Dwarves didn’t want to, then they wouldn’t be forced. As the matter stands, how could the Dwarves oppose?

After thinking about this, Solomon turned to Leir. Upon meeting Solomon’s eyes, Leir nodded and said, “I agree with Queen Yerd’s suggestion.” Solomon relaxed and nodded, “Alright, then we have reached a decision. We’ll proceed to discuss which troops to send.”

At this time, Zhao Hai was inside the Space looking at what was happening. When Zhao hai went to the foreign race territory, he also made maps for the Space. One shouldn’t forget that Zhao Hai didn’t reach the Dwarven territory first. Instead, he actually arrived at the Beastman territory. At that time, Zhao Hai released his staff to map the Beastman territory. Because of this, he can now monitor the Foreign Races at will.

Laura and the others were sitting beside Zhao Hai. Their faces were scrunched up as the foreign races discussed which troops to send. Then Laura coldly snorted and said, “These group of ungrateful things. Brother Hai, we must teach them a lesson this time.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Teach them a lesson? Why? Isn’t this what we wanted? Now that they had dispatched troops, we will be able to see how the O’Neal family would deal with them. Presently, I’m afraid the magic armors wouldn’t be able to deal with the Supreme Elders. When the time comes, the O’Neal family would surely send more formidable magic armors. We need to pay attention at that time.”

Laura still coldly snorted and said, “We should still teach them a lesson. Aside from the Dwarves, I’m quite tired of looking at the smug faces of the Beastman and the Elves.”

Zhao Hai slightly smiled and said, “Don’t worry, that time will come for sure. However, that time isn’t now. Don’t worry about this anymore. Let’s go tell Shan about the situation and then have them prepare.”

Laura nodded before immediately calling Shan. She knew how useful the current situation would be for Shan. Now that the O’Neal family had invaded the Winged Pegasus Plane, the clan’s impression of Shan underwent a subtle change. Shan would be able to make good use of Fenglei’s request for help from the foreign races.

Shan was currently staying inside the Space without worry in the past two days. He intends to make his clansmen anxious. Otherwise, they would never appreciate what he has done for the clan.

At this moment, his messenger fish sounded out. Shan looked and saw that it was Zhao Hai’s messenger fish. Shan immediately took the call and heard about the Foreign Races’ troops from Laura.

Upon hearing Laura, Shan immediately knew what the Foreign Races intend to do. He didn’t expect Fenglei to resort to such a drastic option.

Shan’s face was ugly as he he put his messenger fish down. Then he turned to Speaker Fang, Fei’er, and Ding. They were currently inside Fei’er’s villa and had also heard what Laura said.

Shan looked at Fei’er and the others as he smiled bitterly and said, “My clansmen really doesn’t fail to make me worry. Fei’er, what do you think?”

Fei’er forced a smile, “I have some ideas, but I couldn’t meddle in this matter. Otherwise, it would only cause resentment from your people. I also feel that Mister told you this information so that you can make use of it.”

Shan gently frowned. He understood what Fei’er wanted to say. However, he has no confidence in his clan. He can use this news but with his people’s attitude towards him, who knows how much it would be valued.

Speaker Fang looked at Shan and said, “I think we could use this very well. With the O’Neal family’s invasion, the tribe is now aware that we weren’t lying. And now that Fenglei had asked the foreign races for help, the clansmen would surely resent him. Don’t forget, we had just been liberated from the Divines. It wouldn’t be long before our clan would oppose the control of the Foreign Races. Compared to the Foreign Races, our people would rather accept Mister Zhao Hai.”

When he heard Speaker Fang, Shan’s eyes lit up as he said, “Right, then we’ll do that. This time, even if we can’t get everyone to the Space, we can still find more ways for others to get in. Even those who wouldn’t want to come will have to join in.”

Chapter 986: Acting Out A Play

Fengling’s recent days weren’t very well. She was a vegetable farmer selling her produce to the Speaker’s mansion. During the time when Shan asked Zhao Hai to kill the Patriarch, she was enraged. She stopped supplying the mansion with food. Although this significantly reduced her profit, she didn’t mind.

To Fengling, Shan asking Zhao Hai to kill the Patriarch was an act of betrayal. Because of this, she decided to go against what Shan stood for, to the point where she wouldn’t give Shan any food to eat.

Although Shan said that there were invaders coming and the clan would need to shift to a safer place, Fengling was just like the other Winged Pegasus, she didn’t believe.

But when the O’Neal family arrived, Fengling began to believe Shan’s words. However, when she returned to the mansion, she discovered that it was devoid of people. Nobody knew where Shan and the others went.

Fengling began to feel regret. Because of this, she kept returning to the mansion every day. She was hoping to meet Shan and apologize. She also wishes for Shan to request Zhao Hai to help the Winged Pegasus to pass this time of difficulty.

However, in the following days, Shan didn’t appear. Fengling soon began to feel despair. On this day, just as usual, she went to the mansion. The mansion was currently bleak, there was no sense of vitality in it whatsoever. This caused Fengling’s mood to turn awful. She could still remember the time when the mansion was still very lively.

Fengling unconsciously began to walk throughout the mansion. At the same time, she thought back to how she treated Shan before. Fengling regretted her actions very much.

At this moment, Fengling suddenly heard people speaking inside the study room. Fengling stared for a moment before her face lit up with happiness. She immediately stepped forwards and went to the mansion’s study.

There were no guards outside the study. Fengling slowly approached the door until she heard the words being spoken, “Speaker, is this true? Did Fenglei really ask the Foreign Races to rescue the clan?”

Fenglei could never forget Shan’s voice. But what shocked her more was the content of the conversation. Fenglei asked the Foreign Races for help?

Although these seem to be ordinary words, it made Fengling think about the time when the Divines still ruled the Winged Pegasus Clan. Fenglei began to feel shock, then she continued listening.

At this time, it was Speaker Fang’s voice who spoke, “It shouldn’t be wrong. Mister Zhao Hai is currently not in the Divine Realm, so he didn’t have the means to help us. However, he’s still worried about the situation here. When you informed Mister that people had invaded the clan, he immediately wanted to come back. However, he became caught up with something, so he has no way to return. But Mister still had contacts within the Foreign Races. Mister Zhao Hai has some relationship with Bingya and the others. Now that the three of them have great status in their clan, they were able to find out that Fenglei had asked the Foreign Races for help.”

Fengling was quietly listening. However, she lamented deep in her heart about two things. First was her prior prejudice against Shan, and the other was hatred for what Fenglei did.

Fengling had three children, and her eldest son was a Winged Pegasus soldier who died while fighting against the Divines. Because of this, Fengling deeply cherished the Winged Pegasus Clan. It was precisely because of this that Fengling opposed to entering the Space. This was because she thought that Zhao Hai would rule over them. She wouldn’t allow her son’s sacrifice to go in vain, this caused her opposition to be very strong.

However, it seems like Zhao Hai wanted to help the Winged Pegasus Clan from the very beginning. The only thing that Fengling knew was Zhao Hai killing the Winged Pegasus Patriarch. This caused her to dislike Zhao Hai as well as the idea proposed by Shan.

But even then, her resentment towards the Foreign Races was bigger. The Winged Pegasus were keen on education. Because of this, Fengling wasn’t a fool who didn’t understand anything. Upon hearing that Fenglei had asked the Foreign Races for help, she began to feel terrible. Wouldn’t the foreign races use this opportunity to control the Winged Pegasus Clan?

Just as Fengling was thinking about this, Shan’s voice was heard, “So what is the Foreign Races’ response:? Are they going to send troops?”

Speaker Fang replied, “Yes. Bingya already told Mister that the foreign races are ready to dispatch troops. They would send four Supreme Elders as well as 20 million people.”

Shan ‘gawked’, “Four Supreme Elders? What do they want to do? Rule the Winged Pegasus Clan?”

Speaker Fang replied, “The Foreign Races had already discussed it. Among the three races, only the Dwarves strongly opposed to this idea. This was because they knew about Mister Zhao Hai’s good relationship with us. However, the Beastmen and the Elves supported sending troops. They want to do this in order to test Mister.”

Shan proceeded to ask, “Test? What do you mean?”

Speaker Fang replied, “Right, test. Ever since Mister Zhao Hai helped them deal with the Divine Race, the Foreign Races began to believe that they are now the strongest in the Divine Realm. Moreover, they think that all other race should submit to them. However, they still haven’t found a reason to move against the other races. At this moment, the Divine Realm is in a delicate state. All vassal races had just obtained their freedom. Because of this, the Foreign Races couldn’t just rashly invade. Otherwise, they would risk being attacked by all vassal races. They would need a good excuse to make a move. But now, with Fenglei’s request, the Foreign Races gained what they want, an excuse. And because of Mister Zhao Hai, the Foreign races entered a discussion. In the end, they decided to send troops. If they send troops and Mister Zhao Hai intervened, then they would just say that it was Fenglei who asked them for help. And if Mister Zhao Hai didn’t arrive, then they would occupy our Winged Pegasus Plane. With their Supreme Elders present, it would almost be impossible for us to counter-attack. In the end, the Winged Pegasus Clan would turn into a vassal race for the foreign races.”

Boom! Fengling’s heart couldn’t help but jump upon hearing Speaker Fang. And just as she thought about this, Shan broke the table.[1]

Sure enough, Shan’s angry voice was soon heard, “They dare! Mister Zhao Hai will not let them off!”

Speaker Fang replied with a hint of helplessness in his voice, “We have to accept that Mister couldn’t take care of us forever. You should be aware that the 12 ultimate weapons are now in the hands of the Foreign Races. Even if it is Mister Zhao Hai, he still would have a hard to dealing with them. This time, the foreign races are just going according to Fenglei’s request.”

The room turned quiet for some time. Then after a short while, Shan sighed and said, “I really don’t know what everyone in the clan is thinking. They don’t know the current state of the Thunder Clan and the Barbarians inside Mister Zhao Hai’s Space. The two clans doesn’t need to worry about eating or drinking anymore. They can do whatever they want to do. I’ve already asked Fei’er whether Mister Zhao Hai meddled in their affairs. Fei’er told me that Mister Zhao Hai didn’t do anything to them at all. They just went on like they used to. Why would everyone stay here and defend against the Foreign Races instead of living well inside Mister Zhao Hai’s Space?”

Speaker Fang replied, “It is because of power. Yifei wants to be the King of the Winged Pegasus Clan and rule the entire Clan alone. So he fought heavily against entering the Space. Think about how many times you have asked him. Did he listen? In the end, you had to ask Mister Zhao Hai to kill him. You only thought of best for the clan. But after Yifei died, his camp still survived, falling under Fenglei’s control. When I went to fight against the Divine Race, it was Yifei and Fenglei who went and won the Councilmen over. This caused me to be pushed out. At this point, I have no influence to stop them. This caused the Winged Pegasus Clan to be in a dire situation. We need to think of a solution to solve this.”

Shan sighed and said, “I have the method to make the clan enter the Space, but they didn’t enter. I’ve also asked the Thunder Clan and the Barbarians to help in these past few days. However, the Thunder Clan had been severely crippled by what happened before they entered the Space. On the other hand, the Barbarians have yet to settle inside. This made it impossible for them to dispatch troops. Now, our sole means is to convince our clansmen to enter the Space. However, the Clan doesn’t listen to me. I’ve done all that I can.”

Speaker Fang’s voice replied, “Let’s go inside the Space once more and see if the Barbarians could send troops. After all, this involves the life and death of the Winged Pegasus Clan.”

Shan’s reply came in, “Alright, let’s give it another try.” Then after that no other sound was heard.

At this time, Fengling opened the room’s door. However, the only thing she saw was the broken table. Upon seeing nothing, Fengling couldn’t help but feel regretful.

However, her eyes suddenly shone with light. She heard the conversation between Shan and Speaker Fang and came to know many things. More importantly, these information were very important for the Winged Pegasus Clan. She needs to spread this information to the others.

One shouldn’t underestimate a woman’s skill in spreading news. In less than one day, an entire city was able to hear rumors that the Foreign Race troops that were coming over weren’t here to help them, instead it was to conquer the Winged Pegasus Clan. Even if Fenglei flew to this place, it was already too late to hide anything.

Moreover, the rumor was still spreading fast. This new wave of information expanded in all directions. In just a few days, all of the Winged Pegasus Clan knew about this matter.

But how could Fengling think that what she heard was just a play that Shan and Speaker Fang performed?

* * *

Again, Shan the table-destroyer

Chapter 987: The Frantic Winged Pegasus Clan

Shan and Speaker Fang can only do this. At this time, everyone in the Winged Pegasus Clan who were loyal to them have already moved to the Space. Just going outside and spreading information would be impossible, they cannot do it with their current status.

Moreover, they chose the person carefully, Fengling. They knew about the history of Fengling’s family. Although Fengling didn’t give them any food, Shan didn’t actually hate her. In fact, Fengling’s eldest son was one of Shan’s men.

Since Shan knew how sincere Fengling was, he decided to have this information spread through her.

There was also another reason why Shan chose Fengling. This was because of Fengling’s personal connections. Although she was only a vegetable grower, but she used to give food to the Speaker’s hall. This allowed her to know a lot of people. Moreover, some of these people held great status. And there was also her son. Because of this, it was certainly possible for her to spread messages in a short period of time.

Shan’s plan was very successful. In less than three days, the Winged Pegasus clan were already aware that the Foreign Races were on their way. They also knew that although the Foreign Races came to support them, they actually wanted to absorb the Winged Pegasus Clan.

Since the credibility on this rumor was high, and adding on the current sensitive environment, Fenglei soon discovered that his days weren’t doing well. Even his family members were affected. Everytime they walk on the streets, they would always be looked at with hostility.

Fenglei and the others haven’t felt this before. However, they’ve seen it happen. The people used to look at Shan with the same gaze, now this gaze was directed at them.

Fenglei felt that each day was like a year. Asking help from the foreign races was his decision. Even if he wanted to explain himself, he couldn’t. This was because it wouldn’t take too long before the foreign race army arrives.

Fenglei wanted to stop the Foreign Races from coming, but this was impossible. The Foreign Races wouldn’t miss this opportunity.

The internal state of the Winged Pegasus Clan was unsteady. Naturally, they weren’t able to use their full might against the O’Neal family. But fortunately for them, the O’Neal family was afraid of being baited into a trap, causing them to slow their advance. For the Winged Pegasus Clan, this was absolutely good news.

At the time when Fenglei was having his worst, Shan and Speaker Fang suddenly appeared. This time, they came with a large number of Thunder Clan and Barbarian Race soldiers.

Upon seeing the soldiers from the two clans, the Winged Pegasus Clan was shocked. This didn’t mean that they weren’t expecting the Thunder Clan and the Barbarians to appear. In fact, at this point, the majority of them knew that Shan went to the Space to look for help. Because of this, they knew that the Thunder Clan and the Barbarians would appear sooner or later. What caused their shock was the appearance of these Thunder Clan and Barbarian soldiers.

The Thunder Clan and the Barbarians weren’t very good at forging. In the past, almost all of their weapons and armor were provided by the Divine Race. However, the two clans would also need to send almost all of the ores that they mined from their plane. Because of this, majority of their weapons and armor weren’t made in high-quality. This was especially true when they rebelled against the Divine Race, their weapons and armor were beyond miserable.

But now, the armaments equipped by the two clans made the Winged Pegasus stuck in a daze. Then suddenly, Shan appeared in air outside the Palace and  loudly said, “My clansmen, I’ve invited the Barbarians and the Thunder Clan for help in bringing everyone into the Space. I will be opening the rift outside the palace. If anyone wants to enter the Space, then you can go home and pack your things. If you are still hesitating, then this rift will be open for three days before I head towards the other cities. So if you want to enter, please do it with haste!”

Shan was sitting on his mount as he shouted these words to the entire capital. His words laid everything on the table. You either follow him into the Space, or stay here and wait to be enslaved by the foreign races!

For a time, the whole Winged Pegasus capital was plunged into total silence. The Winged Pegasus were still digesting what they heard.

But after a moment, someone loudly cheered before running home. Then they quickly packed up their things and ran towards the Palace’s door.

The action of this individual was like a stone being thrown into a calm pond. The ripples of the action became bigger and bigger before everyone in the capital was seething with movement.

Almost everyone in the city ran to their homes and took their belongings. They packed their precious things and quickly ran towards the Palace.

Shan didn’t expect this situation, nor did the high-level members of the Winged Pegasus Clan. In the past, these people heavily opposed to Shan’s proposal of moving to the Space. Now, almost everyone went crazy as they ran towards the spatial rift. This was truly unexpected.

In fact, Shan didn’t know that compared to being killed and enslaved, the Winged Pegasus Clan would rather go to the Space. At the very least, Zhao Hai had always been kind to them. Even if they treated Zhao Hai badly before, Zhao Hai still didn’t retaliate against them.

These Winged Pegasus Clan were highly educated and weren’t fools. In the past, they didn’t enter the Space because they believed that their people would just do well on their own.

But when they discovered that they would be killed or enslaved if they don’t enter the Space, they immediately chose to enter the Space.

Even if Shan didn’t expect his clansmen to frantically enter the Space, the situation still made him very happy.

Fortunately, he didn’t waste his time inside the Space. He invited the Thunder Clan and the Barbarians to help him settle the Winged Pegasus who enters the Space. It can be said that the Space was fully prepared to deal with the influx of people. However, they still didn’t expect the Winged Pegasus to frantically enter.

The reason why Shan and the others were unprepared was because they weren’t aware of the current situation of the Winged Pegasus Clan. Although it can be said that the O’Neal family’s advancement wasn’t very fast, but they were still steadily advancing. Moreover, everywhere they went had been broken through. After a baptism of fire, there was basically no people left in those cities. Even if there were survivors, they were turned into either crazy people or disabled. There was no need for the O’Neal family to care about these people. In other words, the O’Neal family ravaged everywhere they went to.

Facing this enemy, the Winged Pegasus Clan were finally scared. They feared extermination and they didn’t want to be enslaved by the Foreign Races. And now that Shan and the others appeared, they were given the opportunity to save themselves. Therefore, it was natural for the Winged Pegasus to turn frantic.

With regards to the Winged Pegasus Clan’s situation, Zhao Hai was the one who had the most understanding. He expected the Winged Pegasus to enter the Space because he saw how desperate things had become in the past few days. So when Shan and the others showed up, they gave the Winged Pegasus great hope. In this case, it was natural for the Winged Pegasus to go frantic.

Although there were shortcomings in the preparation, Zhao Hai didn’t bother to remind Shan and the others since he trusted the Space. With the Space’s ability, there would be no problems in receiving the Winged Pegasus Clan. Moreover, this would also help cover up Shan’s lie. Zhao Hai would have the Winged Pegasus believe that he was impeded with other matters.

After seeing that the Winged Pegasus were basically settled, Zhao Hai began to feel relief. Then he turned his attention to Yanking City. The construction of Wolf Fang mountain had begun. The place was already settled, the next step was to start building the factory.

Bluewell was responsible for these things, so Zhao Hai didn’t have to worry about it. What he was concerned about right now was the O’Neal family. He wanted to see the current state of the family.

It can be said that the discovery of the Winged Pegasus Plane was definitely a good thing for the O’Neal family. They suddenly found a rift that led to an infinite amount of planes, and all of the materials will belong to them. This assured that the development of the Winged Pegasus Clan in the future would be limitless.

However, Zhao Hai discovered an issue. Information about the O’Neal family’s spatial rift was already possibly known by the other families.

Zhao Hai expected these families to suppress the O’Neal family upon hearing this information. But what surprised Zhao Hai was the lack of response from the other families.

After Zhao Hai asked Bluewell about this issue, he finally understood why this was the case.

In the Atlanta Plane, there were families that discovered other planes. Moreover, when they conquered these planes, they found that they obtained a lot of benefits. And this was why they didn’t attack the O’Neal family.

There was an unwritten rule among the families in the Atlanta Plane. When a family discovers a plane, the other families couldn’t suppress them. This was because these families understood if they suppress the family that discovered the plane, then when they discover their own plane in the future, they would also be suppressed. For these families, this type of things didn’t offer any advantages.

Moreover, one must know that the situation of the Magic Armor Continent wasn’t the same as the other continents. People in the Warrior and Mage Continents didn’t need a lot of ores. Their cultivation relied mainly on basic weapons and armor. On the other hand, magic armors required tons and tons of materials to make, each one equivalent to thousands of weapons and armor. The consumption of the Magic Armor Continent was several times compared to the other Continents, it might even be dozens of times.

It was impossible to rely on the Magic Armor Continent alone to supply the ores required for mass manufacturing of magic armors. So when the resources of the continent was running thin, a supply crisis emerged. In the end, unless they break open some planes, the Magic Armor continent would suffer losses. So once the magic formation for opening planes appeared, it enabled the Magic Armor Continent to forcefully conquer other planes and plunder their resources. This reinvigorated the Magic Armor Continent. Therefore, once a Family conquered another plane, it became a convention for the other families to not interfere.

Naturally, this only regards to outward suppression. Underhanded tactics was fair-play. However, even then, nobody went too far. It was because of this that the O’Neal family was still having a safe time.

After knowing about this point, Zhao Hai began to feel relief. To be honest, he didn’t want the O’Neal family to be suppressed right now. This would be disadvantageous to his current plans. At this time, Zhao Hai really wanted to see the clash between the O’Neal family and the Foreign Races.

Zhao Hai turned his gaze towards the Foreign Race army. At this point, they had already reached the Taurus Continent and were rushing towards the Winged Pegasus Plane. They wanted to control the Winged Pegasus Clan before they manage to enter the Space. If the Winged Pegasus Clan enters the Space, then what would they do to the Winged Pegasus Plane? They still haven’t done anything to the other ten continents, so why would they care about this small plane?

And the reason why the Foreign Races obtained this information was because of Fenglei’s message.  When Fenglei heard that Shan reappeared and everyone was scampering to enter the Space, he began to report everything that happened almost all the time. At this point, the Foreign Races knew almost everything going inside the Winged Pegasus Plane.

Zhao Hai had nothing to say about Fenglei’s actions. He actually sold the Winged Pegasus Clan to the Foreign Races. Zhao Hai thought about killing him, but in the end he resisted.

The speed of the Winged Pegasus when entering the Space exceeded everyone’s expectation. Just as they brought their valuables into the Space, they suddenly discovered that bringing only the good ones would suffice. This was because inside the Space, as long as you have gold coins, then you can exchange for everything you want.

When these people entered the Space, they immediately believed that Shan wasn’t deceiving them. The Space was very good, it was very nice to live in.

With the help of the Barbarians and the Thunder Clan, village after village was established. And all of the Winged Pegasus clansmen who entered the Space had smiles on their faces.

Chapter 988: Magic Armor vs Ultimate Weapon

Axe was standing on his war tank with George at his side. Then Axe turned his head to George and said, “George, how many days has it been?”

George replied, “Young Master, it’s been three days. We haven’t met those Winged Pegasus fellows for three days. Even in the cities we’ve passed through, there was still no trace of them.”

Axe let out a long breath as he muttered, “Three days, it’s really three days. George, can you also feel that this situation seems very familiar?”

When George said this, he stared for a moment. Then he turned to Axe and said, “Young Master, you mean?”

Axe replied, “Isn’t the situation here very much like the Ark Continent? The people disappeared and we don’t know where they went. This is the same as what happened to the Ark Continent.”

George nodded, “Right, just as Young Master said, it’s pretty much like back in the Ark Continent. But it’s not completely the same. Back in the Ark Continent, the inhabitants had already left for some time. But here, it seems like they had just moved out. If we speed up, then it’s possible that we would be able to see where these people moved to. But Young Master, I don’t approve to this. No matter where these people went, their action only meant that they couldn’t oppose our advance, so they withdrew. We only need the ores in this plane. But if we pursue, then it’s possible that we’d run into an ambush. If this is the opposite party’s plan, then it would be troublesome.”

Axe quietly listened to George’s words. George had been performing very well for quite some time. As a staff member, he was very qualified. After hearing George, Axe nodded and said, “Right, what you said is good. Unfortunately, if only we can find out who is the one behind the migration of these people, then we’d be able to solve the knot in our hearts. Forget it, let’s continue with what we’ve been doing. Let’s proceed with caution.”

George didn’t say anything. The army’s speed right now wasn’t very quick. So as long as they kept going at their current pace, then there won’t be any problems.

At this time, Shan was still flying around city after city to move people. Shan already told his clansmen that it was fine as long as they carry their bare minimum possessions. There was no need to carry bulky things because it would affect speed too much. Although they would need to be set-up when they go into the Space, almost all things they need could be purchased with gold coins. As long as they were willing to work, then they would never have problems inside the Space.

Because of this, Shan wasn’t worried about looking after his clansmen’s life inside the Space. He’d already asked Fei’er about this. Fei’er said that it was very cheap to live comfortably inside. Everyone can afford everything they need. And if you don’t want the Space to build you a house, then you can build one yourself. This way, you would save a lot of money.

The speed at which the Winged Pegasus clan entered the Space evidently sped up a lot. The reception inside has been very tense, but it was still being handled properly. This was mainly because nobody expected the Winged Pegasus to be this frantic.

At this point, Shan began to feel relief. While he was moving his Clansmen into the Space, he made sure to go to the place with the highest risk of being attacked. Because of this, the O’Neal family wouldn’t be meeting any Winged Pegasus member within a few days.

While Shan and his clansmen were busily moving to the Space, the Foreign Races’ reinforcing troops had arrived outside the Winged Pegasus Plane’s rift. At this time, the rift has been controlled by the O’Neal family. They had built a defensive line and left some war tank and magic armors to defend it.

An army of more than ten million was impossible to miss. Naturally, the O’Neal family was able to discover them. Upon seeing the army, the garrison troops immediately sent out requests for reinforcements. The reinforcement request was divided into two. One went to inform Axe’s group, while the other went towards the Clan’s base.

The garrison commander seems to have rich battlefield experience. Upon seeing that the enemy would be a threat, he immediately made the right choice and made adjustments to defend as long as they could.

The Foreign Race army arrived in front of the defensive line. And with almost no rest, they launched an attack at the spatial rift.

The Foreign Races anxiously attacked because of two main reasons. The first reason being that Fenglei had been constantly telling them that the Winged Pegasus were migrating quickly. And the second reason, they didn’t really care about the O’Neal family.

After Zhao Hai dealt with the Divine Race, the Foreign Races found themselves to have unprecedented confidence. In their opinion, now that the Divines were gone, nobody in this world could match them. Because of this, they didn’t put the O’Neal family in their eyes. Therefore, just as they reached the spatial rift, they immediately launched an attack without even taking a rest. And when the Foreign Races attacked, the O’Neal family also countered. Their cannons began to fire and hit the approaching army.

The Foreign Races didn’t expect such ferocious attack from the opposite party. There were a lot of people who weren’t able to get their Domain up in time and were extinguished by the incoming fire.

The O’Neal family’s attack was obviously very strong. This cannon attack was even stronger than an attack coming from a magic armor. So naturally, the Foreign Races would suffer.

Upon seeing this situation, the Foreign Races couldn’t help but look seriously at the O’Neal family. After they retreated, they didn’t immediately launch a second attack. Instead, they slowly drew back and proceeded to reorganize.

However, the O’Neal family wouldn’t give them time. The O’Neal family had already known about Domains since they fought with the Winged Pegasus Clan. They also knew that this group wasn’t good to deal with. Because of this, after the Foreign Race retreated, the O’Neal family’s magic armor immediately came out and attacked them.

The magic armor army might not be able to fight in the skies for a long time, but their strength in a short time was very powerful. Not only were they fast, they also had strong defenses and decent firepower. Therefore, the magic armors launched a lightning attack against the Foreign Races.

The magic armors changed to their aircraft forms and became bomber planes. They used the quickest speed to fly above the foreign race army before bombing them down. Then after unloading their bombs, they immediately made a sharp turn in order to avoid any direct confrontation.

The foreign race Elders didn’t expect the enemy to be this bold. They actually dared to initiate an attack. Therefore, they weren’t able to respond after being bombed on.

This made the Elders’ expressions change. Their previous attack was just a light poking. On the other hand, the O’Neal family’s counter-attack was clearly a huge slap to their faces. They couldn’t just bear to endure this.

Four Elders immediately flew out of the army before dashing towards the O’Neal family’s defensive line. After seeing four people from the enemy side coming out, the O’Neal family commander immediately knew that these four were experts. They wouldn’t dare to clash with these people so he immediately commanded war tanks, cannons, and magic armors to prepare. As long as the other party enters their range, then they would immediately pepper them with attacks.

Before long, the Elders entered the attacking range of the O’Neal family. When this happened, the O’Neal family immediately sprang to action. The garrison troops didn’t dare to treat this matter lightly. In order to deal with these four people, 50 cannons fired their shells simultaneously. The O’Neal family had such great weapons for defending. The rounds they used were of very high quality. The fifty rounds of artillery fire went straight towards four people, and they were also very accurately aimed.

But at this moment, the four experts suddenly wore full body armors. Then one of them launched lightning fast punches, sending bulls towards the approaching shells. Without even getting close to the four people, the shells were quickly decimated.

When he saw this, the garrison commander’s expression sank. He knew that he had ran into his match. He immediately made the artillery fire five or six more shots while  with the magic armors prepared. This way, they could respond to anything at any time.

The reason why he didn’t make the magic armors enter the battle this time was because if he did, then the artillery would have to stop.

The artillery fire has to stop, but it still wasn’t the time. The cannons had a certain range, not too far, and not too close. The current position of the four Foreign Race elders was at the optimum location for cannon fire. Naturally, the commander wouldn’t send his magic armors at this time.

However, the attacking strength of the four Elders have exceeded the imagination of the O’Neal family. As the cannons fired just three rounds, the Elders have already battled their way towards the defensive line, which wasn’t in the firing range of the cannons. It was at this moment that the magic armors began to be deployed.

This was the first clash between Magic Armors and the Divine Realm’s Ultimate Weapons. Altogether, the O’Neal family had deployed 50 magic armors. Sending this many people in order to deal with the four Elders shows how much vigilance the O’Neal family currently had. They sent 50 magic armors in order to keep their losses in check. Even if they couldn’t beat the enemy, at the very least they can’t have the magic armors be destroyed. One must know that the manufacturing costs of magic armors were very high. Magic armor production wasn’t a trivial matter for the O’Neal family, especially magic armors that reached God-rank.

Chapter 989: Flaw of the Ultimate Weapons

The magic armors and the Elders quickly began their battle. One has to recognize that the O’Neal family’s pilots were really excellent. The mutual cooperation between each one of them were perfect. Additionally, they can transform their magic armors at opportune times, allowing them with a wide degree of attacks. Their attacking strength was also quite good. Almost immediately, the two sides were at a stalemate.

This battle really shook both sides. The O’Neal family didn’t expect that 50 magic armors wouldn’t be able to exterminate these four experts. At the same time, the Foreign Races were also startled. They see their Supreme Elders as symbols of invincibility. Besides against the anomaly that was Zhao Hai, they haven’t seen Supreme Elders suffer a loss. They didn’t expect the enemy’s metallic men to block the Supreme Elders’ attacks.

Both sides were shocked, neither of them expected the strength of the other. At the same time, the O’Neal family also prepared to have the other magic armors substitute. They were very clear that the magic armors couldn’t fight for a long time.

But what the O’Neal family didn’t know was that the Foreign Race Supreme Elders couldn’t fight for a long time as well. Although their current combat suits were products of the Space, it still needed energy to function. With the strength of the combat suits, their energy requirement was not small. Because of this, the Supreme Elders couldn’t fight as for a long time as well.

The biggest advantage of the Space’s combat suits was its lack of backlash to the user. In the past, in addition to the immense energy required to run them, if the user can’t achieve the requirements, then they would suffer a backlash. In other words, the Divine Race’s Supreme Elders, after using the combat suits for a long time, would receive internal injuries. This was the case with Gold Ben from the Taurus Divines.

The Space’s combat suits didn’t have this disadvantage. These combat suits were now akin to a giant sword. This sword can give you a huge promotion of strength, but when you use it, it would also consume your stamina. And once you run out of strength, then this sword wouldn’t be used anymore. More importantly, this sword wouldn’t attack you if you run out of strength. At the most, it was a sword, it alone cannot injure you.

Although the current combat suits wouldn’t have any backlash, the energy required to use them was still quite big. Even if they were Supreme Elders, using these combat suits for a long time was impossible.

Actually, this disadvantage was left behind by Zhao Hai. The combat suits that he handed over had more problems compared to the ones that the Space was using; such as an over excessive consumption of energy. The combat suits used by Zhao Hai also had problems in energy consumption, but they weren’t as severe as the ones used by the foreign races.

Zhao Hai discovered that these people from Foreign Races have no sense of gratitude and were always wary of him. Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t give them good things, he wasn’t stupid.

Zhao Hai was such a person, if he treated you right and you didn’t return the sentiment, then he wouldn’t be polite to you. He wouldn’t discuss his plans with you anymore.

The Space has the Scanner and the Processing Machine to help Zhao Hai with his life. Although the combat suits have been planted, Zhao Hai used the Scanner and the Processing Machine to modify them a bit before handing them over to the foreign races. Because of this, these combat suits weren’t as good as the ones used in the Space.

The four Foreign Race Supreme Elders were aware about their limitation, so after clashing with the enemy for some time, they chose to draw back.

As the four Supreme Elders retreated, the O’Neal family’s magic armors drew back as well. To be honest, the pressure that they felt was really big. Fortunately, they were all experienced fighters, so they made zero mistakes. Otherwise, the consequences would really be unimaginable.

So far, the two sides had been acquainted with the others’ power, so nobody attacked. The foreign races needed to rest. Meanwhile, although the garrison troops didn’t need to rest, they still need to write a report about this situation and then have it sent back to the family.

In the past, they never thought that there were people so strong that four of them could block the attack of 50 God-rank magic armors. Fortunately, the other side didn’t seem to have a lot of those kinds of experts.

But what both sides didn’t know was the fact that Zhao Hai had seen the entirety of their battle. After seeing the performance of the O’Neal family’s 50 magic armors, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but nod. The coordination between the 50 magic armors was really great. Their attack and defensive maneuvers didn’t have any point of mistake. Doing this wasn’t an easy matter.

As the two sides drew back to their own camps, Zhao Hai turned his head to Laura and the others and said, “It looks like the Atlanta Plane is really extraordinary. Four Supreme Elders in their combat suits could actually be blocked by 50 God-rank magic armors. At the same time, it seems like these God-rank magic armors are more formidable than God-rank Experts. They seem to be close to the peak of power.”

Laura nodded and said, “I also didn’t expect the magic armors to be that strong. From what i can see, the Foreign Race reinforcement wouldn’t be able to do anything to the O’Neal family.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Isn’t that great? If they have no way to deal with the O’Neal family, then they would ask for help. When the time comes, the Foreign Race would definitely send support. As for the O’Neal family, it seems like they don’t have a lot of God-rank magic armors. Now, I want to see what kind of magic armor the O’Neal family would send if they suffer huge losses here.”

Then Lizzy added, “The O’Neal family would certainly want to deal with the Foreign Races. With how they intend to rule the Divine Realm, the O’Neal would surely find the Foreign Races as their archenemy. And seeing how they handle things, the O’Neal family wouldn’t treat them as friends.”

Zhao Hai nodded, even he didn’t expect the O’Neal family to be so ruthless. Almost all of the Winged Pegasus cities that they came upon were left with no survivors. This caused Zhao Hai to feel puzzled, don’t they need any slaves?

But what Zhao Hai didn’t know, in the Magic Armor Continent, major families who conquered a plane rarely took slaves. This was because  these planes were mainly practicing either magic or martial arts. Such people were hard to conquer, and even if they were captured, there were little use for them. After all, the strongest means of attack in the Magic Armor Continent were magic armors.

If the people from the Magic Armor Continent were out of their magic armors, then they would have almost no fighting power. On the other hand, most of the people in those planes were physically strong. And with the magic armor pilots not being able to wear their magic armors everyday, if the people from the lower planes attacks them, then the consequences would be unimaginable. So for their own safety, the people from the magic armor continent wouldn’t accept slaves.

Additionally, most of the heavy work in the Magic Armor Continent were done using magic armors. Their working efficiency was higher than average people by many times. Therefore, they simply didn’t need slaves.

At this time, Lizzy said, “The O’Neal family naturally had stronger means, but they just haven’t used it yet. Perhaps their stronger method is the same as the Divine Race’s combat suits, they would need to pay a price in order to use it. As long as the Foreign Races compel them to a certain point, then the O’Neal family would certainly use them.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “The Foreign Races are certainly enough to push the O’Neal family. Although magic armors are formidable, they also have their weak point. If the pilots want to rest, then they need to come out of their magic armors. During war time, they have to do this every time they rest. Although they had practiced for so long and had this transition time reduced significantly, they would still suffer under the Foreign Races who were good to go all the time. Moreover, the Foreign Races are rich with fighting experience. They might not understand magic armors for now, but after being in a stalemate for a long time, they would eventually find this weakness. When that time comes, the O’Neal family would certainly suffer a loss. They would need greater strength in order to get an advantage in the war.”

Lizzy nodded, “Right. Because of this, I’m quite sure that the O’Neal family would use stronger means. But Brother Hai, you need to pay attention. Commanding magic armors to war isn’t the same as commanding ordinary people. In the future, when we have our own magic armors, we need to train good commanders.”

When Zhao Hai heard Lizzy, he couldn’t help but stare. He hadn’t thought about this point, but Lizzy reminded him about this important matter. So he nodded and said, “It seems like we’ll look for an opportunity to get Undead creatures from the Atlanta Plane.”

Lizzy smiled faintly and said, “Although the Undead are very intelligent, they still fall short compared to living people, perhaps its because of their insufficient experience. So Brother Hai, I think we should get some people from the Atlanta Plane if we want to create a magic armor army. I don’t think we should go for undead.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, I’ll listen to you. I’ll pay attention to this matter. Now that the Foreign Races have clashed with the O’Neal family, I’m certain that Axe would return. This would give Shan time to move his clan in the next few days. And after all the Winged Pegasus moved, we can finally be relieved about this matter.”

Laura smiled and added, “Brother Hai, what do you think about inviting the Dwarves over to the Space? Their impression of you is very good. Moreover, there are no problems with their recent performance and moral behaviour. Having them in the Space would give great benefits to us.”

Chapter 990: Preparations For A Night Assault

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and then he said, “If you want to try, you can tell Ryder about it. If it’s successful, then that would be the best. If it isn’t, then it’s fine. We already have quite an amount of people inside the Space.”

Laura smiled and said, “The more people we have inside the Space, the better. We have dozens of backgrounds, but the ones we truly use is actually less than ten. It’s such a waste.”

Zhao Hai smiled and replied, “Don’t worry, let’s just take our time. Sooner or later we will make use of them. Right, do you want to go back to the Space to have a look?”

Laura and the others knew what this meant. He wanted to go back to Wild Dragon Island to see how the place was doing.

Naturally, they wouldn’t decline Zhao Hai’s decision, so they entered the Space with Zhao Hai and went to Wild Dragon Island. There was no need to discuss the island’s situation, the laboratory was doing really well. In order to speed up the research, Zhao Hai got a few computers from the science and technology background and improved them using the processing machine. Then he handed them over to Karen and the others to use. This made their work much more efficient.

While Zhao Hai and the others were relaxing inside the Space for the day, Axe and the others weren’t having a great time. They had received the report from the defensive line describing the attack. These days, they had been steady and weren’t going very fast. And this time, they suddenly received this request for help. As soon as the letter landed on Axe’s hand, Axe couldn’t help but be surprised.

Axe was very clear, now that they were inside this plane, if the rift was sealed up, then that would be equal to them being choked to death. This wasn’t a good development. Because of this, Axe immediately looked for the Generals who came with him.

These Generals were old members of the O’Neal family. Even the O’Neal family’s Patriarch would give them some face. Because of this, Axe needs to discuss this matter with these people.

After waiting for these Generals to arrive inside his War Tank, Axe presented the letter on the table as he looked at these officers and said, “I just received a report from the defensive line. An army has suddenly appeared outside this plane. It seems like there are millions of soldiers. Everyone have a look, what do you think?”

Upon hearing Axe, the expression of those present changed. One of them immediately stood up and said, “Young Lord, we’re currently inside a plane with enemies inside. If we let people block our exit, then we’ll end up being surrounded on both ends. That wouldn’t be good. Young Lord, we should get back right away.”

Every commander present nodded. Axe nodded as well as he said, “I also know about this. But I believe that we should return in batches. We will send a group of magic armors back first as we slowly draw back. So even if those inside this place counter-attacks, then we would have some people to block them. In this case, we wouldn’t fall into a situation where we get our backs attacked. What do you think?”

As soon as they heard Axe, these commanders were a little surprised. To be honest, they weren’t convinced of Axe before. After all, Axe hadn’t commanded a battle in the past. But after this time’s attack, they became relieved. Axe’s commanding capabilities were quite satisfactory, and he hasn’t made any mistakes. Because of this, they didn’t raise any objections nor did they neglect giving him face. After all, Axe was the son of the Patriarch, it wasn’t a good idea to offend him.

And this time, the plan that Axe proposed made them a little stunned. It wasn’t the plan, per se, the plan can be said to be alright. But for a newcomer in the battlefield, Axe keeping a calm mind in this situation showed his character. This was what made these people surprised.

However, they didn’t react too much as they just agreed to Axe’s plan. Axe then proceeded to assigned tasks. He left behind the majority of War Tanks and some magic armors. As for the remaining magic armors, all of them were going to be sent back to the defensive line. To speed up the return of the magic armors, Axe made the magic armors bring energy converters with them. With this, they would be able to fly for a long time.

The method that Axe was doing was generally used on magic armors dedicated to sending letters. These magic armors would carry multiple energy converters so that the pilot could replace them while on the go. This would make their travel quick. Naturally, this tactic wasn’t suitable for a long-distance attack. It was because this method would make the magic armor pilot extremely fatigued, it will affect their fighting strength.

However, the situation this time was different. This was because they needed to support the defensive line. As long as their magic armors were able to reach the defensive line, then their pilots could just rest there before they can be mobilized for battle. Additionally, the defensive line wasn’t very far, so Axe was able to use this method.

Axe didn’t head back with the magic armors. He took charge commanding the main army to slowly retreat. It was George who went with the reinforcing magic armor troop.

Axe’s current situation was unknown to Shan. At this time, he was still moving his people to the space. The situation didn’t change from before.

But the same cannot be said about the Foreign Race camp. They were actually anxious. Although most of them were taking a rest, there were some who cannot fall asleep. They didn’t expect the enemy to be able to block their Supreme Elders. The influence of this event to their morale was quite significant.

The foreign races were somewhat like the Divines, they too worship the power of their Supreme Elders. They held great belief towards their ultimate weapons. In their eyes, once their Supreme Elders use their ultimate weapons, then there wasn’t anything that they couldn’t solve. This worship wasn’t brought about in one or two days, it was a mindset that was passed down through tens of thousands of years, it was almost carved into their bones.

This sense of worship both had its advantages and disadvantages. As long as there was a Supreme Elder present, then an army’s fighting spirit would be amplified, strengthening the army by an explosive 120%. Naturally, the disadvantage was an obvious one. If their Supreme Elder gets entangled with something, then the morale would fatally drop.

Now, after seeing the Supreme Elders not being able to deal with the metallic men, the morale of the Foreign Race army would surely be affected.

The Supreme Elders have also noted this situation. Of these Supreme Elders, one of them was the original Supreme Elder of the Beastman Race, the other three had just been promoted when their race gained new ultimate weapons. Compared to the three Supreme Elders, the original Beastman Supreme Elder had the greatest fighting strength.

Combat suits were like weapons, and each weapon had its own characteristic. If one uses a weapon for a lifetime, then the weapon would eventually become part of one’s body. On the other hand, if one just had their hands on a weapon, then even if this weapon was strong, it was impossible for the person to display its real capabilities in a short time. The same was the case for combat suits.

The three had just obtained their combat suits and became Supreme Elders of the Beastman and the Elven Races. Although obtaining the combat suits made them powerful, they were still yet to utilize the combat suits’ abilities completely. Because of this, compared to the original Beastman Supreme Elder, they still fall short. Naturally, this group of Supreme Elders were headed by that Beastman Supreme Elder.

Sitting in the room, the original Beastman Supreme Elder’s expression had sunk. This room was made by magic, the furniture and anything else was made by magic as well. Then a layer of beast skin was placed on top of the floor. In this plain, this condition wasn’t bad at all.

The Beastman Elder looked at the other three and said, “You three, the enemy this time doesn’t bode well for us. Tell me what you think?”

The three elders turned silent. To be honest, the O’Neal family’s performance today made them very startled. They didn’t know any method to deal with them at this time.

The Beastmen Elder looked at the three’s reaction and understood what they were thinking. He couldn’t blame them for being silent, even he didn’t have any means of dealing with them right now. However, the situation needed to be changed.

The Beastman Elder continued, “The army we faced are definitely the ones attacking the Winged Pegasus Clan. Moreover, those we clashed with are merely their garrison troops. If their garrison troops are this hard to deal with, our troubles would be bigger once their main army comes back. Because of this, I think we should recuperate our energies and carry an attack during the night. Let’s see how they fight during nighttime. If their nighttime combat capabilities are still very strong, then we can only make a hard attack tomorrow. If they couldn’t fight well at night, then we will fight it out during nighttime.”

The other Supreme Elders nodded. This time, the four Supreme Elders led an army of 20 million. They had just made contact with their enemy, so they couldn’t just retreat. If they did, then they would have no face left, so they had no choice but launch another assault.

When he saw the three Elders agree, the Beastman Supreme Elder nodded and said, “Since you agree, then you should go back to rest. We will act at night.” The three nodded before bowing to the Beastman Supreme Elder and leaving.

When the three Elders left, the Beastman Supreme Elder also called the army Generals in. The lead General was a Beastman. Naturally, the Elves also had their own General, so the Supreme Elder called two Generals in.

After the two entered the room and exchanged greetings, the Supreme Elder said, “I called you two here to tell you that us four Supreme Elders will be attacking this evening. You need to prepare and see if they manage to adapt to nighttime battle. When we leave, go follow behind us. If the other party isn’t comfortable with fighting in the night, then you will immediately launch an attack. Even if we cannot take their defensive line, we can still make them suffer a loss. Don’t send a lot of people in this attack. The defensive line is huge, taking too many people would be useless. As for how many to bring, I’ll leave that to you.”

The two nodded. Then the Beastman Supreme Elder waved his hand, making them leave. The Beastman Supreme Elder slowly closed his eyes and controlled his breathing. He needed to be in optimum condition later because the other party was very strong. Especially those magic armors, their fighting strength was very good.

The day slowly turned dark, and Axe’s reinforcement troops had yet to arrive. The entire defensive line was brilliantly illuminated. The defensive line was powered with energy converters, allowing the garrison troops to set up a lot of search lights. They didn’t stop staring outside the defensive line. They were afraid that the foreign races would make a night assault.

Naturally, the O’Neal family had certain means to deal with a nighttime assault. However, although their magic armors can fight at night, they weren’t as comfortable as during the day. This would affect the fighting strength of the magic armors. Because of this, they had to resort to such means in order to fight in darkness.

Before 1 o’clock at night, the surrounding area was silent, the foreign races had yet to move. A short while after 1 o’clock, the four Supreme Elders began to make their move towards the defensive line. At the same time, the Elves and Beastmen prepared 100 thousand troops to follow behind. The Elves brought 30 thousand while the Beastman took 70 thousand. Among the 70 thousand Beastmen, 30 thousand of them were from the Rat Tribe, 20 thousand from the Cat tribe, and the last 20 thousand came from the Wolf tribe. These were the races that were the most suitable for stealth.

There were no distinction between War Clans and other Tribes in the Beastman race here. They advanced from 1st to 9th rank and the become God-rank experts. And no matter which race, the disparity between their fighting strength wasn’t very big. Because of this, there were no such thing as War Clans nor Slave Races in the Divine Realm’s Beastman race.

On the other hand, the 30 thousand Elves were all archers. Even if they become God-ranks, they still need to have a discipline they focus on. For example, there were some Elves who prefer swords while some wanted to use bows and arrows, and there were also those who use magic. This time, the 30 thousand troops all used bows and arrows.

Although it can be said that the O’Neal clan’s defense was very dense, it wasn’t enough to intimidate the four Supreme Elders as well as the stealth troops. There was needless to say but the four Supreme Elders were very fast. The same was also true for the stealth troops. However, they couldn’t be hasty or else they would be detected by the O’Neal family. After all, the family’s search lights weren’t just mere ornaments.

The four Supreme Elders quickly entered the area covered by the defensive line. But they were able to quickly discover that the O’Neal family had set-up some early warning systems. The four Elders focused their energies in order to avoid these alarms. But the closer the went towards the defensive line, the more warning devices they encountered. It was inevitable for the group to slow down.

The group carefully moved forward, getting closer and closer to the defensive line. They were now able to attack, but they chose not to. They wouldn’t be able to obtain a huge victory this way. Therefore, they went closer to the defensive line before making an attack.

Chapter 991: Huge Light Bulb

Weng! A grating sound along with flashes of red light resounded inside the camp. This made the entire O’Neal family camp burst into action. Those who were veterans in battles knew very well what the sound and lights meant, the enemy came to attack!

One has to recognize that with regards to understanding magic formations, the Atlanta Plane completely trumps the Divine Race. And even then, the Foreign Races still fall short compared to the Divines when it came to magic formations. Because of this, it was impossible for them to discover all of the warnings that were arranged by the O’Neal family.

For the Supreme Elders to reach one kilometer into the defensive line’s range was already a miracle. If they didn’t have formidable sense, then they might have already been discovered a long time ago.

When the four Supreme Elders heard this sound, they immediately knew that they were discovered. So immediately, they stopped hiding and directly flew upwards. They already put their combat suits on as they went towards the O’Neal family’s defensive line.

Just as the four flew up, beams of light began to shoot up from the O’Neal family’s camp. Then more and more of these beams began to light upon the elders.

The four Elders made shields for themselves. They didn’t bother evading the beams as they just flew quickly towards the defensive line.

At this time, 50 magic armors went out of the O’Neal family’s defensive line and met with the Supreme Elders. Then almost all of the searchlights in the camp were directed at the same time.

At this moment, an innumerable amount of arrows began to fly out of the darkness. These arrows weren’t shot towards the magic armors but instead they were heading towards the lamps. Several bangs were heard as the searchlights were shot down. The night immediately turned darker, plunging the Supreme Elders into darkness once more.

Such change made the people in the O’Neal family camp stare. However, they were still soldiers with experience of a hundred battles. They were quick to respond as they quickly set up a protective shield. This time, it was the foreign races who stared, they haven’t seen such a protective shield before.

It was a white semi-spherical shield with no special characteristics to it. However, when it was set-up, the entire shield lit up like a huge light bulb, sending white fluorescence everywhere.

This wasn’t something that the foreign races had met before. Protective shields could also light up? What is happening?

Actually, the foreign races didn’t know, but this shining protective shield wasn’t a significant matter. The Magic Armor Continent where the O’Neal family were situated in had been fighting against the Warrior and Mage Continents for who knows how many years. Therefore, they were very knowledgeable about Warrior attacks like this one. They knew each others’ weak points and were striving to improve upon them.

And just as the Beastman Supreme Elder thought, the O’Neal family’s magic armors weren’t very suitable for nighttime battles. During the night, the magic armors would lose some combat power because of the lack of light. In this case, what would happen if the enemy launched an evening attack? In the very beginning, they used searchlights to counteract this weakness. But after the searchlights were destroyed several times and causing the Magic Armor Continent to eat a few losses, they began to think of other methods. And in the end, they were able to invent a magical formation that makes a shield that illuminates. This magic formation wasn’t anything special, it was just an ordinary defensive magic formation with a few additions of light producing magic formations. But due to this modification, the energy consumed by the entire shield had increased by a lot.

But still, the discovery of this magic formation made the entire Magic Armor Continent’s nighttime capabilities improve by a qualitative leap. Magic armors still weren’t good with nighttime battles, but with the addition of the magic formation, even if they cannot make a strong attack, at the very least they could still defend their camp.

At this time, the situation with the defensive line was the same. The illuminated defensive magic formation restored the flexibility of the magic armors. They arranged into formations once more and tangled with the four Supreme Elders.

Meanwhile,. the cannons and war tanks of the defensive line weren’t idling. The moment the searchlights were attacked, the O’Neal family immediately knew that the enemy wasn’t just one or two. Therefore, their cannons aimed towards the direction where the arrows came from. It was a covering fire, a completely indiscriminate firing method. No matter who was hiding, if one was unlucky, then they would be obliterated. At the most, the O’Neal family would just waste a couple of shells.

This kind of attack was used by the O’Neal family repeatedly against the enemies in the Warrior and Mage Continent. All of their soldiers would identify the direction the arrows were coming from before peppering the region with cannon shells.

One shouldn’t think that it was just a careless and relaxed action. Each O’Neal family soldier were strictly trained and taught matters of the battlefield. Moreover, they made repeated trials in order to make the most accurate shot as possible.

The Foreign Race army didn’t expect a swift counter-attack by the O’Neal family. Just as they were stunned by this matter, the cannon shells began to rain down upon them.

One shouldn’t underestimate the might of these shells. In the Atlanta Plane, both the Warrior Continent and the Mage Continent never lacked any experts. And both of the continents had combat power no worse than the Foreign Races. If the weapons made by the Magic Armor Continent had no way to harm these people, then the Magic Armor Continent would have long since been destroyed by the other two continents.

The O’Neal family’s attacks were very fast, cannons fired one after another, making the Foreign Race soldiers eat cannon shells. This time, they dispatched 100 thousand people to mount a sneak attack. But they didn’t think that they would be met by a violent counter-attack. This rain of cannons shells had beaten them until there were only 30 thousand of them left..

At this time, more magic armors flew out from the camp. Part of them went towards the four Supreme Elders while the others protected the skies above the camp. Nobody went around to patrol. Since the shells still costs a lot of money, the cannons only fired for another five rounds before all of them stopped.

Upon looking at this situation, the Supreme Elders knew that tonight’s sneak attack was impossible to accomplish. They began to slowly retreat. But at this time, explosion sounds were suddenly heard from the direction of the Foreign Races’ camp. Upon hearing this sound, the four Supreme Elder stared before the quickly retreated from the magic armor encirclement. They knew that they had just been attacked. As for who did it, there was no need to think about it, it was surely the O’Neal family.

When they thought about this, they became even more worried. The people from the O’Neal family had good fighting prowess. At this time, the camp had no way to contend against them. If the O’Neal family sent troops to the camp, then the situation would become dangerous very soon.

Upon returning to the camp along with the stealth army, the four Supreme Elders found that the O’Neal family also retreated. Although they were angry, they were also relieved.

At the same time, the O’Neal family welcomed the reinforcements. This one was completely comprised of magic armors, and their leader was George.

George received Axe’s order to lead the first wave of magic armor reinforcements. Besides the time they changed energy converters, they spent their entire time flying straight towards the defensive line.

But when they arrived, George discovered that they were being attacked by the Foreign Races. The pilots who were with him wanted to offer their support, however, George didn’t agree.

They had been flying for a good several hours, they were physically and mentally exhausted. It would be useless for them to enter the fight this time, it might even be possible for them to suffer a small loss. Naturally, George didn’t want to see that situation. Therefore, George led the magic armors to attack the Foreign Race camp instead of attacking the Supreme Elders.

The Foreign Race camp wasn’t jet black dark. There were magical lamps being lit up in all directions. It can be said that the camp was adequately illuminated. Naturally, George and the others were able to spot them easily. George wasn’t polite as he immediately ordered to launch a small wave of bombs before they retreat.

He knew that this kind of attack wouldn’t be able to do anything to the Foreign Race army, but he can affirm that after seeing their own camp being attacked, then the Supreme Elders would surely go back and help them. As long as these people retreat, then the defensive line’s crisis would be solved. Moreover, their exhausted pilots would then be able to take a good rest.

George’s timely return to help the defensive line made the garrison troops feel relief. The defenders here weren’t a lot while the other party was a twenty million-strong army. Such pressure made the garrison commander feel a headache. Fortunately, George and his men arrived.

The lively evening passed just like that. The Foreign Races’ evening attack didn’t yield the result that was expected. Moreover, they had suffered some losses. But generally speaking, this allowed the foreign races to have a certain understanding about their enemy’s strength. This would provide some advantages in their later fight.

After the four Supreme Elders returned to the camp, the soldiers who were left behind began to feel relief. Although they had been attacked, these people were veterans, they didn’t take it too heavily. When the destroyed places were cleaned up, everything went back to normal.

Chapter 992: The Suppression Has Started!

Zhao Hai was currently inside the Space, looking at the restored calmness on both camps. Then he turned to his side to Laura and said, “It seems like we should find someone from the Atlanta Plane. Magic armors and ordinary armies are indeed two different things.”

Laura nodded and said, “I really didn’t expect it, the O’Neal family are really powerful. The attacks made by the Foreign Races have been destroyed by them. Judging by what I can see, it would be very hard for the Foreign Races to break through this defensive line.”

After hearing this, Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I don’t think so. The O’Neal family has yet to capture the advantage. Don’t forget, the Foreign Races haven’t encountered anything like this before. Now that they have experienced the O’Neal family’s methods, they would surely find ways to deal with them. Additionally, they have the population advantage. I reckon tomorrow, the real trouble for the O’Neal family will arrive.”

Laura gently knit his eyebrows and said, “Are you sure? The O’Neal family’s cannons are very strong.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The cannons are indeed strong, but they have their own characteristic. If it is against enemies on the ground, then there’s no need to dispute how strong they are. However, the Foreign Races can attack in the air. As long as they don’t use formations when they advance, then the cannons’ lethality would be reduced.”

Laura nodded. The individual skills of the Foreign Races were much better compared to the Divine Race. If it wasn’t for these skills, then it would have been impossible for them to block the Divine Race’s attacks.

The Foreign Races suffered losses before because they had zero understanding about the O’Neal family. They were unaware about what the magic armors and cannons did. But once they’re introduced to these things, then the Foreign Races would be able to formulate methods to deal with them. When the time comes, the O’Neal family would have worse days.

After seeing that both sides had gone to rest, Zhao Hai exhaled. Then he turned to Laura and said, “We’ll take a rest as well. I’m sure none of them would retreat tomorrow. When we get up, we can still watch them. And after Shan had all of the Winged Pegasus Clan move into the Space, we can have Ryder go to the Dwarves. And then when that is finished, we can proceed to take a look at the Underworld.”

Laura nodded, “Right. We should go to the Underworld and see the situation. At the same time, we can also receive more Undead, they’ve always given us huge advantages.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Then he led Laura to take a rest. Actually, Zhao Hai’s main focus in going to the Underworld was to take a look at the person behind the Dark Temple. If that person wasn’t Lu Wei, then Zhao Hai can confirm his own suspicion. The Underworld, Divine Realm, and the Atlanta Plane were all controlled by different people from the Cultivation Realm. Which plane he chooses to ascend in would dictate which faction he would join.

This matter was very important to Zhao Hai. As long as he confirmed this point, then he would have a choice instead of being passive like he was doing right now. After all, he has offended Lu Wei, an Elder-level character in a Big Cultivation Realm faction.

While Zhao Hai and the others rested, Shan was still very busy. This time, the movement to the Space wasn’t only happening during the day. Even at night, he still wanted to make his people move. He wants the migration to end as soon as possible. Only after everyone was safe would Shan feel relief.

The next day, Shan and the others had finally taken the Winged Pegasus into the Space. And Shan was finally able to let out a long breath. Also, Shan didn’t make it difficult for Fenglei’s group to enter the Space. Because of this, at this moment, besides magic beasts, nobody was left inside the Winged Pegasus Plane.

When Fenglei entered the Space, he initially wanted to tell the Foreign Races about the current situation. However, he suddenly discovered that his messenger fish had lost its function. At the same time, as soon as he entered the Space, Fenglei was suddenly grasped by an invisible force and was sent to a closed small dark room. There were things to eat inside that room, drinks to quench his thirst, as well as a place for sleeping. But besides all of that, there was nothing else. Everything was black, moreover, nothing could be heard in the surroundings.

Lonely, depressing, it seems like the world was so far away. This feeling almost made Fenglei turn crazy. He began to destroy everything as well as yelling as loud as he could. However, not even an echo was heard back. Every sound coming out from his mouth seems to be eaten by the surrounding darkness.

He wanted to walk around, but he was not able to go beyond the five square meters of space. He also wanted to destroy the area, but an invisible energy was making it impossible.

However, back when Fenglei was captured, he was able to hear a voice announcing his sins. His sins were betraying his clansmen as well as trying to betray the Space. Because of this, his punishment was half a month of time inside the dark room.

For the first five days, Fenglei vented out as though he was crazy. He did everything he could, even the food and water were destroyed.

But his struggles were useless. After the food and water were destroyed, although they wouldn’t restore immediately, after some time, they would mysteriously come back. Moreover, these meals would come three times a day, always at the same time.

He also wanted to kill himself. Whenever he had this thought, he discovered that he would lose his ability to move. He can only rotate his eyebrows, the other parts of his body would simply stop cooperating.

After five days, Fenglei looked shaggy. The thing he did everyday after that was sitting there in a daze. He would eat when he was hungry and he would drink when he’s thirsty. He thought about going on a hunger strike, but it was useless. Whenever he chose to starve himself, he would once again lose his strength while the food and water would turn into a disgusting mulch. Then his mouth would open as this mulch enters it. In any case, he could never starve.

At this point, Fenglei abandoned all hopes of killing himself. He knew that he couldn’t die at this place. Therefore, what he did everyday was be in a daze. Sometimes he would reflect on things he has done before, and sometimes he would just clear his head, not thinking of anything else. Only then could he stop himself from going mad.

After 15 days, Fenglei suddenly discovered that he was once again among his clansmen. He appeared as mysteriously as he disappeared. He didn’t know when he appeared, but when he saw his clansmen, he suddenly cried. He discovered the first time how beautiful his people were. These people weren’t chess pieces, they were simply his clansmen.

While Fenglei was trapped inside the little dark room, the battle between the Foreign Races and the O’Neal family went on. As Zhao Hai previously thought, the Foreign Race were finally able to understand the O’Neal family. After eating two more losses, the Foreign Races began to make adjustments to their tactics. Their formations became more open and they weren’t attacking in secret anymore. Instead they went by waves, after one attack was finished, another one would begin. In this case, the effectiveness of the O’Neal family’s cannons became lower. However, the cannon attacks still couldn’t be underestimated. And with the help of the magic armors, the Foreign Races still had no way to take the defensive line.

After knowing that Shan had moved his people into the Space, Zhao Hai began to feel relief. At the same time, he carried out the next step of his plan. He delivered Ryder to the Libra Continent and had him see Leir.

Leir wasn’t having great days recently. He didn’t want to be Zhao Hai’s enemy. He was a Dwarf, and Dwarves knew how to repay favors. Not only him, almost all of the Dwarves didn’t agree to dispatching troops. Because of this, of the three races, only the Beastmen and Elves sent troops. The Dwarves didn’t even send their Supreme Elders. This was under Leir’s decision.

He knew that he would definitely offend the Beastmen and the Elves with this action. However, he didn’t regret his decision, he was a proud member of the Dwarven Race.

Leir also knew that the moment he rejected dispatching troops, a fissure would be formed between the Foreign Races. Moreover, compared to the united Elves and Beastmen, the Dwarves could be said to be weak. Their future definitely wouldn’t be better.

However, Leir was already mentally prepared for this. Currently, the Dwarven Race also had four ultimate weapons. He didn’t believe that the Elves and the Beastmen would dare to go all out against them. If they dared to do so, then the Dwarves certainly didn’t lack in brave warriors who would go all out.

Leir didn’t have an ounce of regret. He knew that this was what being a Dwarf meant. However, this decision wasn’t something he casually decided on. He gave this decision a very thorough thought.

Leir wasn’t like Solomon and Yerd who were bent on uniting everything into one rule. Although the Dwarves were known for their bad temper, they weren’t ambitious people. For them, hammering metals was more interesting than killing. All they want to do was hammer metals, not rule other people.

Recognizing grace and grievances was the Dwarven Race’s most precious tradition. This tradition allowed the Dwarves to gain a lot of friends. It can be said that the current Dwarven Race was brought up by this tradition. Because of this, the Dwarves couldn’t lose this tradition.

Although it would bring the Dwarves further troubles, in order to protect this tradition, Leir didn’t agree to dispatch troops. To Leir, in spite of the consequences, it was all worth it.

Leir was currently inside his room, looking at the document in front of him. Written on this document was the Dwarves Race’s recent food deficit. Leir knew that the Beastmen and the Elves had started their suppression.

Placing the report down on the table, Leir let out a long sigh. He calculated the time and then muttered, “At this time, have they gotten those people in control?”

Then, at this moment, a voice was suddenly heard from outside, “Patriarch, Ryder is seeking an audience.”

Chapter 993: Divine Dwarf Race

Leir stared, he didn’t expect to hear Ryder’s name at this time. In the past, Ryder didn’t have any impression on him. But ever since he came in contact with Zhao Hai, Ryder’s name began to appear frequently.

But ever since Zhao Hai destroyed the Divine Race, the name vanished. When Leir recalled Ryder and wanted to look for him, the person had already disappeared.

Although there was no evidence, Leir knew that Ryder chose to follow Zhao Hai along with Bingya and Yehta. These three had the most contact with Zhao Hai, and they chose to follow him in the end.

Leir wasn’t like Solomon who became angry upon hearing this information. On the contrary, Leir pondered why. Why would they give up their clansman in order to follow an outsider like Zhao Hai?

In the end, Leir reached a conclusion. All of it was because of Zhao Hai. For Ryder and the others, Zhao Hai was a person worth following.

Leir didn’t express this conclusion to Solomon and Yerd. This was because Leir discovered that the current Beastmen and Elves were different than what they were before. In the past, although the Elves were arrogant, their pursuit of art was unmatched. Although the Beastmen were uncouth, their appreciation for self-improvement was also very strong. But now, Leir saw in the eyes of the Beastmen and the Elves something that he could only see from the Divine Race, ambition!

Both Beastmen and Elves had eyes shaded with ambition. Now, they desired slaves and had lost their conscience. Because of this, Leir decided to not tell them this conclusion. He knew that they wouldn’t listen even if he did.

The Elves had started to suppress the grain that they were sending the Dwarves. Because of this, it’s possible that the Dwarves would enter a food crisis. However, Leir didn’t want to admit defeat despite of this. The Elven Race would need weapons produced by the Dwarves. If they don’t provide grain, then they won’t be getting weapons.

However, Leir knew that this mentality wouldn’t last for a long time. In the end, the Dwarves would still suffer a loss. This was because people wouldn’t have a choice but to eat their meals. And at this moment, Ryder suddenly appeared.

But why would he appear now? What does he want to do? Or to say it accurately, what does Zhao Hai want to do? Leir knew that Ryder appearing here would surely be connected to Zhao Hai.

When he thought of this, Leir immediately said, “Have him come in.” The person on the door complied and before long Ryder was inside Leir’s room.

Ryder gave Leir a salute and said, “This one has seen the Patriarch.”

Leir looked at Ryder and said, “Ryder, did Mister send you here? If so, then what does Mister want?”

Ryder smiled faintly and said, “Just like the Patriarch said, Mister had me come here. Mister wants to invite the Patriarch to move the entire Dwarf Race to his Space.”

Leir’s two eyes shrunk. However, he didn’t jump to angrily rebuking Ryder, instead he looked straight into Ryder’s eyes and asked, “Ryder, are you still a Dwarf?”

Ryder’s body shook gently, then he gave an affirmative nod and said, “I am a Dwarf, and forever will be!”

Leir nodded, then he said, “So answer me honestly. As a fellow Dwarf, do you think that entering Mister Zhao Hai’s Space would make our race’s situation much better than it is now?”

Ryder didn’t even think as he gave a strong nod and said, “Yes. It will definitely be better than now. I can guarantee this promise!”

Leir looked at Ryder’s face, and for quite a while he couldn’t reach a decision. After some time he nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll go look for the clan’s Elders. However, if Mister Zhao Hai could come out, then it would be much better for us to have him personally discuss this matter”

And without even waiting for Ryder to speak, Zhao Hai’s voice was heard, “Since Patriarch wants to see me, then I wouldn’t dare to decline.” After hearing this, Ryder saw a spatial rift appearing in front of him. Then from the other side, Zhao Hai walked out. Zhao Hai gave Leir a salute and said, “Zhao Hai has seen the Patriarch.”

Leir saw Zhao Hai and stood up. He gave Zhao Hai a bow and said, “Leir has seen Mister. Mister, please have a seat.” Zhao Hai smiled and then sat down on the chair next to him.

Leir looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister has been listening to our conversation?”

Zhao Hai didn’t cover anything up, he nodded and said, “Yes. This matter is too important, it’s impossible for me to not pay attention. I hope the Patriarch can forgive me for not coming here directly to present the matter. I don’t know how the Patriarch would receive the suggestion, so I had Ryder try to see your reaction.”

Leir nodded, he liked Zhao Hai’s honest manner. He looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Why would Mister want the Dwarves inside your Space? After entering the Space, what can the Dwarven Race get?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I want to have the Dwarves enter the Space because I like the Dwarves. Among the three Foreign Races, only the Dwarves had thought about the favor I gave them. I know that the Dwarves are like the Dwarves in the Ark Continent, so I want to invite you over to the Space. If you enter the Space, then you will have an entire place to yourself, you can do whatever you want to it. Moreover, you won’t have to worry about eating. You can do what you like, the same as the conditions I gave the Goblins. Ryder has seen the situation of the Goblin Race, you can ask him.”

Leir’s gaze switched over to Ryder. Ryder didn’t hesitate as he nodded and told Leir about the Goblin Race’s current situation.

This was also something that Zhao Hai prepared for. After Ryder and the others entered the Space and were arranged a place in Wild Dragon Island, Zhao Hai also had them visit the various backgrounds inside the Space. It can be said that Ryder had some understanding regarding the places inside.

Leir quietly listened to Ryder’s words. He believed that Ryder was telling the truth because he could hear a hint on envy from Ryder’s tone.

After Ryder was finished talking, Leir quietly sat down and closed his eyes. He didn’t say anything for a while. Zhao Hai looked at Leir and stayed quiet as well. He just smiled faintly as he took a pot of tea from the Space and drank some tea slowly.

After some time, Leir opened his eyes and looked at Zhao Hai, “Is Mister aware of the Dwarves’ current situation?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I didn’t know, but now I do.” When he said that, he pointed at the crisis report on top of Leir’s table.

Leir laughed out loud and said, “Mister is really frank. Then I won’t go in circles, I can’t decide on this matter alone. Please wait a moment, I want to meet with the family elders first. After we convene, only then could we reach a decision.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Patriarch, do as you please.”

Leir nodded before he loudly said, “Someone call the Elders over to the Conference Hall. Tell them that I have something important to discuss.” The Dwarf on the door complied before leaving.

Leir turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister please wait a moment. I need to head to the conference hall. Can I ask Ryder to come with me?”

Zhao Hai lightly smiled and said, “No problem. Since the Patriarch asked, Ryder, you can go with the Patriarch.” Ryder nodded before he walked out with Leir.

When the two left, Zhao Hai returned to the Space. He knew that the Conference Hall wasn’t that far from the Patriarch’s room. Therefore, Zhao Hai can definitely see their meeting from the Space’s monitor.

When Zhao Hai returned to the Space, Laura and the others immediately welcomed him. Then Laura said, “Brother Hai, fantastic. I didn’t think that it would be this smooth. From what I can see, Patriarch Leir agrees to enter the Space.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and nodded, “Right, by seeing his attitude it seems like he agrees. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have taken Ryder along. We need to get ready. Right, after entering the space, do we group them up with the Ark Continent’s Dwarves or do we give them a separate background?”

As soon as Laura and the others heard this, they couldn’t help but chuckle. Then Lizzy said, “Big Brother Hai, why are you being impatient? They still haven’t agreed to come, why did you jump into conclusions?”

Zhao Hai lightly smiled and said, “Isn’t it better to be prepared? If they agree, then it’ll be too late to think about it.”

Laura smiled and said, “Alright, if we need to think about it, I think Brother Hai should give them a separate Space. They’re unable to live together with the Ark Continent’s Dwarves. At this time, the Dwarves from the Ark Continent are living inside the Ark Space, and they’ve been living very well there. The Ark Continent’s development is intertwined with the races living inside. If we insert the Dwarves from the Divine Realm, then that wouldn’t be good.”

Lizzy also nodded and said, “Although the Dwarves from the Ark Continent are still Dwarves, they still have their own culture. Meanwhile, the Divine Dwarves also have their own culture. If we have them live together, then it’s possible that a conflict would occur.”

At this time, Megan added, “Most importantly, the Divine Dwarven Race also had their own air of arrogance. If they live with the Ark Continent’s Dwarves, then it’s possible that they would treat themselves as higher level beings. I’m not sure if the Ark Continent’s Dwarves would be able to accept this. Don’t forget, Patriarch Billy and Ryder’s first interaction didn’t go too well.”

When he heard these opinions, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “So we should give the Divine Dwarves their own background? Alright, then we need to choose which background to give them. Moreover, we need to transform it, making sure to have mineral lodes inside.”

While they were discussing this matter, the Dwarven Elders began to arrive inside the conference hall. When these people noticed Ryder, they couldn’t help but gawk. They might not recognize Ryder before, but after Ryder’s connection with Zhao Hai, these people began to know him. They didn’t expect Ryder to suddenly appear at this time.

After the group had sat down, Leir said, “I know everyone has noticed it, but Ryder came back. This time, he represents Mister Zhao Hai to propose a matter. Mister Zhao Hai is inviting our Dwarven Race to migrate into his Space.”

Upon hearing Leir’s voice, the Dwarves present were shocked. Then the room blew up, the news was too shocking for them.

After a couple of minutes of messy discussion, Leir knocked on his table a few times before loudly saying, “Quiet down and listen to me.” The Elders slowly calmed down and looked at each other before turning their attention to Leir.

Leir swept the room with his gaze and said, “Mister Zhao Hai also came over and we talked about it. Mister assured me and guaranteed the Dwarven Race’s safety. I think Mister is sincere. I called everyone over to say that I agree to enter Mister’s Space. Everyone should be aware of this, now that we didn’t dispatch troops, the Elves had started to suppress our grain supply. Although we can also suppress their weapon supply, we would still be losing in the end. Weapons are different from grains. Food is indispensable while weapons can be reused. And this is only the beginning. In the future, the suppression would increase. The Elves and the Beastmen would unite against us and our days wouldn’t be very good. Mister Zhao Hai assured absolute safety for us, and he also said that we can do whatever we want. Because of this, I agree to moving into Mister’s Space.”

The words that Leir said made the hall silent. The Elders began to calm down and carefully consider Leir’s words.

When Leir saw this situation, he decided to hammer it down, he said, “Everyone should know about the Goblins. They were enslaved by the Divines. Their lives are miserable. But now that the Goblins have entered Mister Zhao Hai’s Space, their lives had improved significantly. Ryder was able to see the state of the Goblins. Ryder, tell everyone about what you saw.”

In an instant, everyone’s eyes turned to Ryder. Ryder didn’t delay, as soon as Leir finished talking, he immediately spoke. When Ryder began to recall what he saw, the Elders carefully listened from beginning to end. Nobody made any noise.

When Ryder was done talking, an Elder suddenly said, “How do we know if what you said is real? Patriarch, this is a huge matter for our Race. I think we should see it with our own eyes.”

Leir turned his head to Ryder and said, “Will Mister agree to this condition?”

Ryder smiled faintly and said, “Patriarch, rest assured, Mister will certainly agree.”

Chapter 994: The Dwarves Enter The Space

Leir was currently looking at his clansmen who were tidying up. And in a place not too far away, there were also people who were walking towards a spatial rift.

He remembered the matters that happened in the past two days. Leir felt that everything he saw was just a dream. When they entered the Space with Zhao Hai, they saw how the Goblins were currently living. And after seeing the place Zhao Hai had prepared for them, everything else became smoother, nobody opposed entering the Space.

Leir and the others had seen the state of the Goblins before. In their view, Goblins couldn’t even be considered as a member of the intelligent race. There more like a group of walking dead, a group of unthinking magic beasts. They were emaciated, dirty. They would eat anything in order to live. It seems like as long as they could survive, then they’re satisfied.

But this time, when they saw the Goblins in the Space, Leir and the others were shocked. They simply didn’t believe that they were seeing Goblins. Now, the Goblins were wearing very good clothes, their bodies were also washed clean. At the same time, everyone had their own proper homes. Most importantly, the Goblins had developed a temperament, a mild-mannered and cultured temperament. Although they were short and small, and their skin was still green, nobody could imagine that these were the Goblins that were enslaved by the Divine Race.

Perhaps this was what “One who is filled with knowledge always behaved with elegance” meant. The Goblins now looked like scholars, they were completely different compared to what they were before.[1]

And the most important thing was the Goblin Race’s change in mentality. The Goblins seem to have gained a strong and persistent passion. It was a kind of appreciation for life as well as a dedication to researching magic formations. This fact really made Leir and the others surprised.

It was because they saw the transformation of the Goblins that Leir and the others decided to move their clansmen into the Space.

Moreover, the place that Zhao Hai had prepared left Leir and the others with no way to decline. In that place, there were rice bamboo and bread trees everywhere. And besides these, there were also iron spear trees present. And most importantly, there were plenty of mineral lodes inside. These mineral lodes were enough for the Dwarves to work on for many years. Zhao Hai also showed the church to Leir’s group. Upon seeing what can be exchanged, Leir and the others were left speechless.

While looking at his migrating people, Leir couldn’t help but let out a long breath. Although the Divine Dwarves and the Ark Continent’s Dwarves had been separated for many years and had developed their own cultures, they still share the same love for forging. And LIbra Continent, with its abundance of ores, had become the place that the Dwarves loved the most.

However, after years upon years of mining, the Divine Dwarves had stockpiled an enormous amount of ores as well as processed goods such as weapons and metal tools. It would take some time to move all of these things.

Fortunately, Zhao Hai promised to help them bring these items into the Space. Overall, the relocation of the Divine Dwarves was going very smoothly.

Although the Dwarves had been migrating, there were no signs of this happening in the outside world. Dwarves lived inside caverns and weren’t usually seen outside. Also, Zhao Hai didn’t open only one spatial rift. This was so that the relocation would go faster. Meanwhile, Leir was currently paying attention to the war in the Taurus Continent.

Leir had already talked with Solomon and Yerd. Although the two said that the war was doing good, and that they took a lot of wins, with how many years Leir had conversed with the two of them, he actually understood something different from the words that were said. Although they said that they had obtained wins, they didn’t say that they had come in contact with the Winged Pegasus. Moreover, they didn’t raise the issue of casualty between their side and the enemy’s. All of these weren’t normal. This made Leir speculate that the war wasn’t going very smoothly for the Foreign Races.

Even if they were migrating, Leir still wants to leave something for the Beastmen and the Elves. After all, the three races had been fighting side by side for tens of thousands of years. Although there had been some friction recently, their years of alliance couldn’t just be forgotten. Because of this, the Dwarves left their four ultimate weapons behind.

Zhao Hai didn’t have any objections to this choice. In any case, the Dwarves wouldn’t need to fight when they enter the Space. It can be said that those ultimate weapons were already useless in their hands.

The Winged Pegasus Clan, Thunder Clan, and the Barbarians have already moved into the Space. And now, the Dwarves were in the process of migrating. One could say that almost all of Zhao Hai’s relations in the Divine Realm had already moved to the Space. At this point, there was nothing in the Divine Realm that needs Zhao Hai’s worry.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai’s factory in the Atlanta Continent has already been established. And along with the factory’s establishment, Bluewell also bought the things that Zhao Hai needed. At this time, those items had been sent to Wild Dragon Island for Karen and the others to study.

After multiple discussions between Zhao Hai and Bluewell, they finally named their factory Wolf Fang Factory due to its address being Wolf Fang mountain. The factory has yet to start full production. Various equipments were still being shipped to the factory, and only after installing them would the factory be up and running.

Zhao Hai didn’t worry about a lot of matters anymore. He also wasn’t worried about the Dwarves’ migration. What Zhao Hai cared about right now was the Underworld’s matter.

Zhao Hai was prepared to immediately depart for the Underworld once all of the Dwarves had moved into the Space. At this moment, Kampala and the others have already fully adapted to life inside the Space. The Dark Mist in the Ark Continent was still under Zhao Hai’s monitoring. He was even able to penetrate his gaze into a small portion of the Underworld.

Currently, the undead roaming this region were no longer Kampala and the others’ subordinates. Instead, they have been substituted with Zhao Hai’s undead. Once other undead arrives, Zhao Hai would immediately know.

Zhao Hai already asked Kampala and was able to know that the Underworld was a very large plane. Nobody knew how long the Lich has lived, but he hasn’t been able to explore the entirety of the Underworld. Because of this, although the spatial rift in the Ark Continent would make subtle disturbances on the Dark Mist, the undead living in the Underworld would still need some time before they were able to sense it. Discovering the change in the Dark Mist in a short time was virtually impossible.

And most importantly, the Underworld was producing Dark Mists all the time. Such a slight change wouldn’t cause a reaction among the undead. This was the reason why the creatures of the Underworld were yet to discover the spatial rift.

However, Zhao Hai also knew that they didn’t have unlimited time. So before someone discovers the spatial rift, Zhao Hai would first take the time to take a stroll in the Underworld. He liked taking initiative in these matters.

The fight between the Foreign Races and the O’Neal family was still going on. And just as what Leir thought, the Foreign Races weren’t having a smooth time. Their 10 million soldiers had been attacking the defensive line and were suffering heavy losses. So far, the Foreign Races had lost several hundred thousand troops while the losses of the enemy side could be said to be negligible.

Although the Foreign Races had been changing their tactics with each attack, their enemies were still veterans with rich experience. Additionally, they had the appropriate weapons to face the Foreign Races. For the Foreign Races, this wasn’t a good thing.

At the same time, the O’Neal family’s situation wasn’t doing any better. Both magic cannons and magic armors consumed a lot of energy after each fierce fight. At this time, the cannons have used up all of their shells. Now they could only rely on their magic armors and war tanks in order to defend. Their casualties would begin to mount up after this.

It was great that the O’Neal family had prepared themselves for this invasion. They had enough energy converters in stock. They also had a small energy charger. Because of this, they weren’t worried about running out of energy.

In the Magic Armor Continent, almost every place used energy converters. It was just like an all-purpose battery that can be repeatedly used. And it also lasts a long time. An energy converter can be used up for up to 1000 times. These referred to the energy converters used by civilians. But for the military, energy converters could only be used 500 times.

This was a property of energy converters. After repeatedly using one 200 times, the energy that can be contained inside could no longer reach its maximum amount. And every time it was used, this maximum amount would become lower and lower. A completely new energy converter could support a magic armor for about four hours. Meanwhile, an energy converter that has been used 400 times could only support a magic armor for one hour. As for energy converters that were used 500 times, they can hardly support magic armors.

This time, the O’Neal family had been wary. Not only did they prepare a lot of energy converters, they also brought a charging station. This charging station can charge 100 energy converters at the same time. As long as there was enough energy to supply, this charger could recharge 100 energy converters in half an hour.

The material used to fuel energy converters were magic crystals. These magic crystals weren’t only found in the Magic Armor Continent, it can be found in other areas as well. Coincidentally, there was a spatial rift to the Winged Pegasus Plane not too far away. And at that place, there was a magic crystal mine. Axe and the others were relying on this magic crystal mine right now. If there were no magic crystals present, then they could only rely on sunlight or water currents for energy. But when that time comes, they would be completely destroyed by the Foreign Races.

* * *

腹有诗书气自华 – source here[http://news.iciba.com/study/bilingual/1575794.shtml]

Chapter 995: Dark Pharaoh

Although the battle was very lively, but for Zhao Hai, this kind of battle wasn’t worthy of his attention. He had already seen through the tricks of both sides. Unless the O’Neal family shows something good, then only then would Zhao Hai take a look. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have any interest in what was happening.

The migration of the Divine Dwarves was still going on. It’s possibly because they didn’t dispatch troops that the Beastmen and the Elves didn’t try to contact them. This allowed the Dwarves to move without the knowledge of the other two races.

Because Zhao Hai opened a lot of spatial rifts, the migration of the Dwarves went faster compared to the Winged Pegasus Clan. Moreover, the important ores and products of the Dwarves had already been moved by Zhao Hai. This allowed the Dwarves to pack lightly, saving a lot of time in the process.

Leir calculated that the migration wouldn’t take ten days. This result surprised him.

The population of the Dwarves was more than any Divine Race Continent. If they didn’t have this population advantage, then they wouldn’t have dared to go against the Divines, and continuing to do so for many years. For these many people to be moved in just ten days was unexpected. In the past, Leir wouldn’t even have dreamt for this to be possible.

At this time, Leir didn’t think too much about the migration. Inside the Space, the responsibility of settling the Dwarves has been handed over to Ryder. Ryder was the one with the most contact with Zhao Hai. Nobody was more qualified than him to take charge of the relocation. Meanwhile, Leir would be the one taking charge in directing the other Dwarves in the Libra Continent towards the spatial rifts.

Days passed and the Dwarves only used seven days to completely move to the Space. Moreover, everything was managed very well. The Dwarves had all that they needed. Because of this, the Dwarves felt that they were sent to heaven upon entering the Space.

Here, one could live in a bright room, eat grain every day, have bread, drink wine, and even hit iron. They can also mine all they want. Their situation here was much better compared to their previous living environment.

What made the Dwarves most happy about was the fact that they could eat fresh vegetables and fresh meat here. Moreover, when they go mining, they could buy special carts that could carry the ores. They can also take baths in their own house. In the past, they wouldn’t even dare imagine such a lifestyle.

There were Dwarves who didn’t understand why they needed to move and had some grievances in their hearts. But upon entering the Space, they immediately fell in love with it. Although they would need gold coins in order to construct their house, all of them felt that it was worth it. It can be said that aside from being able to hammer iron all they want, everything else was solved by the Space. This made the Dwarves very satisfied with the move.

The Dwarves finished their migration in seven days. Now, Zhao Hai was ready to head towards the Underworld. Just three days ago, more reinforcements arrived from the O’Neal family. This time, the battle didn’t just happen in the spatial rift but in the fields outside as well. The two sides clashed and it was a huge battle. This time, the Foreign Race suffered losses in the hands of the O’Neal family. Their total number of casualties had already surpassed 1 million.

Facing this situation, the Foreign Race army had no choice but to make a temporary retreat. At the same time, Solomon and Yerd realized that the enemy wasn’t going to be easily dealt with. But they still sent reinforcements, an additional 20 million troops as well as two Supreme Elders.

After sending the reinforcements, Solomon and Yerd suddenly discovered that Leir had been perfectly silent in the past several days. The two were very puzzled, so they immediately went to contact Leir using his messenger fish. But no reply came.

Solomon and Yerd couldn’t understand why Leir would do this. It can be said that the suppression done to the Dwarves wasn’t that ruthless. With Leir’s character, he shouldn’t have been pushed too hard. In the current war, the damages to their weapons were very critical, they would need the Dwarves to provide massive amounts of weapons. If Leir dared to break the weapon supply at this time, then this would certainly cause the two races to be enraged. From how the two understood of Leir, he wouldn’t do this.

After repeatedly calling Leir and coming up with no result, Solomon and Yerd began to be worried. They immediately sent two teams to the Libra Continent to examine the situation. However, the result that they received made them greatly surprised.

There were no longer any Dwarves in the Libra Continent, everyone had moved out. In the Dwarven territory, the only things that the scouts found were large quantities of weapons, four ultimate weapons, as well as a letter.

This letter was written by Leir for Solomon and Yerd. Its contents were very simple. In essence, Leir didn’t want to stay in the Divine Realm anymore. He also said that Solomon and Yerd had changed and since the Dwarves didn’t want change, they decided to leave. And that these weapons as well as four ultimate weapons were the last help that the Dwarves would give to the Beastmen and the Elves.

Solomon and Yerd read the letter and were left with shock. Leir’s letter said that the Dwarves had followed Zhao Hai. Just like the Winged Pegasus, the Dwarves had moved to Zhao Hai’s Space.

Solomon and Yerd didn’t know where the Winged Pegasus and the Dwarves moved to, but they had made calculations from what Zhao Hai told them before. They believed that Zhao Hai used Space magic in order to move them to another plane. It was just like what Zhao Hai did to the Ark Continent.

However, the two still couldn’t accept this result. They couldn’t understand what method Zhao Hai used to convince Leir and the others to allow the entire Dwarven Race to migrate. Moreover, when did Zhao Hai complete such a huge operation?

Solomon and Yerd were startled, they even led their own teams and personally went to the Libra Continent. They want to see whether the Dwarves moved on their own or if they were seized by Zhao Hai. If Zhao Hai forcefully took them, then they would find Zhao Hai at all costs and rescue the Dwarves.

Although there were some contradictions between the three races, they still existed together for tens of thousands of years. The three races were like three brothers. Even if they had some small quarrels, they were still siblings. Now that one brother left them forever, the other two couldn’t just easily accept it.

But after seeing the situation in the Libra Continent, Solomon and Yerd became silent. This was because there were no traces of fighting in the Libra Continent. Moreover, one could see that the Dwarves had calmly moved. They didn’t bring any unwieldy things with them and only took important possessions. Moreover, they also left behind some weapons as well as the four ultimate weapons.

When they heard this news before, Solomon and Yerd already knew that this was the case, but they still couldn’t believe it at that time. But now, they had no choice but to accept it. The two were in a heavy mood especially when they saw the letter that Leir had left behind. They began to think about themselves and recalled that they had really changed.

Zhao Hai didn’t have time to care about Solomon and Yerd’s concerns. He was now preparing to enter the Underworld. But before he went in, he would need to have an identity. Zhao Hai didn’t want to enter the Underworld as a human. This would only make the undead attack him, and he didn’t want that.

Because of this, Zhao Hai needed to an identity to assume while in the Underworld. After repeated discussions with Kampala, Kampala finally remembered a profession that was almost forgotten by the whole Underworld, a Dark Pharaoh!

A Dark Pharaoh was a type of Dark lifeform that belonged to the mage class. They wore clothes but it was different to what other people wore. These clothes wrapped their whole bodies with no area uncovered. Most importantly, despite being a Dark lifeform, they weren’t considered as undead since they had heartbeats as well as an aura of life. However, their entire body was made out of dark energy. As for how a Dark Pharaoh was born, Kampala and the others had no idea. They only knew that there were very few Dark Pharaohs in the Underworld. And it had been several thousand years since news about one was heard.

It just so happens that being a Dark Pharaoh best suits Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai has a heartbeat, has life aura, and can change his energy into the dark element. Most importantly, although these Dark Pharaohs were in the mage class, they also had certain close combat capabilities which meets Zhao Hai exact description. Because of this, Kampala decided to have Zhao Hai act as a Dark Pharaoh.

There was also another advantage in posing as a Dark Pharaoh. In the Underworld, every Dark Pharaoh were powerful beings. Therefore, nobody in the Underworld would suspect Zhao Hai no matter how much power he shows.

Zhao Hai also thought that being a Dark Pharaoh was very suitable for him. With his status as a Dark Pharaoh, Zhao Hai can be open in taking over Kampala’s territory. After all, in the Underworld, the universal language was strength. Kampala and the others submitting to a powerful Dark Pharaoh was very normal.

Now that his identity has been settled, Zhao Hai spent the remaining time learning the customs and etiquette of the Underworld. These were matter that he would also need to pay attention to.

Who would’ve imagined that there would be so many races in the Underworld. Aside from the undead, there was also the Dark Creatures. These dark creatures were beings like the Dark Pharaoh. They were entities made and honed by dark energy. Such creatures can be seen all throughout the Underworld. They were another major force aside from the three Undead factions.

Chapter 996: Entering the Underworld

Gazi, gazi, gazi, gazi!

The sound of bones clanking was heard inside the dark mist. If a Dark Mage from the Ark Continent was present and was able to hear this, then he would immediately know that this was the sound of a large number of moving undead.

However, it was a pity that this wasn’t the Ark Continent. This was the Underworld, such sounds could be heard everywhere, it was quite normal here.

Groups upon groups of grey skeletons were slowly moving forward in the Dark Mist. These were the lowest ranked skeletons in the Underworld. Only such skeletons would make this sound when walking, higher-level skeletons would never make this sound.

In the Underworld, everywhere was full with these unintelligent grey skeletons. These things only had two uses. First one was for cannon fodder while the other one was food for the other undead. Aside from these two, there were no other uses for these grey skeletons.

Every day, batches of these grey skeletons would be born in the Underworld. Some of these grey skeletons would be born with intelligence. They would then start killing other grey skeletons to make themselves stronger and more powerful. Finally, they would become silver or even gold skeletons. But in most cases, these grey skeletons would just be killed.

However, this group of grey skeletons were evidently led by someone. They were neatly lined up as they moved forward. If there was no dark mist, one would be able to see a white bone carriage in the middle of this group. Inside the carriage was a mage wearing a black robe. This robe was very strange. It completely wrapped around the mage’s body, there was nothing left uncovered.

Beside this mage were two undead. One of them was a skeleton who wore full-body armor. On the slits of the armor, one could see the skeleton’s bones. Moreover, his bones were different compared to the other skeletons. It seems to have crystallized, it glistened from time to time.

The other undead was a zombie. He wore tattered clothes and had long and sharp fangs. One could see his status from his appearance, he was a Zombie King.

Naturally, this was Zhao Hai’s group. The grey skeletons around them were Guli’s subordinates. Zhao Hai plans to take them all into the Space in the future so that they would be upgraded.

It was precisely because of this that Zhao Hai had Guli round up as many grey skeletons as possible. After all, nobody would want to manage these grey skeletons here in the Underworld.

At this time, Zhao Hai who was sitting there, suddenly said, “Guli, how far is Three Saint City from here?”

Guli’s deep voice replied, “Young Master, it’s quite close. We would reach it in one hour. Three Saint City is a place that the three of us has established. It is the biggest city in this generation. You can find Zombies, Skeletons, Lich and even  High-Level Darkness creatures within. There are also some Vampires in the city.”

Then Zhao Hai said, “Interesting. I didn’t expect that you could establish a large city in the Underworld. Do you do trades as well?”

Guli nodded and said, “Yes, we also do transactions. However, we don’t use the same currency as the Humans. Instead what we use to trade are fiery souls and spirit stones.”

Zhao Hai replied, “I know about fiery souls, each Undead has one inside their bodies. But why would they be used as currency? Also, what are spirit stones?”

Guli went on to explain, “Just like you said, fiery souls exist inside all Undead. When an undead is killed, one would be able to obtain these fiery souls. These souls have two uses, first, one could absorb the souls in order to strengthen themselves. The second purpose is for exchanging for things that you want. Spirit stones are like magic crystals from the Ark Continent. But unlike magic crystals where you can acquire from both mining and magic beasts, spirit stones can only be acquired through killing magic beasts. There’s no such thing as a spirit stone mine.”

Zhao Hai was puzzled, “So the undead can get stronger and stronger as they absorb fiery souls? What else do you need?”

Guli nodded and said, “Right, we get stronger if we absorb fiery souls. However, after reaching a high level, it would be very difficult to improve if you only absorb fiery souls. Only by absorbing high-level fiery souls or souls stones could one improve. But high-level fiery souls could generally be found on powerful undead, and killing those undead is very hard. Because of this, we need to look for other means to promote our strength. In the Underworld, there are special plants and ores that we can use. And some of these plants and ores are useless to low-level Undead. Even if they have peak-level fiery souls, they still wouldn’t be able to absorb it. Therefore, whenever low-level undead gain these resources, they would generally go to the city and trade them with the correct level of fiery souls.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he understood what Guli said. The Underworld wasn’t a safe place. But as long as an Undead reaches bronze-level, then they would be able to attain intelligence. And at this time, if they want to level up, then they would need massive amounts of fiery souls. If they only hunted and killed undead by themselves, then their progress would be very slow. Moreover, they will be more likely to meet powerful undead. When that time comes, they would be the one being hunted.

Because of this, those bronze undead who found high-level plants would go to the city in order to exchange for large amounts of items that they could use at their current level. Then when they absorb those things and become stronger, they would be able to subdue massive amounts of undead, which in turn would hunt fiery souls for them. Then they would use these fiery souls to exchange for more precious materials to get stronger. Doing it like this seems to be very troublesome, but in fact, this was the safest method in the Underworld. Even if one was a Gold Skeleton, then it was still possible for them to meet a Crystal Skeleton and be turned into food. Naturally, this wasn’t the only method to get stronger. If one obtains a high-level resource that would make one stronger, then they wouldn’t hesitate to absorb it. They wouldn’t save it and bargain for more value with the other undead. In the Underworld, there was no such thing as savings. If you get something you can use, then you should use it right away, you need to get stronger as soon as possible.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Guli and said, “Are there laws in your city? If a skeleton brings their item to the city and gets robbed by the other undead, wouldn’t they lose everything?”

Guli immediately replied, “There are laws present in the city. No matter how low-leveled an Undead creature is, as long as they enter the city, then it would be impossible for them to be killed. If they were killed, then the killer would be punished. In Three Saint City, if there’s a murderer on the loose, then the three of us would send our subordinates to kill them off. If the murderer is strong, then the three of us would personally go.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he asked once more, “What level are you now? Are you enough to shake the Underworld?”

Guli replied, “My current level is Skeleton King. It’s considered to be high-rank among the skeletons. Above me are Skeleton Saints. There are only a few of these experts in the Underworld. And there is also a more powerful rank than Skeleton Saints, and they’re called Skeleton Gods. They only exist in legends, not one managed to appear in the Underworld.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned his head to Jiang Zheng and said, “Jiang Zheng, how are the zombies ranked?”

Jiang Zheng immediately replied, “There is also a very strict classification for zombies. The lowest level is called the Carrion, after that are Dry Corpse, Jumping Corpse, Ironskin Zombie, Copperskin Zombie, Clawed Zombie, Fanged Zombie, Black-haired Zombie, Red-haired Zombie, Green-haired Zombie Kings, and then Zombie Saints. This one’s rank is Green-haired Zombie King, a rank that is the same as Guli.

Zhao Hai nodded,. The levels of the Undead were much stricter compared to the Ark Continent and the Divine Race. But they were indeed strong. No wonder they became a hegemonic group in the Underworld.

Zhao Hai looked at Jiang Zheng and said, “Jiang Zheng, do you also need fiery souls to get stronger? Do the Zombies have fiery souls as well?”

Jiang Zheng nodded and said, “Yes, Zombies need fiery souls to upgrade as well. In addition to fiery souls, we also need to soak in Blood Ponds. These Blood Ponds can be seen everywhere here in the Underworld, they aren’t special things. But after one becomes a Copperskin Zombie, they won’t need to use Blood Ponds anymore. After we reach that stage, we would be like the skeletons. We would either need high-ranked fiery souls or high-level materials.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned towards the front. Naturally, he couldn’t see anything. Zhao Hai discovered that the eyes were the most useless things in the Underworld. This was because of the Dark Mist. In the Underworld where the visibility was less than ten meters, your eyes would just be as good as decoration. One could only use spirit sense to ‘see’ ahead.

It was good that Zhao Hai already had powerful spiritual sense, this allowed him to see far away. Otherwise, he would be blind in the Underworld. Zhao Hai had just felt that Three Saint City wasn’t that far away.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but turn to Guli and ask, “Guli, in the Underworld, you Undead could see using your sense, but how about the Dark Creatures? Do they also use spiritual sense? Are their eyes useless?”

Guli promptly replied, “Young Master, the Dark Creatures also rely on spiritual sense rather than their eyes. In fact, most Dark Creatures in the Underworld don’t have any eyes.”

This information gave Zhao Hai a shock, he didn’t expect the Dark Creatures to not have eyes. He couldn’t help but be curious, “So the Dark Creatures have no eyes? That’s interesting.”

Guli immediately said, “Young Master, there are only few creatures in the Underworld who have eyes. An example of this are the Dark Creatures known as vampires. Their eyes are very special, it allows them to see through the Dark Mist.”

The mention of vampires sparked interest within Zhao Hai, “Vampires, huh. Interesting, I want to see one.”

Then Jiang Zheng said, “Vampires are quite similar to us Zombies. They’re essentially Undead and not Dark Creatures. Unlike Dark Creatures, Vampires don’t have heartbeats, making them undead. However, their progression is very interesting. They start out as a Dark Creature called Vampire Bats. This Vampire Bat is divided into; Black Vampire Bat, Red Vampire Bat, Silver Vampire Bat, and Gold Vampire Bat. Then after that, they undergo metamorphosis, becoming a low-level Vampire called Vampire Barons. After Vampire Barons are Vampire Viscount, then Vampire Count, then Vampire Marquis, Vampire Duke, Vampire Prince, and the most powerful rank being Vampire King.”

Zhao Hai nodded. After many years of development, the Underworld had already established its own power hierarchy. Its civilization wouldn’t lose out against others. This made Zhao Hai thing about it more as his curiosity increased.

While they were speaking, Zhao Hai felt that they had already arrived at Three Saint City. To be honest, Zhao Hai still wasn’t used to this kind of detection where you use spiritual force instead of eyesight. Zhao Hai turned to Guli and said, “Guli, is this it?”

Guli nodded, “Yes. Young Master, wait for a moment.” After he said that, Guli released his spiritual force forwards. Before long, several spiritual forces replied back. This gave Guli and the others a signal to proceed.

However, the grey skeletons that Guli managed to subdue were left outside the city. Upon seeing this situation, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but ask, “Should we leave them here or should I take them to the Space?”

Guli replied, “If Young Master wants to send them to the Space now, then that’s fine. But if you don’t, there’s no problem with leaving them outside the city. After a while, I’ll send some of my subordinates to round them up. Since they would be under their control, they shouldn’t be able to go away.”

Zhao Hai began to think about how the Grey Skeletons seem to be treated as livestock here in the Underworld. After Guli and the others subdued them, they would be reared in a pen. They would only be released when they were needed. It’s kind of interesting in its own way.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “Then let’s do it according to the rules here. In any case, there are far more of these things roaming around in the Underworld.”

Guli nodded, then he commanded the bone carriage to enter the city.

Chapter 997: Three Saint City

Zhao Hai began to understand how great Three Saint City was when he entered it. The city wouldn’t lose against any great Human city.

Its walls were made of stone. However, the adhesive used to paste them together wasn’t cement nor mud, instead it used a bloody red soil that had a strong bloody smell.

The city wall was about 20 meters high with a gate that was 20 feet wide and ten feet high. The gate was made out of bones and looked horrible.

Zhao Hai still can’t feel the total length of the city wall, but he reckons that it should be more than 10 thousand meters. On such a huge wall, there was only this single gate, and there seems to be no other carriages around. I looks like there weren’t a lot of carriages here in the Underworld.

There were two rows of skeleton soldiers standing by the city gate. All of them were Silver Skeletons equipped with spears. There was no armor on their bodies, but high-ranked skeletons with weapons was still terrible to go against.

Zhao Hai curiously examined this group of skeletons. Although he already used his spiritual force to inspect them, Zhao Hai was still used to using his eyes to ‘see’ things.

The skeletons were motionless, they looked like statues. After glancing through them, Zhao Hai immediately used his spiritual force to scan the situation inside the city.

Upon feeling what was inside, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get shocked. Zhao Hai imagined that the Undead in the Underworld wouldn’t have houses. After all, Undead weren’t sensitive to cold nor heat. For them, having shelter was basically useless.

However, Zhao Hai found out that Three Saint City not only has houses, but there were plenty of them inside. Zhao Hai swept his spiritual force towards the city to see its structure. He thought that he was seeing a human city. The city’s design was good, it’s roads were very neat. It’s streets were covered by stone slates, the same material was used for the houses. There were three towers on the east side of the city. Each tower was 100 meters high and stood in a triangle, overlooking everything inside the city.

If one just looks at the structures, then one would think that it was just an ordinary human city. But when you see its inhabitants, you would immediately change your mind. The majority of those roaming the streets were Zombies and Skeletons. There were also Dark Creatures, Lich, and so on. After a while, you would even notice pale faced people. They were actually vampires wearing neat clothes as they walked the street.

It was a city comprised of Undead and Dark Creatures. Zhao Hai didn’t notice it at first, but as his spiritual force explored the city, he noticed that almost all the houses had an undead theme. And with the addition of the dark mist, the whole city looked like a ghost forest, a miniature version of how one would imagine the Underworld.

At this time, when the Undead and Dark Creatures saw Zhao Hai’s group, they were really respectful and even bent down their bodies.

In the Underworld, the difference with each ranks were very strict. Existences like Guli stood at the very peak, low-level undead needed to give them a salute whenever they meet. Naturally, if the Undead belonged to another faction, instead of giving respects, they would immediately proceed to attack.

However, in this Three Saint City, Guli and the others were the genuine rulers. The Undead inside the City wouldn’t dare to neglect Guli’s group. Or else, their fiery souls would be pulled out and eaten. It was this overbearing here.

Guli commanded the group to head towards the three towers in the city. These were the tallest structures here, and naturally this was also where Guli stayed.

Before long, the group arrived at the tower. Zhao Hai also came out of the carriage and entered. But since that tower belonged to Kampala, Zhao Hai called Kampala out. One must know that this tower had many Lich living inside it. These Lich were subordinates that Kampala kept here in order to manage Three Saint City. And if Zhao Hai just entered the tower without Kampala, then these Lich may attack.

Kampala was now immersed in Magic Formations. For Kampala, the world of magic formations was a really wonderful world. He didn’t want to go outside and waste time. So when he was called out by Zhao Hai, he immediately called his subordinates over and had Zhao Hai take them to the Space. Then he returned to his research, he didn’t care how Zhao Hai wanted to deal with these Lich.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but shake his head when he saw Kampala’s action. Kampala and the others, these immortal beings, used to have nothing to  pursue. After countless years, power or desire had almost nothing to do with them. They just wanted to do what interests them. And now, the world of magic formations just provided this thirst for Kampala.

A few days ago, when Zhao Hai entered the Space, he went to visit Karen’s laboratory. He was surprised to find that the laboratory already had some improvements. These were the benefits they gained from books regarding magic formations and magic armors that were gained from the Atlanta Plane.

Although these books were only at a primary level, they were undoubtedly treasures to Karen and the others who had been in the dark.

Besides these books, another thing that Karen and the others cared about were the computers that Zhao Hai had provided them. The formidable computational abilities of these computers greatly helped Karen’s group. More importantly, Zhao Hai didn’t expect them to use a computer much better compared to him.

Zhao Hai was very surprised about the learning capabilities of the group. One must know that Karen and the others had only been introduced by Zhao Hai to the simple operations of a computer. Then Zhao Hai just gave them books in order to use alongside the computers. Who would’ve thought that Karen and the others would be able to learn how to use computers with more ability than Zhao Hai. At this time, Karen’s group were now able to do magic formation simulations using the computer’s tools.

And with the addition of Kampala and the others, Karen’s progress became faster. The knowledge of the Lich allowed Karen to discover that the Lich had also been performing strange and foreign research. Every time the researches discussed, their outcome had always been constructive.

Zhao Hai began to recall. After arriving in Three Saint City, he saw that the Lich weren’t really needed to manage the undead in the city. Some of these Lich were completely erudite, they preferred learning than fighting. So Zhao Hai took these Lich into the Space and then replaced them with large quantities of skeletons.

This change went unnoticed by the Undead in Three Saint City, nor would they care. In the Underworld, strong beings killing another strong being and taking over their territory was very common; there’s nothing strange about it. So when Zhao Hai sat inside Guli’s bone carriage and entered the city, the Undead weren’t very surprised. For these undead, this only meant that the City had a new ruler.

The Underworld had the rule of the jungle and respected the strong. Here, as long as you have the strength, then you can do whatever you want. If you were weak, then your fiery soul could only be used as food and currency for the others.

After taking care of the Lich, Zhao Hai arrived at the topmost level of Kampala’s room. Upon entering the room, Zhao Hai was shocked. He felt that this wasn’t a room that was made for living. Instead, it seems to be like a huge ancient library as well as a museum!

The entire room was very big, it seems to be hundreds of square meters. However, there were no chairs in this room. There weren’t any living supplies inside instead of a small study. There were rows upon rows of shelves. Some of the shelves had rolls of beastskin scrolls while some had strange items such as fried tree bark, dried grass, a hoe, a pickled head, a broken knife, and an unfinished embroidery. When Zhao Hai saw these things, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but freeze. He couldn’t believe that this would be the room of a peak-level Lich.

Before long, Zhao Hai arrived at a desk with a beastskin scroll rolled out on top. He didn’t know which beast this skin belongs to. There was a bone pen beside this scroll. The skin was treated and was pale yellow. It was also filled with blood red words.

The things written on this beastskin seems to be the records of Kampala’s research. But when Zhao Hai saw it, he was a little dumbfounded, Kampala’s research turned out to be poetry!

The Underworld followed the rules of the Jungle where the strong reigned king. But a Lich race’s top existence actually researched poetry? Nobody would believe it if they were told.

Zhao Hai put the beastskin down as he turned his attention to a nearby shelf. He picked a scroll at random and gently opened it. Zhao Hai took a glance at the scroll and carefully read its contents. When he saw what was written, Zhao Hai’s eyes couldn’t help but shrink.

Written on this scroll wasn’t poetry, instead it was a magic spell. It was a fire-element attack that Zhao Hai hadn’t seen before. The steps to casting this magic, from the incantation to the hand signals were clearly written. It can be said that the scroll had turned a complex fire-element magic into an inscribed blueprint. As long as one casts the magic spell according to what was written, then one would be able to use this powerful magic.

Zhao Hai carefully followed the magic from the first step. His finger moved while his mouth mumbled the incantation. After completing these steps, a three-winged boomerang made out of fire appeared in his hands.

Zhao Hai stared blankly at this boomerang. He didn’t think that he could use this magic. Moreover, it was as exactly as what the beastskin scroll described!

Chapter 998: Some People Have Plan About Three Saint City

Zhao Hai was really surprised by this fire boomerang. This boomerang wasn’t like any fire magic he had seen. As soon as the magic was cast, the fire boomerang began to compact, not a lick of flame was seen. It seems to have become a crystal. This made the boomerang in Zhao Hai’s hand look like it was made out of red crystal.

Such fire-element magic was novel to Zhao Hai. He didn’t think that fire-element magic would assume this appearance.

Another thing that surprised Zhao Hai was the fact that this research happened in the Underworld. One must know that the magic that was used here was of the dark-element. In other words, Fire-element Mages was practically useless here since there wasn’t any fire-element present. The only reason why Zhao Hai was able to use this fire-element magic was because he has the Space to supply fire-element.

However, any new magic would need repeated experiments. One couldn’t just provide proof through theory alone. This was especially true for magic, it needed to be tested time and time again before being finalized.

And now, this fire-element crystal magic was successfully researched in a place without the fire-element. Isn’t that surprising? How did Kampala do it?

Zhao Hai placed the beast skin down before picking another one from the shelf. Recorded inside was another fire-element magic that had something to do with arrows. It was thus named as, Flame Arrow Spell.

Although the spell Flame arrow was also present in conventional fire-element spells, the one written in the beastskin scroll was actually different. This spell requires the user to do compression on the fire-element to make this fire crystal arrow. This arrow had the strength of a normal arrow. But after this arrow was shot out and hit its target, it would explode. Even if it was shot down by the opposite party, as long as a certain resistance was felt, the arrow would still explode.

Zhao Hai immediately did the incantations expressed on the scroll. And sure enough, to his surprised, casting the magic was a success.

Zhao Hai placed the beastskin scroll down as he looked at the shelf full of scrolls. He suddenly felt that he had entered a huge treasure trove. These scrolls were the product of Kampala’s countless years of research. Although there were things like poetry among them, spells like the Fire Boomerang and Flame Arrow were inventions that had subverted the current magic system.

Magic compression had always been a topic of study among the researchers in the Ark Continent. People had invented compressed magic spells before, but they found that even if compressed magic was powerful, it was also very dangerous. If the compressed magic wasn’t stable, then it was very likely to explode, which would be dangerous to the Mage. Therefore, this was the first problem that needed to be solved.

Zhao Hai continued to scan Kampala’s beastskin scrolls. Almost all of the things recorded on these scrolls were compressed magic, and all of them were compressed to an ultimate degree. Spells like Flame Arrows were much stronger than their contemporaries by about 100 times.

And after reading these scrolls, Zhao Hai managed to find a trend. There were several incantations and hand movements in these spells. Zhao Hai hypothesized that these incantations and gestures might be the key to compressed magic.

After he thought about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t stay still. He immediately took all of the things in this room and received them into his Space.

On Wild Dragon Island, in addition to Karen’s magic formation laboratory, there were also other people who did their own research. This was because Wild Dragon Island was a place where studies had become integral to day to day life. There were people here who were studying magic spells, so Zhao Hai had these people inspect his recently acquired scrolls.

Besides these scrolls, Kampala’s collections were also taken by Zhao Hai to the Space. First, he wanted to see if these things could increase the Space’s experience. And second, he wanted to see if he could discover new ores or materials. These discoveries would have huge benefits to him.

And there was no need to mention that Kampala’s collection, especially the ores, were things that couldn’t be seen in the Ark Continent nor in the Divine Realm. These ores contained the yin(dark)-element. People in the Cultivation Realm divided materials into Yin and Yang. For example, there were things such as yin wood and yang wood, yin stone and yang stone. Naturally, metals were also divided into such classification.

It was a very simple method. But in the Cultivation Realm, the usage of these yin and yang items were totally different.

Dark-element items in the Underworld were seen by the people in the Cultivation Realm as yin-type items. For some people in the Cultivation Realm, these things were precious.

After emptying the room, Zhao Hai refurbished the room. He just made it according to his current thoughts. After all, he didn’t intend to stay in the Underworld for a long time. And in his downtime, he would still return to the Space.

After taking care of the room, Zhao Hai returned to the Space. But he didn’t want to take a look at the battle between the O’Neal family and the foreign races. Instead, he continued to look at Kampala’s scrolls. This time, he didn’t intend to study them, instead he divided the scrolls according to their classification.

Who knows how long Kampala had these scrolls stored up. There were some scrolls that had been researched recently and there were also some who had been there for a very long time. Although it was very messy, one has to recognize that these things were really useful.

Whether it was magic tests or other research, a single person researching all of it was different compared to when series of people took over one after another. Their accomplishments would certainly not be the same.

With compression magic, Kampala personally went through the research for a long time. He managed to capture several important points with regards to the magic. To him, compression magic had become very simple.

On the other hand, the people from the Ark Continent wouldn’t be able to achieve this point. This was because Kampala was only able to get this essence after several hundreds of years. The Mages from the Ark Continent couldn’t live for that long. Once a Mage dies, their apprentice would be taking their place. Even if the research was doing very well, there was a high possibility of it branching into some other result once the successor takes charge, causing the research to fail.

After sorting through the scrolls inside the Space, Zhao Hai returned to the Underworld. This time, he wanted to gain a better understanding of the Underworld. If he wanted to stay here daily, this was imperative.

Just as Zhao Hai went out of the Space, Guli and Jiang Zheng arrived at his tower. Naturally, Zhao Hai invited them in. When the two saw the room, they couldn’t help but stare. They had seen Kampala’s room before, and now it was different. It now had one shelf filled with books. It had a desk and a chair. Then in the distance was a resting area with a set of sofas, a coffee table, and some daily necessities. The area was also covered with carpet, and there was also a rocking chair.

Zhao Hai looked at the two and smiled faintly, “Sit, aren’t you supposed to handle Three Saint City? Why did you come here? Also, I didn’t think Kampala’s room would have such good things. Right, did you know that Kampala was researching magic here?”

The two nodded, Guli said, “We knew. For a while, Kampala was immersed in studying magic of other elements. In the Underworld, although it was filled with dark-element, after years of development, using other elements had become possible. After all, light and dark magics are the most fundamental magic in the universe. Although dark magic is still widely used in the Underworld, there are still some who use magic in other departments.”

Upon hearing Guli, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but nod. He remembered the first batch of Lich that he met before. They used innate yin fire which can be said to be part of fire-element spells. However, that spell didn’t belong to the yang(light) flame, instead it was yin(dark) fire. After he thought about this, Zhao Hai began to relax. But this made him even more curious about the Underworld. He didn’t think that the Undead would be this smart.

Zhao Hai looked at the two and said, “Right, why did you come see me at this time? Did something happen to Three Saint City?”

Jiang Zheng replied, “Young Master, we came looking for you to report that Three Saint City might be targeted by other people. After we came back, we asked a few of our men about what happened when the three of us went out. At that time, there was a sudden increase of undead entering the city. Although they were doing business in a proper manner, it’s hard to say what they are going to do in the future.”

Zhao Hai stared, then his two eyes glimmered, “So you’re saying that some people have ideas about Three Saint City? A battle is coming to the city?”

Chapter 999: Blood Energy!

Jiang Zheng nodded and said, “Yes, it’s possible that Three Saint City would have to go to war. We’ve already arranged for people to find out who wants to deal with us.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, do it. I’m afraid it might be the Dark Temple. But that would be good, I would like to see how strong they are.”

Jiang Zheng shook his head and said, “The attackers aren’t necessarily from the Dark Temple. They could also be from the resistance army. Recently, a very powerful person appeared in the faction. He’s a Vampire King and he wants to unify the rebel forces, forming a nation and then dealing with the Dark Temple. However, most of the rebel forces disagrees. I heard that there has been several rebel-created cities that had already been occupied by this Vampire King.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think that the rebel army wouldn’t actually be strongly united, there were even conflicts happening within. Things had just become more interesting.

Zhao Hai looked at Jiang Zheng and said, “Didn’t you say that there are only very few Vampire Kings? How come there’s one that appeared right now?”

Jiang Zheng and Guli didn’t know what to say. They just smiled bitterly. Then after a moment, Jiang Zheng couldn’t help but reply, “Young Master, the rebel army has quite few powerful experts within. If we didn’t have that many powerful beings, then we would have already been flattened by the Dark Temple.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He was aware of Jiang Zheng, Guli, and Kampala’s strengths. At most, they have reached the Vampire Prince level, a worse position compared to the Vampire King. If they faced a Vampire King, then they would have to be really careful.

Zhao Hai also knew that the three were very strong. Even if they didn’t have any special weapons, with only their strengths, they were similar to the Foreign Race Supreme Elders who wore combat suits. And now, this Vampire King was stronger than them. One could see from this point how strong the Vampire King was.

When he thought about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get excited. It has been a long time since he had run into someone that might match him. In the Divine Realm, while fighting the Divine Supreme Elders, Zhao Hai wasn’t able to use his full strength. Because of this, Zhao Hai felt suffocated. In the end, he can only grind the other side to death.

But now, things were different. Zhao Hai can use his full strength, and he wants to test it to see to what degree his strength has reached. To achieve this, he wasn’t planning to use the Hell King’s ship this time.

Ever since he completed his study on the Myriad Stellar Transformation art, Zhai Hai’s strength has been constantly increasing. The increase wasn’t very fast, after all the art had a strong compressive force. Increasing his cultivation quickly like before was basically impossible.

This was the Myriad Transformations Yin-Yang art’s weakness. However, Zhao Hai didn’t care, he believed that the art was a very formidable cultivation method.

Jiang Zheng and Guli saw Zhao Hai’s excited appearance. But the two didn’t really know what Zhao Hai was thinking about. And then Guli said, “Young Master, if there’s really a fight, then what do we do?”

Zhao Hai turned to look at the two and understood what Guli meant. At this time, they were no longer part of the Underworld, but were now in Zhao Hai’s faction. It wasn’t like before where they would have to fight against the Vampire King. They now have another choice, and that was to avoid fighting the Vampire King and leaving Three Saint City.

Zhao Hai thought about it and said, “We’ll prepare. We cannot give up on Three Saint City right now. If the other party really comes, then we would just meet them in battle.”

When the two heard Zhao Hai, they quickly understood his stance. The two nodded before they left to prepare. Zhao Hai stayed inside the room. But this time, he wasn’t reading a book. He wanted to see how Jiang Zheng and Guli handled things How would they prepare against an approaching enemy?

Soon enough, when Guli and Jiang Zheng returned to their towers, they immediately began to move. Teams of Skeletons and Zombies directly captured some undead. Zhao Hai was quite certain that those Undead were being suspected as being sent by the enemy.

Sure enough, some of these Undead counter-attacked. However, the numbers made the difference, allowing them to be arrested. Besides those who were caught or killed, the other Undead didn’t get affected. There were even a lot of Undead standing on the side watching with excitement.

After capturing these undead, Three Saint City’s gates closed. Then Zhao Hai felt that there was blood starting to flow below Jiang Zheng’s tower.

Zhao Hai stared, then he remembered Jiang Zheng mentioning Blood Ponds. It seems like this was one of those Blood Ponds.

Zhao Hai looked at the blood-like liquid flowing out from under Jiang Zheng’s tower. Zhao Hai also began to discover that there were small engravings all throughout Three Saint City. The blood flowed along those engravings. Before long, a complicated pattern was made out of this blood as it flowed towards the city wall.

Zhao Hai’s figure moved as he appeared inside Jiang Zheng’s tower. Jiang Zheng was currently sitting on the topmost floor of his tower. In this room, there was an enormous Blood Pond, but the liquid inside this pond began to be slowly reduced.

Juang Zheng felt that a person had appeared on his side. He turned his head to see Zhao Hai. Jiang Zheng immediately said, “Young Master.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Is this a Blood Pond? How could one be in such a high place?”

Jiang Zheng replied, “Replying to the Young Master. This isn’t an ordinary Blood Pond, but it is a Blood Spring. It is the main reason why we constructed Three Saint City. In the Underworld, each Blood Pond is actually a Blood Spring. However, these blood springs cannot spurt as high as this one. Later on, Kampala built upon this pool. The entire Blood Spring became centralized here. Then there would be valves to let some blood out. When there’s no need to use a lot of blood, then a lot of these valves would be opened. But during war, when the magic formation needed blood, these valves would be closed. Then other valves would open so that the blood would enter the magic formation.”

Zhao Hai nodded. This method wasn’t difficult, but it wasn’t easy for Kampala to implement this design.

While he thought about this, Zhao Hai said, “Is it fine if I take some of this blood away?”

Jiang Zheng quickly replied, “Young Master can take it freely. Actually, this blood is very common in the Underworld. Our survival in the Underworld is actually because of two things. First is the Dark Mist, and the second is the Blood Pond.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he waved his hand as a clump of blood flew away from the Blood Pond. Then Zhao Hai sent that clump of blood to the Space.

As the blood entered the Space, a prompt was immediately heard, “Strong yin element blood detected. This blood can provide a boost of energy to the Undead. At the same time, it has the ability to corrode the yang-element.”

Although the prompt wasn’t long, Zhao Hai was still able to understand the properties. First, the blood’s attribute was yin. Second, it was a type of energy. And Third, the blood can be used by the Undead, providing them with an advantage against their enemies.

Zhao Hai could remember that the items in the Cultivation were primarily divided into yin and yang types. If a yang-type item was drenched with this blood, then it might be possible to make it useless.

When he thought about this, Zhao Hai became glad. He didn’t think that the blood pond would have this much use. Then at this time, another prompt came, “Extracting the blood’s properties. All the Dark Creatures and Undead inside the place will now be able to use the blood spring.”

Zhao Hai gave a satisfied nod. He expected the Space to extract the properties of the blood. In the past, every material that was sent to the Space always had their properties extracted.

Jiang Zheng observed Zhao Hai’s action, he didn’t understand why Zhao Hai needed to get the blood into the Space. But after seeing the satisfied smile in Zhao Hai’s face, he knew that Zhao Hai got something good from the blood. Then Jiang Zheng suddenly said, “Young Master, if you want, you can take more. After the blood fills the magic formation, the amount would be quickly restored.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s fine, I just need a little bit for research. The rest can be provided by the Space. Right, those people you captured, are you confident that they’re spies?”

Jiang Zheng nodded and said, “Yes, they’re all suspected spies. Now that they had been captured or killed, there wouldn’t be any troubles when the siege arrives.”

Zhao Hai nodded. There was no such thing as a legal proceeding in the Underworld. In Three Saint City, Jiang Zheng and the others’ words were practically law. If they want to deal with someone, then they wouldn’t need a reason to do so.

Zhao Hai said, “Did you kill those undead?”

Jiang Zheng shook his head and said, “We didn’t, will they be useful to the Young Master?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Take them here and I’ll throw them to the Space. Then after they come under my control, we can ask them about who wants to deal with us.”

Jiang Zheng stared, then he smiled before he made some orders. Before long, Skeleton and Zombie soldiers led the detained Undead in. Zhao Hai wasn’t polite as he threw them all into the Space. After they had been subdued by the Space, Zhao Hai took them back out.

When these undead came out, they already belonged to Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai looked at the undead and said, “So you are the spies sent to the city, which group do you belong to?”

Just as he said that, a Vampire quickly replied, “Vampire Count Eric has seen the Young Master. The undead present here aren’t all of us. There are still those who are hiding inside the city. We are Vampire King Addison’s subordinates.

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “You go lead the others to capture those who weren’t taken.” Eric nodded before he turned around and left. Jiang Zheng also directed the Zombies and Skeletons to help in the capture.

When Eric left the tower, Jiang Zheng immediately turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, how about taking all of the Undead here into the Space, make them into your people?”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think about doing this. But as soon as Jiang Zheng brought it up, he began to contemplate on the idea.

After careful thinking, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It’s possible, but it will be troublesome. After all, these Undead have their own lives. If they are going to be captured now, they will certainly resist.”

Jiang Zheng quickly replied, “Young Master, although it’ll cost us right now, as long as we bring those Undead into the Space, then our strength will be greatly increased. When the time comes, we wouldn’t need to be afraid of those who will attack us.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, military strength was what he didn’t lack the most. Let alone this Undead City, even if it was an even bigger city, he still wouldn’t be moved. However, Jiang Zheng had good intentions, so Zhao Hai just nodded and said, “Alright, let’s do it. I will open spatial rifts in the City. You can send the other Undead through those rifts.”

Jiang Zheng nodded and began to prepare. Zhao Hai made an intention in his mind as spatial rifts appeared everywhere in the city. At the same time, he also released a large number of his own Undead. Before long, fighting sounds could be heard inside Three Saint City. Zhao Hai didn’t care about this. With his Undead as well as the troops inside Three Saint City, taking those creatures into the Space wouldn’t be an issue.

Jiang Zheng and Zhao Hai’s action was swift, everything was done within a day. All of the Undead inside Three Saint City has been captured. On the other hand, the magic formation of the entire city was still being irrigated by the Blood Spring.

The captured Undead had been released back from the Space, but now they were under Zhao Hai’s command. Zhao Hai didn’t manage them and just passed the responsibility over to Jiang Zheng and Guli. However, he went to look for Eric in order to learn more about Vampire King Addison.

But much to Zhao Hai’s disappointment, Eric hadn’t seen Addison before. This was because Eric’s rank was still quite low. He was a subordinate to a Vampire Prince, but his task was given to him by a Vampire Marquis. As for the other matters, Eric simply had no idea.

Chapter 1000: Spiritual Confrontation

The levels of the Underworld were very strict. Take Three Saint City for example, since all of the Undead in this city were weaker than Guli and the others, whether they were captured or not, they would still need to listen to Guli and the others’ words.

And Eric was just a Vampire Count, an identity placed in the middle-lower rank among the Vampires. If this was the human race, he was at most a lower-ranked noble, just a bit more powerful than the commoners. But compared to the Great Nobles, people like him were simply nothing.

Eric can only be regarded as a Captain in Addison’s reconnaissance team. Naturally, he wasn’t qualified to see Addison himself, but he knew about the Vampire King’s strength.

Through Eric’s words, Zhao Hai came to a certain understanding with regards to Addison’s strength. There was no doubt that Addison was a pinnacle existence in the Resistance Army. At this moment, he controls over 20 cities no smaller than Three Saint City. Moreover, all of the undead on those cities who opposed him were all killed. Then he took their fiery souls out and then rewarded them to his loyal men. It can be said that his overall strength was ten times more than Three Saint City.

Just as said in the Art of War: “It is the rule in war, if our forces are ten to the enemy’s one, to surround him.” Addison’s strength was equal to ten Three Saint Cities. In this case, Addison naturally wouldn’t give Three Saint City a chance. But at the same time, Zhao Hai was also able to see at Addison’s conduct. It seems like the Vampire King was a very cautious person. His military strength was ten times that of the enemy, but he still sends reconnaissance teams to see the situation inside. This in itself can explain his character. People like these weren’t easily dealt with.

When Eric relayed Addison’s strength, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Eric, what attacking methods do Vampires have?”

As soon as he heard this question, Eric immediately said, “We Vampires have a lot of ways to attack. We can use sound attacks, we can also grow claws to attack the enemy. At the same time, we also have blood attacks as well as Dark Energy attacks.”

Zhao Hai nodded. To be honest, these attacking methods were within his expectations. From what Jiang Zheng said, Vampires were evolved forms of Vampire Bats. Since this was the case, Zhao Hai can deduce that they would have sound attacks.

As for the other forms of offense, Zhao Hai expected them as well. In the Underworld, two energies were the most prevalent, first is the Dark Energy in the Dark Mist, and the other was the Blood Energy from the Blood Ponds. With the Vampire’s evolutionary system, it wouldn’t be strange if they were able to use these two.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Eric and said, “Alright, Eric. You can go back to the Space. Practice well and maybe you’ll become a Vampire King in the future.”

Eric nodded before he was sent by Zhao Hai to the Space. This was the first Vampire that Zhao Hai had taken into the Space. Although this Vampire had some differences to the ones on Earth, but they also have similarities. To be honest, after he saw Eric, Zhao Hai felt a little warm. It looks like he had seen those Vampires that were being depicted back on Earth.

Shortly after that, Zhao Hai arrived right by the room’s window. This window had no glass pane. After all, wind or no wind, to the Lich, it didn’t matter. And at the same time, there were no winds in the Underworld, only fog; the Dark Mist.

After Zhao Hai discovered that there was no wind in the Underworld, he didn’t bother renovating the towers’ windows. In Zhao Hai’s mind, there was absolutely no need to do so.

Zhao Hai didn’t know what magic formation Kampala used, but the Dark Mist couldn’t enter the room. There was also some light on the room’s ceiling. The magic light was quite faint, it was soft enough to feel accommodated inside the room.

Actually, one couldn’t see anything when standing in front of the window. Aside from the ever-changing form of the Dark MIst, you can hardly see anything else. However, the window made the room feel more like a room.

On the three towers, only this top room had windows installed, the other floors didn’t. This also demonstrated that the top floors were the master’s rooms, a place of special status.

Zhao Hai quietly faced the window. He looked at the changing Dark Mist as though it was an ever-moving behemoth. His heart couldn’t help but be moved.

He was really grateful for transmigrating. His crossing over made him obtain things he would never have on Earth. It allowed him to experience the mysteries of the universe. If Zhao Hai didn’t cross over, then he wouldn’t have imagined that a place as mystical as the Underworld exists.

Zhao Hai was a nerd back on Earth, always afraid of getting into trouble, a complete introvert. In fact, nobody knew that he was a fire wrapped in ice, someone who had drank dog’s blood, someone who was a hidden beast.

Although such people didn’t look any different compared to the others, but their face was just a disguise. Their hearts were indifferent and they were able to ignore feelings and even life. Only a few people can have this mindset. Their minds were akin to a wide lake. Even if a stone was thrown in and cause ripples, the lake would still calm down in time.

Because of this indifference, Zhao Hai was able to quickly adapt himself to the life in the Ark Continent. This allowed him to kill people without hesitation; dozens, hundreds, thousands, or even millions. Besides the other people who he cared about, he wasn’t really concerned about the other people.

The more someone was like this, the harder they were to move. Unless they find something that interests them more, then they would just decide to settle down. Back on Earth, Zhao Hai was like this. He stayed home all the time because he had found something that he liked to do, and that was indulging in fantasy worlds. He even confessed in his own articles that this was what he liked to do; always staying at home.

In fact, Zhao Hai had another thing that he liked to do, and that was to travel. But unfortunately, travelling was very expensive in Earth. Zhao Hai had no money so he could only suppress this desire. It was also for this reason that Zhao Hai didn’t fancy sports cars but instead he opted for RVs. He liked to imagine himself driving his own RV while travelling every corner of the world.

But on Earth, he could only dream of this. Because at that time, there was no need to say about RVs, he couldn’t even afford a conventional car.

And now, in the Ark Continent, he almost had everything that he didn’t have on Earth; a warm home, women who he loved and loved him. At the same time, he was also able to gain great power. And besides these, Zhao Hai was also able to see sceneries that he wasn’t able to see back on Earth. It was precisely because of this that Zhao Hai transferred his dreams of travelling to the Ark Continent. He wanted to make up for his second desire back on Earth.

Because of this subconscious desire, Zhao Hai was interested in travelling to the Demon Realm, the Divine Realm, the Atlanta Plane, and now to the Underworld. Moreover, he also believed that he would be able to explore the Cultivation Realm soon.

Although he couldn’t see the situation in the Underworld, his Divine Sense made up for it. It was a feeling that he wasn’t able to enjoy before. So after feeling the novelty of the matter, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get excited.

Zhao Hai slowly closed his eyes as he felt the situation inside the city. Presently, dozens of Undead were being sent to the spatial rifts by his undead. Guli and Jiang Zheng’s subordinates were doing the same. Although there were some resistance, with Zhao Hai’s army present, it didn’t take long before the Undead were sent to the Space. When they came out, they were already on Zhao Hai’s side.

At this time, Zhao Hai suddenly felt a very strong spiritual wave. The wave was heading towards Three Saint City to search it. Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he opened his eyes fiercely and intensifying his spiritual sense, directly clashing with the incoming wave.

Naturally, the other party was able to sense Zhao Hai, it then proceeded to clash.

Boom!

Their spiritual force silently clashed in the air. Others couldn’t hear this clash, but since Zhao Hai heard this, he believed that the other party heard it as well.

This mental collision was just a probe. However, a clash like this was still dangerous. If one loses, then they might turn into idiots, or even be brain dead.

This time, the clash of the two parties wasn’t weak, and they also didn’t retrieve their spiritual force. Zhao Hai’s mental power was like a spiked shield, covering the entire Three Saint City. On the other hand, the enemy’s mental power was like a net full of barbs. It was constantly looking for loopholes in Zhao Hai’s mental strength.

Nets and shields, these two items didn’t seem like they had any attacking power. However, with the thorns and the barbs present, they became vicious weapons. It can be seen that both sides weren’t easily trifled with.

Ordinary undead couldn’t feel the confrontation. They just felt that there was a sudden pressure appearing in the sky above Three Saint City. This gave these undead the feeling of unprecedented crisis.

One must know that these Undead were intelligent, so they knew this feeling clearly. The Undead who were still resisting had almost lost their strength. They just stood there and stared as they were taken to the Space.

On the other hand, Guli and Jiang Zheng were able to feel the clash. Since they were able to sense it, then they were also able to know how terrifying the two parties involved were.

Chapter 1001: Violent Wind and Acid Rain!

The spiritual force coming from the other party was still going on. However, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried. He discovered that the  other party’s attack was just a probe. Even if Zhao Hai didn’t counter-attack, this attack would just serve as a warning.

The enemy’s spiritual force was very formidable. However, the distance was too far. Zhao Hai believed that the opposite party was at a minimum two days away. So even if the enemy was powerful, it was still impossible for them to kill Guli and the others with just their spiritual force.

However, the other party still made Zhao Hai vigilant. This was because Zhao Hai knew how strong one would need in order to attack Three Saint City from such a distance. The enemy wasn’t someone that should be underestimated.

In fact, Zhao Hai was able to achieve this ability as well. After all, he had the Succubus Clan inside the Space. And the Succubi were innately skilled in spiritual force.

Zhao Hai could do it, but to do it in the same way as the other party, he couldn’t. Although he had learned the method of the Succubi, he couldn’t maintain it for a long time. So he could definitely do the attack, but he couldn’t do it at the same degree as the enemy.

However, Zhao Hai still continued to attack. He believed that the other party couldn’t compete with him in spiritual strength. This was because such a battle was dangerous. Even someone as strong as the other party wouldn’t go all out, that would be courting death, the losses to be suffered wasn’t small.

But if the other party has this formidable spiritual force, then his other skills would certainly be as good. In the Underworld, there were a lot of benefits if one has strong spiritual force, but one couldn’t rely on this at the very beginning. This was because spiritual force couldn’t be supported by a weak body. Otherwise, one would only become food to other Undead.

In the Underworld, besides the Lich, every other race needed to have strong physical bodies. The Lich body was only powerful because they had the ability to negate all physical attacks.

At this point, Zhao Hai was becoming more and more eager to fight the enemy. He wanted to see how formidable they really were.

It was also at this time that the other party discovered that his own spiritual force was unable to threaten the Undead in Three Saint City. The spiritual power of the entity inside Three Saint City wasn’t any weaker than him. Perhaps the entity might not be as strong in skill, but he certainly wasn’t weaker in overall strength. Because of this, the other party decided to retreat.

After seeing that the enemy had drawn back, Zhao Hai also retrieved his spiritual force. And as he was retrieving his spiritual force, he also swept the entire Three Saint City. Zhao Hai was impressed with Guli and Jiang Zheng’s efficiency. They had taken advantage of the spiritual pressure and taken almost all of the undead into the Space. Now, only a small number of Undead were left uncaptured. However, these undead have already lost their resistance, capturing them would be much easier.

When he saw this situation, Zhao Hai immediately said, “Guli, Jiang Zheng, come here.”

Zhao Hai’s sound spread all throughout Three Saint City. Guli and Jiang Zheng immediately complied and quickly went to Zhao Hai’s tower.

Before long, the two arrived at Zhao Hai’s room. Zhao Hai was sitting inside, when he saw the two arrive, he nodded and said, “Come sit.”

The two complied and sat down. After that, Guli said, “Young Master, I felt a spiritual attack. Is it the Vampire King?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Right. It should be Addison’s spiritual attack. But this time, it was only sent as a probe. You don’t need to be worried. If he led his people here, then it would take two days. During that time, you would be able to prepare Three Saint City.”

Jiang Zheng and Guli were startled. Although Zhao Hai was here, Addison’s presence had already seeped deep into their bones. So when they heard that Addison was two days away, the two couldn’t help but get nervous.

Zhao Hai looked at their eyes and smiled faintly, “Don’t be afraid. His spiritual force might not be weak, but he isn’t that strong. There’s no need to worry.”

As soon as they heard this, Guli and Jiang Zheng let out a long breath. In addition to their fear of Addison, they were also worried about Zhao Hai. Now that they were loyal to Zhao Hai, they didn’t want Zhao Hai to get into bad situations. If Zhao Hai hadn’t said this, then they would’ve urged him to go to the Space and avoid fighting with Addison.

Zhao Hai looked at the two people and said, “I’m not familiar with the battles in the Underworld, so I’ll leave that to you to arrange. Remember, two days.” The two nodded before they turned around to leave.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly before calling Laura and the others over. The women had long been curious about the Underworld, but when they came out, they couldn’t see anything besides the Dark Mist. This made them dislike staying here any longer, so they opted to return to the Space. Zhao Hai didn’t stop them since he also wanted to momentarily return to the Space. He wanted to feel the difference between the Ark Continent and the Underworld.

Although the fight between the O’Neal family and the Foreign Races was still going on, Zhao Hai didn’t worry much about it. At this time, the battles of both sides weren’t very fierce. This was because both parties couldn’t afford going all out. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get disappointed when the higher level magic armor didn’t appear.

Zhao Hai had a rare moment of solitude. He had left Laura and the others to oversee the battle between the O’Neal family and the Foreign Races.

Two days went by in a blink of an eye. In these two days, the spiritual attack didn’t appear in Three Saint City anymore. Zhao Hai knew that the other party was aware that spiritual attacks were useless, so he didn’t bother using it. Instead, the other party would rather attack instead.

Just as Zhao Hai estimated, two days later, Guli and Jiang Zheng felt a large amount of undead souls slowly surrounding Three Saint City.

Guli and Jiang Zheng didn’t do anything. In fact, wars in the Underworld were very simple. It wasn’t like in the Divine Realm or the Ark Continent where there were advanced weapons. Here, low-level Undead only had stone or rocks as weapons. This was because their levels were insufficient for them to be able to make bone weapons.

Zhao Hai didn’t make a move as he stood at his tower and swept the surroundings with his spiritual force. Three Saint City has been surrounded by Undead. Most of these Undead were Skeletons and Zombies. There were also Dark Creatures and Vampires. Meanwhile, there weren’t much Lich present.

Zhao Hai also discovered that in the direction where the spiritual attack came from, there were ten huge tents present. Unlike other places where there were Undead standing, this place was a huge clearing. The bone fence stopped the other Undead from entering. The tents were also made out of Dark Creature skin. This made the camp look more like a human barracks.

Guli and Jiang Zheng were standing beside Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get curious upon seeing this so he turned and asked, “Guli, Jiang Zheng, I feel quite puzzled about why Three Saint City had so many houses. And now, the other party had set up tents outside. Is shelter really useful to you?”

Guli and Jiang Zheng completely understood Zhao Hai’s confusion. They were Undead, and properly speaking, there was no need for them to build houses. Guli immediately replied, “Young Master, you might not know, but in the Underworld, Besides the Dark Mist and the Blood Pond, there are other two elements that affects our lives. If the Dark MIst and the Blood Pond are the source of our strength, then Acid Rain and Violent Winds are our bringers of death.”

Zhao Hai asked, “Oh, there’s something like that? Tell me more.”

Jiang Zheng continued, “Acid Rains and Violent Winds don’t happen often in the Underworld. But when they come, they would take away the life, or death, of countless Undead. Acid Rain is a black and acidic downpour of liquid. This rain had a corrosive effect on our bodies as well as our fiery souls. Some low-level Undead wouldn’t be able to last an hour under an Acid Rain. This rain is a unique phenomenon in the Underworld. On the other hand, every time Violent Winds arrive, the Dark Mist that benefits us a lot would suddenly become extremely turbulent. It will form an unprecedented tornado and as long as an undead gets entangled with it, then they wouldn’t be able to find an easy way out. Even someone on my level would have a very hard time surviving.”

Upon hearing Jiang Zheng, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be surprised. Jiang Zheng and Guli’s strength, even in the Divine Realm, was placed on the topmost level. And now, it seems like Violent Winds would be able to kill them off. This shows how devilish these winds really were.

Actually, for people in Guli and Jiang Zheng’s level, there were very little things that could threaten them. Zhao Hai didn’t expect that there would be two things that could kill them in the Underworld. This infinite universe did indeed have a lot of strange things.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai asked once more, “Are Acid Rains and Violent Winds frequent?”

Guli and Jiang Zheng shook their heads. Then Guli answered, “They don’t happen that often. Acid Rains occur more than Violent Winds. Acid Rains happen maybe once every three to five years, there’s no fixed cycle. But as for Violent Winds, nobody really knows when. Sometimes they are frequent, maybe once every few months. And there were also time where it didn’t appear for dozens of years.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “So your houses and tents can prevent Acid Rains. But if Violent Winds arrive, then how could your shelters help you?”

Guli shook his head and said, “Young Master, our shelters can only help us survive the Acid Rain. As for Violent Winds, once they arrive, the city would activate its magic formation. The magic formation would protect the city from the onslaught of the Violent Winds.”

Chapter 1002: Why Don’t You Submit To Me?

Zhao Hai nodded. In the Ark Continent, magic formations weren’t capable of resisting natural disasters. But in the Underworld, they could. Perhaps this was something that was brought up because of the environment.

Just as Zhao Hai was about to reply, a calm voice was suddenly heard, “Kampala, Guli, Jiang Zheng, come out and meet me!”

This voice was somewhat ice-cold. The words weren’t said quickly, making one feel that the speaker was unflustered. This made Zhao Hai curious.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Since he called us, then we might as well take a look. I want to see what this Vampire King looks like.” Then Zhao Hai’s figure moved as he flew out from the tower and headed towards the direction of Addison’s voice.

Jiang Zheng and Guli also hastily followed behind. Before long, the three had flown out of Three Saint City. It didn’t take long until a group of people appeared across from them. These people stopped five meters away from Zhao Hai’s group.

Altogether, there were 20 people in this group. This includes two Lich, ten Skeletons, five Zombies, and three Vampires.

Standing in front of this group was a Vampire wearing a black dress. His dress was embroidered with gold, it looked very gorgeous. His hair was neatly tied with a black tie. The man was handsome, but he was on the softer androgynous side. His face was very pale, a kind of pale white skin that hasn’t seen the the sun for a long time. He had two red eyes, looking like two red gems.

He was gracefully standing there, looking like a true king gazing at his own subordinates. This kind of temperament was something that just subconsciously comes out of a person. It made the recipient of this temperament feel like they were inferior.

While Zhao Hai was sizing up Addison, Addison was also sizing up Zhao Hai. The first time Addison felt Zhao Hai, his eyes shrank a bit. This was because Zhao Hai had a heartbeat as well as life aura. But when he saw Zhao Hai’s appearance, Addison began to relax, he was finally able to identify Zhao Hai as a Dark Pharaoh.

However, Addison also paid more attention to Zhao Hai even if he was relieved. He knew that Zhao Hai was the one who fought with him before. Addison couldn’t help but look at Zhao Hai more carefully.

As he looked at Zhao Hai, Addison became even more curious. In the Underworld, he was someone who stood on top, so there would inevitably some pressure coming out from him. It was a majesty that was present in a king. An aura that indicated to ordinary Undead that they should surrender, otherwise they would be killed.

And Addison, who had clashed with Zhao Hai, suddenly discovered that Zhao Hai didn’t have the same aura. What’s wrong? This made Addison very puzzled.

After looking at Zhao Hai for a while, Addison said, “Who are you? Where’s Kampala?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “This one is Zhao Hai. Kampala is not here, he went to another place.”

Addison looked at the people behind Zhao Hai. And like guards, Guli and Jiang Zheng were there. Addison’s expression slightly changed as he asked, “Jiang Zheng, Guli, what is going on?”

Jiang Zheng looked at Addison and smiled, “We have already pledged our allegiance to Mister Zhao Hai, Kampala did the same. Any matter you want to say can be said to Mister Zhao Hai.” After he said that Jiang Zheng proceeded to shut up.

Addison looked at Zhao Hai in surprise. He didn’t think that Zhao Hai would be able to subdue Kampala’s group. He didn’t know Kampala and the others for just a day or two, he knew how different the three of them were compared to the others in the Resistance army. They didn’t want authority, instead they wanted freedom. Because of this, the three of them didn’t join any faction and won’t bow to any other. And now that they had submitted to Zhao Hai, Addison was surprised.

Addison looked at Zhao Hai for some time before he said, “Alright, since I’m supposed to talk to you. Zhao Hai, I think you should already be aware of the Underworld’s situation.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I know a thing or two.”

Addison nodded and said, “You should know that the reason why the Rebel army isn’t able to hit the Dark Tempe is because the Dark Temple is acting as a whole, under one leader. On the other hand, the Resistance army is scattered, simply cannot muster up enough fighting strength. In this case, it’s natural for us to suffer a loss. Because of this, the Resistance army needs to unite and form a whole entity. Only by doing so could we defeat the Dark Temple.”

Zhao hai nodded and said, “What you said is true. But what does this have to do with Your Majesty bringing your army here to surround Three Saint City?”

When Addison heard Zhao Hai, his nose almost scrunched up. Naturally, he didn’t believe that Zhao Hai was unaware of what was going on. Zhao Hai was obviously acting stupid. This stoked Addison’s anger.

There weren’t any qualified politicians in the Underworld, so Addison wasn’t able to hold his temper as he flared up. He looked coldly at Zhao Hai and said, “Submit to me. Treat me as your King, or else you’ll die!”

Zhao Hai looked at Addison, then he suddenly laughed and said, “It’s still early, yet you’re already spouting nonsense. And why would I submit to you? Why don’t you submit to me instead?”

When Addison heard Zhao Hai, his two ruby like eyes shone. Two sharp fangs sprang out from his mouth as his expression turned fierce. Then he opened his mouth and sent out a horrifying scream.

Just as Addison’s eyes changed, Zhao Hai had already covered his group with a protective shield. At the same time, he also took all of the Undead in Three Saint City into the Space.

When these Undead were released from the Space before, they already had the Space’s imprint. If Zhao Hai wanted to send them to the Space, then he would only need to make an intention to do so.

When Addison opened his mouth, a transparent energy erupted out. A wave of energy went out from his mouth and headed towards Zhao Hai and the others. This was a unique skill to the Vampires, a sound attack.

The sound attack went straight towards Zhao Hai. The distance between Addison and Zhao Hai was only five meters, but such a close distance was not a big deal for experts like Addison. He wouldn’t even need less than a blink of time to reach that distance. This made the sound attack reach its target in no time.

But when the sound attack was about to reach Zhao Hai, a shield suddenly appeared to block it. The shield appeared as fast as the sound attack went, absorbing it and eliminating it altogether.

Addison saw that the attack didn’t receive the effect he expected it to have and immediately attacked Zhao Hai using his hand. His nails glimmered with red, indicating that it was sharp.

To counteract this attack, a sword quickly appeared in Zhao Hai’s hand. The two moved very fast that Addison didn’t have time to change his attack. However, he didn’t think much about it, he just went through and clashed with Zhao Hai’s sword. Zhao Hai didn’t move as well as he met Addison’s hand with his sword.

Just as Addison’s hand caught Zhao Hai’s sword, a bang was suddenly heard. Flames came out of the sword before it vanished.

The sword that Zhao Hai just used was the fire element sword that was made from Kampala’s compression magic. Addison didn’t suspect anything since Zhao Hai used the Underworld’s yin fire in order to make the sword instead of the Space’s yang fire.

Zhao Hai was very clear, although yang fire was very effective against Addison, he knew that he shouldn’t use it in the Underworld. If he used yang fire, then Addison would suspect his identity. When the time comes, the whole Underworld would know that there was a spatial rift. It would affect Zhao Hai’s plan so he didn’t use yang fire.

Addison clearly had some reservations about yin fire. He retracted his claws as he grasped in the air and took out a cross sword.

This cross sword was silver white, the hilt was like a bat that had expanded its wings. The blade wasn’t straight but instead it snaked out. Other than that, it was a standard cross sword. It was gorgeous as it was sturdy.

When Zhao Hai saw this, he also extended his hand as he took out his own sword. This wasn’t the usual sword that people would describe. It was a overly curved sword, it looks like a scimitar but it was double-edged. [1]

As the two took their weapons out, they immediately began to attack once more. A collision could be heard, but this time it didn’t make any explosion since there was nothing made out of fire element.

After the two clashed, they immediately separated. Addison looked at the curved sword in Zhao Hai’s hand and said, “Where did you get your weapon from?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Where did you get your weapon from?”

Addison coldly snorted as he flew once more towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai didn’t retreat as he charged as well. The two moved fast and their swords continuously clashed. Dang, dang, dang, dang. Rapid successions of this sound was heard to the point where their collisions could no longer be counted.

After a while the two men entered the Dark Mist. Their figures could no longer be seen, only the sounds of their swords could be heard.

When Addison’s men saw their King vanish, they turned their gazes towards Guli and Jiang Zheng Guli and Jiang Zheng looked at the other party and immediately knew what they were thinking. Guli quickly took his sword out as Jiang Zheng’s nails grew longer. Addison’s men roared before throwing themselves towards the enemy.

Guli and Jiang Zheng were completely inferior in numbers. Just as the two were beginning to get flustered, a large group of Skeletons appeared around them. These Undead immediately turned towards the approaching enemies and blocked them..

Addison’s subordinates were startled upon seeing these Skeletons. They discovered that even if these Skeletons were inferior, they actually formed battle formations and were very well coordinated. They suddenly found that they weren’t able to simply deal with these Skeleton troop.

Upon seeing the situation, Addison’s subordinates immediately screamed. This scream not only disturbed the enemy, it also summoned their men. When the screams went out, the undead surrounding Three Saint City began to attack.

In the minds of Addison’s men, the strength of Three Saint City definitely wouldn’t be able to stop their attack. And because Jiang Zheng and Guli were outside, the magic formation hasn’t been activated. It seems like Three Saint City was about to be broken through.

Ideas were sweet, but reality was cruel. Under the gaze of the attackers, countless skeletons began to stream out of Three Saint City. These Skeletons were not only powerful, they were also numerous. The attackers were quick to discover that their forces began to suffer losses.

Such a change made them surprised. This was far from their expectations. They didn’t expect Three Saint City to have this many troops.

As the battle of Three Saint City became heated, the same was true with the fight between Zhao Hai and Addison. At this point, nobody could see their figures. The two increased their speed to the extreme. The swords in their hands danced quickly as spark upon spark appeared. The sounds of their impact were like fried beans resounding one after another, there was no moment of pause.

Besides their swords, the two didn’t use any other tricks. They were already too deep into the battle and their swords were already going too fast. There simply was no way for them to use other tricks, this was because they can feel that if they were distracted, then they would be stabbed by the other party’s sword. For masters like them, even a small wound would greatly impact their ability. Once the other party’s energy enters their body, then they would certainly suffer serious internal injuries.

Regarding such experts, even a small slash on the skin would prove fatal. If the other’s sword pierces their skin, then that would mean that their defense had been broken. The enemy’s energy would quickly invade their bodies and may proceed to shatter their internal organs.

Because of this, nobody dared to divert their attention from swinging their sword. As though they were perpetually locked into battle, the two didn’t leave any opportunity for the other party to take advantage of.

At this time, a Skeleton suddenly appeared amongst them. The two paused in an instant before separating. Then both looked at  the other in fear.

They were fully immersed in their fight to think about anything else. But now that they had separated, they suddenly felt that they had consumed a lot of energy. With experts like Zhao Hai and Addison, the energy consumed would surely be terrifying.

The two knew that they had been too focused on their fight that they completely neglected anything else. They were aware that they had swung their swords as though they were possessed. If the skeleton didn’t appear, then the two of them would have fought until they died of exhaustion!

* * *

This is how I imagine it. Malthael from Diablo 3.

Chapter 1003: Fighting a Wolf with a Flex Stalk

Died of exhaustion!

This was something that some people would never worry about. But there were also some who knew that the more powerful an Expert was, the more susceptible they were to this phenomenon.

Just like Zhao Hai and Addison! Upon meeting a well-matched opponent, they didn’t dare to divert any attention, especially in the heat of the battle. They were afraid that a single mishap in their concentration would give the opponent the opportunity to kill them. Because of this, they were focused on the match. Their instincts had taken over their bodies, they were simply unable to know how much energy they’ve already spent.

In this case, if there were no external stimulus, then it would be too late for them to discover that they had used up all of their strengths. In the end, they would only exhaust themself to death, even Zhao Hai was not safe from this outcome.

The reason for this was because Zhao Hai had underestimated Addison. Addison was a rank higher than Guli and the others. But Guli and the others were already peak God-ranks. If they were in the Divine Realm, then they would already be Supreme Elders, needing only one step before ascension. In other words, if Addison was in the Divine Realm, then he would have already ascended.

Being an ascendant meant that Addison was himself already a cultivator. Although Addison had yet to ascend, his strength was actually at a level of a cultivator, a rank equal to Zhao Hai. And although Zhao Hai’s energy was very solid, his body’s rate of using this energy was still inefficient.

On the other hand, although Addison’s energy wasn’t as solid as Zhao Hai, his physique made him equal to Zhao Hai. And with their high-intensity battle, their bodies weren’t able to supplement their usage on time. That was to say that the two were having difficulty making ends meet. If it wasn’t for that skeleton, then it would have been very difficult to save the two of them.

The two examined the state of their bodies and immediately felt a sense of fear. The appearance of the skeleton was too timely. Naturally, it was impossible for Addison to know how the skeleton appeared. On the other hand, Zhao Hai was aware that the skeleton was sent by Laura and the others. It must have been them who discovered the current situation and decided to send the skeleton to stop it. When he thought about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel that his love for his wives had deepened much further.

Naturally, there was no such thing as a useless battle. This meant that Zhao Hai had deepened his understanding of martial arts with this experience. He had discovered a fault in the Ark Continent and the Divine Realm’s system. And this fault was no other than Domains!

Zhao Hai used to think that the Domains used by the Experts of the Ark Continent and the Divine Realm were extremely powerful. Not only was it powerful, it’s attack and defense were also good. At the same time, it could also help in absorbing the energy of the heavens and the earth.

But when Zhao Hai got stronger and stronger, he used his Domain less and less. He always felt that the Domain hinders him from using 100% of his strength.

And now, after battling with Addison, Zhao Hai finally understood why. He discovered that Domains were a mistake.

Domains might look very good; they can attack, they can defend, and they can also replenish your energy. But because of these characteristics, the Domain couldn’t focus all of its energy in offense. This might not be a problem ordinarily, but when people of the same strength fight, it can be deadly.

Take Zhao Hai for example, if he established his Domain, then he would have to allocate his strength to maintain it. Additionally, he would have to think about the changes in his Domain, hindering him from using 100% of his attack. Also, each attack made by a Domain was very wide, the shape of the energy was huge. Although it seemed formidable, but the lethality of the attack wouldn’t be as desired.

If one concentrates the power of a Domain in an attack instead of just supporting a Domain, then one’s power would double!

Take Zhao Hai’s battle against Addison for example. Both of them used their swords at their fastest and most lethal state. And Zhao Hai can be certain that each of their slashes could easily tear open a God-rank expert’s Domain and kill them immediately. In addition to the difference in level, this was also caused by the existence of the Domain. A Domain would spread the utility of the user’s strength. The situation was just like a piece of iron cut into two equal halves, if one half was made into a square meter sheet while the other was made into an iron dagger, then can their offensive strength be the same? No. There was no doubt that the dagger would easily pierce through the sheet.

Naturally, one couldn’t say that Domains were useless. If they were used to cultivate, then Domains were really good. When the Domain wasn’t attacked nor being used to attack, then the Domain would be able to efficiently absorb energy. Although the Domain would consume a part of the energy, the absorption was more than what it consumed. This was beneficial to a person’s strength.

These thoughts only flashed through Zhao Hai’s mind. His attention was still concentrated on Addison’s body.

Addison was so terrifying that Zhao Hai didn’t dare to be careless. If he didn’t have the Space nor the Hell King’s ship, then Addison would definitely be his equal.

Addison held the same sentiment towards Zhao Hai. When he and Zhao Hai clashed, Addison discovered that Zhao Hai wasn’t very skilled at using his power at first. So in the beginning, Addison held the upper hand. But as the battle progressed and Zhao Hai got more comfortable with his strength, the battle went to a standstill.

It was precisely because of this equality that made Addison enter a dangerous situation with Zhao Hai. He had to concentrate the entire fight to the point that he didn’t have the capacity to monitor the energy that he had used.

The two separated for a hundred meters and stood quietly. Although they couldn’t see each other now, they can clearly feel each others’ presence. It can be said that even if a hair on the other party moved, the other would immediately find out.

The two didn’t attack. In fact, both of them were worried. Just after the fight, the two had become aware of the other’s strength. Like a chinese proverb, ‘fighting a wolf with a flex stalk – either is afraid of each other.’[1]

Addison’s spiritual force was locked into Zhao Hai. Naturally, he knew that Zhao Hai’s spiritual force was also locked into him. Addison felt bitter. He didn’t think that the Underworld would spawn such a powerful Dark Pharaoh. Moreover, he heard that Dark Pharaohs were primarily mages, how could this one’s close-combat capabilities be so strong?

Neither of them dared to sheath their swords. Since the two were focused on each other, once one of them took back their weapon, then the other could immediately launch an attack.

Not to say about receiving their sword, neither dared to talk as well. Although the two weren’t fighting and were only armed, the battle became more imposing and patient instead. The one who spoke first would lose their momentum.

This had been the most thrilling battle that Zhao Hai experienced since he went out. It can be said that he was taking careful steps, any mistake would cause him to be overwhelmed.

However, the two also knew that the battle could only continue in this situation. The one who determined the winner and loser weren’t the two of them, but their men who were still fighting below.

The two combatants, with their strength, surely had their own people who would fight for them. Because of this, their battle didn’t only involve themselves, but it included their overall strength. Their men could kill the other’s men and establish momentum. A Great King would be able to overwhelm a smaller country because his country was stronger, his momentum was more pronounced than the other. A King didn’t only fight on his own, his country would be involved as well.

Addison’s confidence was very strong. He believed that his men could deal with Three Saint City. He didn’t know Three Saint City for a day or two, he already understood that although Three Saint City was strong, it was still far compared to him. He believed that as long as he kept Zhao Hai here, then his people would be able to easily clean Three Saint City up. When the time comes, he would be able to overwhelm Zhao Hai with his momentum and then win.

But at the same time, Zhao Hai’s confidence wasn’t any weaker. If Addison was confident in his men, then Zhao Hai was more confident in his. Addison’s men couldn’t possibly contend against a billion undead. Moreover, Zhao Hai’s undead weren’t weak. Dealing with Addison’s men shouldn’t be a problem.

Also, Zhao Hai found some faults when he scanned the Undead outside the city using his spiritual force. These undead didn’t seem to learn battle formations. They were chaotic and had little to no order. Even if Zhao Hai commanded the battle, he could still laugh at the ease of dealing with these undead.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai’s undead were already adept in the battlefield. And with Lizzy and Megan commanding them, defeating the enemy would be very easy.

Zhao Hai initially had some concerns of the Dark Mist blocking the Space’s monitor. After all, back in the Ark Continent, the monitor wasn’t able to see through the Dark Mist.

However, after entering the Underworld, the Space had adapted to the Dark Mist. The Underworld was now clearly seen on the monitor. Because of this, Zhao Hai was confident that his Undead would be able to defeat Addison’s men.

* * *

麻杆打狼—两头怕 — Each party is fearful of the other: the wolf thought the stalk could be a fatal weapon while the person fears the consequence of his trick seen through by the wolf. source[https://people.wku.edu/haiwang.yuan/China/proverbs/m.html]

Chapter 1004: The War of Three Saint City

Lizzy and the others were truly diligent. They also noted Zhao Hai’s situation. They didn’t expect Addison to push him to this point.

Since Zhao Hai had the help of the Space, he almost had a carefree journey and hadn’t met too many dangers. Even if he encountered some roadblocks, it was still easily solved. Moreover, Zhao Hai wasn’t physically harmed in these ordeals. To say the most dangerous experience that Zhao Hai had in the past was during his first fight against Lu Wei. At that time, Zhao Hai was almost killed, but in the end he gained a huge advantage.

But this time it was different. Zhao Hai had run into his match, a formidable match at that. Naturally, Lu Wei’s true body was more powerful than Addison, but it was a pity that Lu Wei’s body could never reach here. Because of this, up to date, Addison was the most powerful enemy that Zhao Hai had faced.

While Zhao Hai was fighting against Addison, Lizzy and the others weren’t able to see what was going on. Their cultivation hadn’t reached that level, so they were completely unaware.

But even if they weren’t able to discover it, someone was still able to. This person was none other than Cai’er. Cai’er was now integrated with the Space. And since the Space was dependent on Zhao Hai, nobody could understand Zhao Hai’s situation more than Cai’er.

So when Cai’er sensed that Zhao Hai’s energy had gone out of control, she immediately knew that Zhao Hai was in danger. Because of this, she immediately informed Laura and the others. In the end, the women thought of a way to prevent the situation from worsening. They made a skeleton suddenly appear between the two, disrupting their rhythm and disentangling them from each other.

Their decision was very successful. However, they didn’t expect that after separating, the two would actually stay motionless. Neither spoke and just stood there with their swords in hand. They looked like two statues suspended in the air.

When Laura and the others saw this, they knew that the danger on Zhao Hai still hasn’t been lifted. But now, in this case, they didn’t know what to do.

As the people in the room were getting anxious, Meg, who didn’t usually speak, suddenly said, “Sister Laura, how about we have my Grandfather take a look? My Grandfather is also a God-rank expert, moreover, he’s been in several wars before so he’s quite experienced. Perhaps he can enlighten us on what is happening.”

Upon hearing Meg, Laura stared for a moment and said, “Right, right. Let’s go ask Grandpa Green to come here and take a look.”

Megan nodded before she turned around and left. Before long, Green and Merine arrived in the Space’s Villa. They were cultivating on Wild Dragon Island when they heard the news, so they immediately got up and came over.

While Karen might not like it, Green and Merine loved to cultivate. Because of this, besides managing the affairs of the Island, the two would cultivate in their free time.

When Green entered the room, he immediately said, “What happened? How is the Young Master?”

After giving Green and Merine their greetings, Laura and the others immediately explained the situation and had Green look at the monitor. Since Zhao Hai was respectful towards the two Elders, Laura and the others shared the sentiment as well.

After Green heard about what happened and looked at the monitor, he went silent for some time. Upon seeing Green’s expression, Laura couldn’t help but get a bit anxious as she asked, “Grandpa Green, what’s wrong?”

Green looked back up at the screen and said, “The Young Master and the Vampire King should now be using their spiritual force to lock on to each other. Neither wanted to act rashly. Any slight movement would make the other party attack. Although their current state isn’t in combat, it isn’t any easier than what they were doing before. It’s no longer possible to break this standoff using your previous method. Now, both needed to overwhelm the other with momentum. If the Young Master can do this, then he would defeat the Vampire. Megan, Lizzy, immediately control the undead and end the battle as soon as possible. During this time, make sure to completely crush the Vampire’s subordinates. Only then can Young Master crush the other party’s momentum and win.”

Upon hearing Green, Lizzy and Megan immediately complied. The monitor’s image changed and showed the state of Three Saint City.

Three Saint City was quite lively. But generally speaking, Three Saint City held the advantage. No matter what, Three Saint City held the numerical advantage. Coping with Addison’s subordinates would be easy.

It was just that Lizzy and Megan didn’t take command of the Undead. In their eyes, it was completely unnecessary. The strength of the Undead was very clear. Even if they didn’t take control of them, they would never lose. With their strength, it would be very difficult for the enemy to deal with them. After all, the Undead in their hands were battle-hardened. And since these Undead had some wisdom, even if they weren’t controlled, they would still be able to manage.

But now it was different. Since Green said that Zhao Hai would no longer be in danger once Addison’s undead were quickly settled, Lizzy and Megan were no longer being polite. They immediately took control of the Undead to attack.

Zhao Hai’s undead were quite excellent since they were able to learn battle formations. However, in the battle, the things that they could do were limited.

On the other hand, Lizzy and Megan were different. They were inside the Space looking at the monitor. For them, it was like they were playing chess, gaining an overall vision of the battlefield and were able to make sudden decisions.

Also, this wasn’t the first time that Lizzy and Megan had commanded a battle. Therefore, with their ability, and their anxiety about saving Zhao Hai, the two didn’t hold back. They took control of the undead and launched a full attack against Addison’s Undead.

Although Addison’s Undead were also quite good, they were inferior when it came to battle formations and numbers. They were being pushed back from the very beginning, and with Lizzy and Megan taking control, they were unable to block the assault.

Lizzy and Megan didn’t have the mood to grasp these Undead into the Space, they just directly killed them all. All of a sudden, Addison’s Undead were being killed in massive numbers, their fiery souls were all sent to the Space.

Although the enemy undead were subordinates of Addison, this didn’t mean that they were under his direct control. So even if they die, Addison wouldn’t be able to feel anything. Only the Vampires under Addison would have a direct connection to him. When they die, Addison would immediately feel it.

However, because Addison himself was a Vampire, a Vampire’s position in the army was very high. A dangerous thing such as charging the city wasn’t something that Vampires would do. Naturally, these Vampires who were hiding behind the army wouldn’t be killed. This made Addison unaware of the general state of Three Saint City.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai’s undead were directly under his control. Every death of the Undead would be known by Zhao Hai. However, Zhao Hai didn’t care, he simply had too many Undead in his control. And in a fight like this, it was impossible to not lose anything, so Zhao Hai decided to feel numb towards the losses.

At this time, Zhao Hai and Addison’s consciousness were still locked on to each other, both of them didn’t care about anything happening outside. Although the two were strong and could spare some spiritual force to sense the situation, both of them didn’t dare to get distracted.

But this wasn’t the same case for Lizzy and Megan. The situation of Three Saint City had been completely overturned. Those who were fighting against Guli and Jiang Zheng could feel that they were in a crisis. Even if they wanted to leave, they couldn’t since they were entangled here.

They blew the sound for help, but they discovered that Zhao Hai and Addison simply couldn’t hear them. This in turn wasted the efforts made by Addison’s men.

Laura and the others continued to survey the battle. They counted that there were hundreds of millions of undead under Addison’s command. Naturally, the levels of these undead were uneven. Some of them were at a silver rank and wouldn’t have any bone weapons to equip, only stones and sticks. And even if they had a weapon, such Undead simply couldn’t do any damage to Zhao Hai’s Undead.

Addison’s men who reached above silver rank only totaled to less than 200 million. This number wasn’t small in the Underworld. After all, Addison had more than 20 cities. And in conquering these cities, these Undead were able to improve their strength rapidly. But these 200 million Undead still had no chance to contend against the Space. This was because the Space had more than 1 billion advanced level Undead.

One side had the numerical advantage, commanding advantage, training advantage, and battle formation advantage. And on the other side, there was a state of disunity. If Addison’s men could still keep being undefeated, then that would be totally unreasonable.

However, there was a characteristic when it came to battles of the Undead, they weren’t afraid to die. Because of this, dealing with Addison’s men wasn’t as easy as dealing with a normal army.

Lizzy and Megan had completely calmed down from their previous anxiety. The two women commanded the undead like a changing tide and surrounded Addison’s men. The two watched as Addison’s troops became less and less.

At this time, Addison began to sense something. He discovered that several of the Vampire subordinates were being killed. However, it can be said that Addison had a tenacious will, his heart was like a stone and he remained unmoved. His consciousness was still locked on to Zhao Hai. He wasn’t too affected by the losses of his subordinates.

In fact, Addison’s discovery had some mistakes. These Vampires weren’t killed, but they were taken to the Space. Now that Zhao Hai’s army had taken the winning side, capturing Undead wouldn’t be a problem. Moreover, Lizzy and Megan could see that Zhao Hai was still able to hold on for a while, so they were impolite and swept all of Addison’s men. Those who they liked were directly thrown into the Space.

Chapter 1005: Dissolving the Contract

Green looked at the actions made by Lizzy and Megan, but he didn’t say anything. Although he was also worried for Zhao Hai, he can see that Zhao Hai wasn’t in grave danger right now. Moreover, Green could see that Lizzy and Megan’s commanding skills were very good. He knew that there was no need to worry, he felt relief as he thought of this.

Laura and the others didn’t say anything as well, they knew Lizzy and Megan were as worried as them. At this point, they looked at the Undead with pity as they were killed and turned into fiery souls.

Seeing that Addison’s men were getting fewer and fewer, Laura let out a sigh and said, “We’re almost done. Megan, you go direct the Undead to kill Addison’s remaining men. Lizzy, take the other Undead and head towards where Brother Hai is. Grandpa Green, what do we do next?”

Green looked at Laura and then smiled, “There’s no need to do anything else. Just have the Undead be in a battle formation as they go towards the Young Master. Have their spiritual force help Young Master’s momentum and put pressure on Addison.”

Laura nodded. Then she turned to look at Lizzy who nodded back. Lizzy immediately knew what to do as she took some undead and went according to Grandpa Green’s words. She called Guli and Jiang Zheng and had them lead the Undead to support Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai and Addison were still in a confrontation. Then at this time, Guli and Jiang Zheng lead a group of Undead and appeared behind Zhao Hai. The undead were in a cube formation. With about a hundred million undead, the cube blotted out the sky, giving great pressure to the surroundings.

Due to his senses, Zhao Hai was able to know that his Undead were coming. His aura couldn’t help but get stronger, it seems like it exponentially increased.

Since Zhao Hai and Addison were locked on to each other, Addison was naturally able to sense Zhao Hai’s increase in momentum. In the beginning, he didn’t understand why Zhao Hai’s aura became stronger. Then at this time, he finally saw Guli and Jiang Zheng’s group appearing behind Zhao Hai.

Upon seeing Guli and Jiang Zheng, Addison’s expression couldn’t help but change. His mind became shaken for a little moment. Using his spiritual force, Zhao Hai was able to discover Addison’s disturbance. Zhao Hai’s eyes turned fierce as his mind shouted ‘Kill’. Then he waved his sword and charged towards Addison.

Addison’s expression was incomparably ugly. He knew that he had lost, but he didn’t know if he would be able to escape under Zhao Hai’s assault.

Addison knew that he couldn’t retreat at this time. If he did, then his momentum would be weaker. And under Zhao Hai’s spiritual force, he would be heavily attacked. Who knows if he could be killed this time.

Zhao Hai didn’t actually think about a lot of things right now. His aura strengthened as he waved his curved sword and attacked Addison. This time, Addison was on his back foot. He can only parry, he didn’t have any opportunity to attack.

Zhao Hai’s curved sword danced faster and more vigorously, making Addison complain inside time and time again. He was clear that he was more unfortunate than lucky. Addison was also clear that he still had one move to use, but he preferred to not use it.

While Zhao Hai was going full on attack, he found that Addison’s sword wasn’t panicked nor chaotic. Addison defended quite well, making Zhao Hai unable to easily deal with him.

Zhao Hai was a learned man. Inside his head he immediately understood that Addison must have means to save his life, so he wasn’t panicking. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but pay more attention to Addison.

Addison didn’t know that his move was already discovered by Zhao Hai. He still resisted Zhao Hai’s attacks. The fighting between the two were very fast. Guli and Jiang Zheng could only see the whirlwinds of attacks, they couldn’t see anything else at all.

At this time, Zhao Hai’s eyes suddenly flashed. His sword changed, it wasn’t a quick slash, but instead it was slow. It felt like this sword strike was hiding myriad changes inside it.

When Addison saw this sword, his expression couldn’t help but greatly change. This was because he discovered that although Zhao Hai’s slash was very slow, it was hiding something inside it, blocking all of his escape routes. The only thing Addison could do was to wield his sword and block it.

When he thought about this, Addison’s eyes flashed a grim light. As Zhao Hai’s move approached, Addison’s cross sword fiercely slashed up and met with Zhao Hai’s curved sword.

However, Addison failed to see the sly glint on Zhao Hai’s eyes as he was concentrated on Zhao Hai’s sword. But when his own sword hit Zhao Hai’s, Zhao Hai’s sword suddenly broke apart. There wasn’t any resistance as the two weapons clashed. The feeling of using the wrong amount strength made Addison almost tumble forward.

But things haven’t ended. As Addison was startled, the originally curved sword became a whip. At the head of the new weapon was a small hammer. Addison’s sword block made the whip lash in, the small hammer on the tip going in to hit the Addison’s back.

Bang! Addison felt his body shake. He couldn’t stop himself from vomiting blood.

Then this time, Zhao Hai’s whip changed its shape into a tiger-tail whip. The whip went on to continually attack Addison. Upon seeing this offensive, a trace of panic finally appeared on Addison’s face. However, it was quickly replaced by fierceness. He looked at Zhao Hai with a vicious gaze and said, “Zhao Hai, I will repay today’s enmity a hundred times over. Blood Flash!” After he said that, an immeasurable amount of blood came out of his body, eventually turning into a giant rotating ball of blood. The rotation got faster and faster and at the same time, the ball became smaller and smaller. Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t wait and whipped the ball of blood. However, that ball of blood was like a ball of water, Zhao Hai couldn’t do anything to it. His attacks was akin to slashing a stream of water in order to stop its flow, it didn’t have any effect.

In front of Zhao Hai’s eyes, the ball of blood became smaller and smaller before it popped in and disappeared.

At this time, Guli and Jiang Zheng arrived at Zhao Hai’s side. Then Guli said, “Young Master, this is a unique technique of the Vampire Race, Blood Flash. Only Vampire Marquis or higher ranked beings can perform this. It allows them to jump a thousand li(500km), and it gets farther the stronger one is. However, a Blood Flash would have tremendous impact to their bodies. I don’t know how far Addison jumped, but recuperating within 8-10 years would be impossible for him.”

Jiang Zheng nodded and said, “It’s a pity he escaped.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t worry about it, he won’t be able to run for long. You take care of things here while I pursue him. Remember to send the remaining Undead to the Space, we shouldn’t waste any manpower.” The two complied as Zhao Hai just smiled. In fact, Zhao Hai didn’t say this to the two, but to Lizzy and Megan instead.

On a Bone Mountain a hundred thousand li(50,000 km) east of Three Saint City, a giant ball of blood suddenly appeared. Then the ball of blood transformed and slowly turned into a person. This person was none other than Addison who just waged a war against Zhao Hai.

This Bone Mountain was also a unique type of structure in the Underworld. Just like its name, bone mountains were huge piles of bones. Nobody knew how these Bone Mountains came to be. Bone Mountains can both be large and small, with some stretching for hundreds of thousands of li. This Bone Mountain was a small one, it can even be called a Bone Hill.

This was generally the birthplace for skeletons. Both strong and weak Skeletons came out from Bone Mountains. However, there weren’t any strong skeletons seen in these Bone Mountains. Once these Skeletons were born, they would immediately leave the vicinity. Only recently born Grey Skeletons could be seen in the area.

Addison chose to appear in this place. Since there weren’t any strong Skeletons in this area, Addison wouldn’t be threatened even if he was seriously injured.

Addison’s current state was very bad. His face was very blue and there was a line of blood coming out of his mouth. He was humiliated but his expression was extremely fierce. When his figure appeared, he vomited blood before he grumbled, “Zhao Hai, wait for me. When I recover, I will make you suffer a hundred times more than I did today.”

Then suddenly, a temperate voice was heard, “Why would I need to wait. I’m already here.”

The voice was very light. But in Addison’s ears, it was as loud as a thunderclap. Addison was too familiar with this voice, he used Blood Flash in order to escape from the owner of this voice.

Addison’s spiritual force swept towards the direction of the voice, to which he found Zhao Hai standing there. Addison’s face couldn’t help but turn grey. If he wasn’t injured, then he would’ve used Blood Flash straight away. But unfortunately, he was seriously injured. If he used Blood Flash once more, then his strength would be permanently damaged, he might even descend one rank. This wasn’t something that Addison wanted to see. So he stopped himself from escaping as he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “How did you get here? In this world, nobody can catch up to my Blood Flash”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “If you become my subordinate, then I will naturally tell you.”

Addison continued to look at Zhao Hai, but various thoughts were quickly running in his head. He couldn’t accept that Zhao Hai was his match. Earlier on, because of Guli and Jiang Zheng, Zhao Hai was able to crush him using his aura. Because of this, Addison lost. If there was no external help, then the fight would at most end in a draw. Pledging loyalty to Zhao Hai wasn’t something he was willing to do.

However, Addison was seriously injured and he could only use 20%-30% of his strength. If he fights Zhao Hai in his current state, then he would only be courting death. Moreover, he couldn’t escape. In this case, pledging allegiance to Zhao Hai was his only choice, he was unwilling to become food for others.

Also, after pledging loyalty to Zhao Hai, when he recovers, he can deal with Zhao Hai then. When the time comes, and Zhao Hai had his guard down, he was confident in making a successful sneak attack. After he eliminates Zhao Hai, he would then proceed to consume Zhao Hai’s fiery soul.

When he thought about this, Addison bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Addison is willing to pledge allegiance to Mister.”

Zhao Hai looked at Addison and a light couldn’t help but flash on his eyes. He knows that Addison wasn’t having any good thoughts. However, Zhao Hai didn’t expose him, he knew that whatever Addison’s plan was, he would never expect something like the Space. As long as Addison enters the Space, then even if he had a great plan, it would still be deemed useless.

Zhao Hai pretended to be happy as he said, “Good, since you’ve pledged your loyalty, then you’re now a person on my side. Since that’s the case, then let me tell you.I have a Space Divergent Ability. Because of this, I can make quick pursuits. Alright, let’s go back to Three Saint City, I’ll help you treat your wounds.

When Addison heard Zhao Hai, his heart couldn’t help but turn cold. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have a spatial ability. Since this is the case, then he would need to choose a good time to attack Zhao Hai in the future. Otherwise, Zhao Hai would be able to teleport away. Even if Addison wants to chase, he wouldn’t be able to.

On the surface, Addison kept being respectful, “Alright, then I would have to trouble Mister.”

Addison couldn’t understand why Zhao Hai haven’t signed a contract with him. But even if Zhao Hai did, Addison wasn’t afraid. In the past, Addison was able to learn a secret technique. This technique was able to slowly void a contract without alerting the other party. Because he had this guarantee, Addison was able to agree to pledging allegiance to Zhao Hai.

This method of dissolving contracts was created by a Lich. This Lich was quite special, he was even probably older than Kampala. This Lich wasn’t interested in getting stronger, opting to do research instead. But since this LIch had lived for too long, his strength became very formidable. Additionally, with his numerous research, he was able to make all kinds of magic. In the end, his strength was something that surprised even Addison.

Also, that Lich didn’t like to fight against people. And since some of his experiments needed some test subjects, he let Addison help him procure them. In turn, he promised that as long as Addison helps him, he would teach Addison a secret technique. Since that Lich was stronger than Addison, he could only comply. However, Addison didn’t expect the Lich to teach him a method to dissolve contracts. At that time, Addison was still weak, around Vampire Marquis level. Afterwards, Addison was contracted to a strong Vampire. During that time, Addison remembered the secret technique. With a mentality of refusing to abandon hope, Addison tried it out. Who would’ve thought that it was actually a success. After that, he found an opportunity to mount a sneak attack, killing that formidable Vampire. Because he had absorbed that Vampire’s energy, Addison was able to attain his current strength. Now, Addison wants to use the same method to deal with Zhao Hai.

Chapter 1006: About the Underworld

Zhao Hai was aware that Addison has his own thoughts. But since Addison wanted him to believe, then he would act that he believed. This way, Addison would put his guard down, finally ending up being cheated by Zhao Hai to enter the Space.

With their current strength disparity, Zhao Hai was completely able to throw Addison towards the Space. However, he was afraid that Addison might rebel at the last moment and blow himself up. If this happened, then Zhao Hai would lose a powerful subordinate. Because of this, Zhao Hai went through all these things in order to deceive Addison to enter the Space.

Zhao Hai looked at Addison and said, “Alright. Addison, stay by my side. I’ll take you to Three Saint City. Since you are injured, I will not sign a contract at the moment. We’ll have you recover first. We’ll sign the contract when you’re healed.”

Zhao Hai knew that if he kept silent about the contract, then Addison might begin to have some suspicions. He chose his words carefully so that Addison wouldn’t think about it.

Sure enough, after hearing Zhao Hai, the little bit of anxiety from Addison was cleared. He nodded before he went to Zhao Hai’s side. He looked very obedient.

Zhao Hai looked at Addison and smiled. Then he waved his hand as he brought Addison to the Space. After the Vampire King entered, the Space immediately issued a prompt, “Vampire discovered. Disloyalty has been detected, subduing, successfully subdued. Vampire is seriously injured. Does the Host want to treat him? Treatment would cost 1 million gold coins.”

Zhao Hai discovered that the Space had slowly gained a humanistic nature. In the past, the Space would just call skeletons robots, but now it could directly identify them as skeletons. Now, it was able to acknowledge the presence of a Vampire. It was clear that the Space was evolving.

Zhao Hai gave his agreement, “Immediately issue the treatment.”

The Space issued another prompt, “Administering treatment!’ After that, Zhao Hai’s gold became 1 million less. On the other hand, a film of blood wrapped around Addison and entered his body. It didn’t take long before Addison’s imposing aura recovered to what Zhao Hai felt before.

Addison quickly bowed to Zhai Hai and said, “Thank you, Young Master.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “Good. You go cultivate for now. I’ll find you later.” Addison complied as he was sent by Zhao Hai to the Hell Space.

At this time, Laura and the others walked out of the villa. Zhao Hai could also see Green and Merine among them.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare, then he immediately gave Green his greetings, “Grandpa Green, Grandma Merine, why are you here? Did something happen?”

Green smiled and said, “Young Master, Laura and the others came to look for me. They didn’t know what to do when you fought Addison, so they went to ask for my advice.”

Laura added, “That’s right. Brother Hai, it’s thanks to Grandpa Green. He advised us to quickly deal with the Undead attacking Three Saint City and then support you.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “If we could say anything about the old treasures of the Buda Clan, then Grandpa Green’s experience is certainly one of them. This time, our harvest is really good. I didn’t expect Addison to be this strong. But with this experience, if I meet another expert like Addison, I would surely be able to deal with them. Today’s event is really good. It’s lucky that you were able to release that skeleton. Otherwise, me and Addison would be in grave danger.”

Laura smiled and said, “You must thank Cai’er well. It was Cai’er who discovered that things weren’t doing well. Because of this, we released a skeleton to break your entanglement.”

Zhao Hai turned his head to Cai’er and faintly smiled, “Cai’er, thank you!’

Cai’er’s small face turned red as she replied, “Young Master is too polite. This is something that Cai’er should be doing.”

Zhao Hai smiled and didn’t give any more response. He turned to the others and said, “Alright, we shouldn’t be standing here outside. Let’s go in.” After that, the group proceeded to enter the villa.

After having sat down, Zhao Hai turned his head to Green and the others and said, “Since Grandpa Green is here, then we should discuss what to do next.”

Laura thought about it and said, “Brother Hai, the Underworld is very important for us. As long as we control this place, then this means that we would have an inexhaustible resource of manpower. I think we should fight here. Our next step would be taking control of the Resistance Army.”

Laura had already explained the Underworld’s matter to Green and Merine. Because of this, the two Elders already had a gist of the happenings in the plane.

Upon hearing Laura, Green nodded and said, “What Laura said is correct. The Underworld is important to us. I think it’s importance even surpasses the Divine Realm and the Ark Continent. If we ascend later on and face the powers of the Cultivation Realm, then the Underworld would be able to provide us with manpower. After all, we can get ores and other items anywhere else. But as for manpower, we can rarely get them.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “We should control the Underworld. But I don’t know if we should do it right now. We’ve already offended Lu Wei. If we ascend in the Ark Continent or the Divine Realm, then we would be chased by him. And this time, we still haven’t found out about the Atlanta Plane’s Ascension magic armor. If that magic armor is useless to us, then we can only ascend in the Underworld. So if we offend the manager of the Underworld, then we would be chased once we ascend. I don’t want to face that situation.”

The group nodded, but Merine knitted her brows as she said, “Young Master, I think you should snatch the Underworld first. In any case, you’ve already offended the people in the Underworld. Moreover, the Underworld is a giant dead landscape, this isn’t something we like to be in. When we ascend, we might as well ascend in the Divine Realm than in the Underworld. Even if we get chased by Lu Wei, the Young Master already fought with him several times, so you have some experience against him. Additionally, if you can’t run, there is still the Space. Also, the Young Master has Lu Wei’s remnant soul who knows about the Cultivation Realm’s situation. On the other hand, if we ascend in the Underworld, we would be going in blind. That case is much more dangerous. Therefore, I believe we should ascend in the Divine Realm or the Atlanta Plane. Ascending in the Underworld isn’t a good idea.”

When Zhao Hai heard Merine’s words, he couldn’t help but stare. He hadn’t thought about this issue. He thought at there wouldn’t be much difference in ascending in the Underworld. Upon hearing Merine, Zhao Hai’s eyes were finally opened. Only the Ark Continent and the Divine Realm belong to the same major plane. If Zhao Hai ascends in the Underworld, then the information that he had from Lu Wei’s remnant spirit would be utterly useless. And this wasn’t a good thing for Zhao Hai.

The faces of Laura and the others changed as well. It seems like old ginger was really more spicy. In terms of experience and wisdom, they couldn’t be compared to Green and Merine. The wisdom of old people were much more meticulous.

Laura nodded and said, “Right, it’s just like what Grandma Merine said. It seems like we should control the Underworld now. Being chased around by Lu Wei is much better than going to a completely unknown place.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright. Then we will take control of the Underworld. Let’s begin with the Resistance Army. Now that Addison is on our side, we can use him to absorb the Resistance Army. After that, we’ll deal with the Dark Temple.”

Green nodded, “That would work. But we still need to be on guard against the people in the Resistance Army. For them to hold on against the Dark Temple for this long means that they have their own methods. If we show our power too much, then it wouldn’t be impossible for those people to work with the Dark Temple to deal with us.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Right, I know what I should do. Grandpa Green, Grandma Merine, you go back first. I still have something to deal in the Underworld. I will certainly come back later to share a meal with you.” Green nodded with a smile.

After that, Zhao Hai’s figure flashed before he appeared back in Three Saint City. Then he called Addison out. At the same time, Guli and Jiang Zheng arrived and bowed to Zhao Hai, “We have seen the Young Master.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Let’s go inside the tower. I have some words to say.” The three nodded before following Zhao Hai into the tower.

After the group had sat down, Zhao Hai said, “I won’t care about Three Saint City’s matters in the future. Addison will take control. Addison, I want you to unify the Resistance Army as soon as possible. If you need my help, then tell me. Understood?”

Addison’s two eyes shone red before he stood up and bowed, “Young Master, you can rest assured, I will complete it successfully.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he continued, “Your people, I will release them after a while. But that doesn’t include the Lich. I have things for them to do. Guli and Jiang Zheng will cooperate with you. I don’t care too much about what happens in the Underworld, I’ll leave everything to you. But you need to be successful.”

Addison nodded, “Young Master can feel relieved, I know what to do. But Young Master, if I may ask, what do you want the Lich to do? Are the Lich important to the Young Master?”

Chapter 1007: Please Turn Me Into An Undead

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t expect Addison to take the initiative to ask this question. However, Zhao Hai could read through Addison’s question. His two eyes shone as he said, “Why do you ask? Do you know a formidable Lich?”

Addison nodded and said, “I do, Young Master. But I don’t know if he’s still there.” Then Addison told him about the Lich and the fact that the Lich taught him the method to dissolve contracts.

Zhao Hai stared, then he smiled faintly and said, “No wonder you easily agreed to pledge allegiance to me. So you have this intent. Good, good. Tell me about the technique to dissolve a contract.”

Addison didn’t hesitate as he quickly said, “Yes, Young Master.” Then he relayed the method to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai calmly listened as Addison told him about how to dissolve a contract. The method was truly wonderful, it could actually negate a contract. After listening to the technique, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh at the amount of talent needed to make it. It truly came from an extraordinarily talented person.

Zhao Hai wasn’t worried that Addison would use this technique. Betrayal was impossible. The method used by the Space was a completely different system to magic. Let alone this technique, even the heavens and the earth couldn’t affect the Space. This was because the Space wasn’t something that belonged to the heavens and the earth.

Addison remained standing there and didn’t make any noise. After some time, Zhao Hai let out a long breath and said, “Really wonderful. Hahaha. Good. Addison, can you visit that Lich? How about this, take care of the matters here first. Then you can lead me to look for that Lich. I need to recruit him under my wing.”

Addison nodded and said, “Young Master can rest assured, I know what to do.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he waved his hand, allowing Addison to leave. Then Zhao Hai stood up and looked at the Dark Mist outside the tower as he smiled, “I didn’t expect the Underworld to bring another pleasant surprise.” Then his figure flashed as he entered the Space.

Inside the Space, Meg and Merine were preparing their supper. Laura and the others were also helping them. Although their technique wasn’t good, their intention made up for it.

Green was inside the living room, happily looking at the battle between the O’Neal family and the Foreign Races. After seeing Zhao Hai come back, Green stood up and said, “Young Master, you’re back.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Grandpa Green, let’s sit and share a few cups. Later on, we’ll call Father-in-law and the others over. It has been some time since all of us gathered together.”

Naturally, Green didn’t have any complains. Zhao Hai quickly sent some Undead to call the others over. Those who were invited weren’t a lot, they were Rockhead, Blockhead, Karen, Shue, and Shun. These people were Zhao Hai’s closest family members. Because of this, Zhao Hai invited them over.

Before long, everyone was present. Then Zhao Hai and Green told them about the basic matters of the Underworld. Blockhead, Rockhead, Shue and Shun had regretful expressions on their faces. They wanted to follow Zhao Hai into dangerous places, it’s just a pity that their strengths couldn’t catch up. At this time, Green was still training them.

The meal was done preparing not long after that. Zhao Hai and the others proceeded to head towards the dining room. After everyone had sat down, Zhao Hai looked at them and smiled, “Everyone, it’s been a long time since we’ve gathered together. It’s not easy to have time like today.”

Green smiled and said, “Young Master, we made every effort to succeed, but we still couldn’t provide any means to help you.”

Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “It’s not that you couldn’t help, our enemies are just getting stronger and stronger. Alright, let’s not talk about this. Let’s eat. Nevertheless, I believe that we can defeat all of the enemies.”

At this time, Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, I have one thing I couldn’t understand. How did you find Addison? He used his Blood Flash and appeared more than 100 thousand li away. How did you manage to find him that quickly?”

Zhao Hai looked at Laura and gave her a smile, “Did you forget the weapon I used? It’s the Blood Ghost Staff. When I transformed my sword and turned it into a whip, I made a thin needle from the whip head and had it attach to Addison’s body. So even if I cannot see where he escaped to, I can still know his location. This way, I was able to quickly find him.”

This method was truly wonderful. But as long as people lift the mysterious veil, it becomes very unappealing, it looked so simple.

When the others heard Zhao Hai’s explanation, they couldn’t help but admire his thinking. This wasn’t some blind admiration, it stemmed from Zhao Hai’s true ability.

Don’t forget, Zhao Hai’s fight with Addison wasn’t something that would permit even a little bit of distraction. But yet, Zhao Hai was able to note Addison’s reaction and made that arrangement. It was something that needed some ability to execute.

Green nodded and said, “The Young Master has done magnificently. In the face of that kind of enemy, what one needs is calmness. At the same time, we can’t just have that enemy escape. If we allow them to escape, then they would certainly retaliate when they recover. We cannot let such a hostile enemy go free.”

Laura and the others nodded. Zhao Hai looked at everyone and then said, “Alright, let’s not talk about this. Actually, this is no big deal. Everyone, let’s eat.”

Green and the others didn’t express any disagreement and just began eating. After having eaten some food, Zhao Hai suddenly turned to Green and said, “Grandpa Green, how is Blockhead and the others’ training?”

As soon as they head Zhao Hai’s question, Rockhead, Blockhead, Shue, and Shun turned to look at Green. This was because the answer was also very important to them.

Green looked at Blockhead and the others and said, “Young Master, they still aren’t prepared. Although their strengths has been promoted to God-rank thanks to the Space, their combat experience is still very small. However, I’m prepared to send them to the Hell Space for practical training. As long as they are done with that, they would be able to work with the Young Master.”

As soon as they heard Green’s response, the expressions of Blockhead and the others went serious. They had never been on an actual war before, it can be said that their combat training was very minimal. Even Shue and Shun who were experienced in assassinations didn’t have the skill to kill the Undead.

Killing people and killing undead was totally different. If one wanted to kill a person, then slicing their necks or piercing their heart would be enough. On the other hand, these methods couldn’t be used on the Undead. The Undead didn’t have hearts nor necks that could be slit. Even Zombies like Jiang Zheng, even if they had necks, it wasn’t their fatal point. Slitting their throats would just be useless.

With these shortcomings, Shun was the one being affected the most. Shun was an assassin, a hidden weapon expert capable of assassinating people using many methods. But upon facing the undead, his hidden weapons were the most useless things. This was because his attacks wouldn’t be able to kill the undead. Therefore, this practical training was very necessary for Shun.

For Shun and the others, this practical training was good news. This was because this training represented them being a step closer to returning to work by Zhao Hai’s side. With this in mind, they were very eager to succeed.

When he heard Green’s explanation, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright. Have them get adapted to the combat suits first. If they can use the suits, then they wouldn’t die easily.”

At this time, Rockhead suddenly stood up and said, “Young Master, I have a request.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he turned to looked at Rockhead and said, “There’s no need to be overly polite. No matter what your request is, I will certainly try my best to comply.”

Rockhead looked into Zhao Hai’s eyes and said, “Young Master, I ask you, if I die in battle one day, then please turn me into an Undead. Let me keep following you at your side.”

Blockhead stood up as well and said, “Young Master, I’m thinking the same thing as Elder Brother. If I die in battle one day, then please turn me into an Undead.”

Shue and Shun similarly stood up and said the same words. Zhao Hai looked at the four, his face sunken as he said, “You four, why are you talking about dying? Do you really think that I lack manpower? Those Undead are more than enough to be my soldiers. Remember, later on, don’t speak of nonsense like this. You’re my family, so how could I just allow you to die in battle? Your mission is to survive and live alongside me.”

Green also turned to the four and said, “Alright, you guys go sit back down. Your Young Master has more than 1 billion Undead, and all of them have abilities no worse than you.”

As soon as they heard Green, Blockhead and the others sat down. They knew that Zhao Hai and Green only said those words because they cared for them, they couldn’t help but feel grateful.

After eating their meal, Green and the others proceeded to leave. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately head back to the Underworld. Instead, he sat inside the villa and looked at what Addison and the others were doing.

Addison and the others were currently taking care of Three Saint City. Actually, there was nothing left that much to deal with. Addison was currently calling his people and returning to the cities where they came from, stabilizing the overall situation.

Addison’s current actions were very clever. During this period of time, he took care of things swiftly and smoothly. He also left some hidden traps in his rear. Now, he can take advantage of this opportunity to remove the hidden dangers so that he can hand complete control of his force to Zhao Hai.

Most importantly, only when Addison stabilized these cities would he and Zhao Hai be able to look for that Lich.

Chapter 1008: Stable Rear Before Leaving

Almost nobody in the Underworld noticed the changes happening in Three Saint City. They were even less likely to know that the changes taking place in the city was something that would affect the entire Underworld.

Addison was now completely loyal to Zhao Hai. Not to say the method of dissolving contracts, even if that magic works, it was still useless. Addison was now intent on doing his best for Zhao Hai.

From what Addison could see, Zhao Hai had paid great attention to that Lich. It even seems like he attaches more importance to the Lich compared to Addison. Although Addison didn’t know why, he knew that this matter would be advantageous for Zhao Hai. In this case, he would need to deal with this matter as soon as possible.

However, taking care of this matter wasn’t easy. Before they can leave, then needed to take care of Three Saint City as well as the other cities that Addison took before.

Actually, in the Underworld, once a city was conquered, there would almost be no rebellion happening. This was because hierarchy was very strict here. This hierarchy was inscribed into the bones of the Undead. Lower-ranked undead wouldn’t dare to rebel.

However, this didn’t indicate that there wouldn’t be any danger in these cities. Because of this, Addison left some high-ranked subordinates inside the cities that he had conquered before. This was to insure the city’s stability.

Also, Addison has his own enemies. They wouldn’t just watch as Addison leaves. When Addison leaves, then it’s possible for his enemies to snatch his cities.

In the Underworld, experts like Addison didn’t only number one or two, there were quite a lot of them. Even if we only counted inside the Resistance Army, there were still several beings on Addison’s level. In fact, despite being strong, Addison wasn’t the strongest.

But although there were other strong characters, their influence wasn’t the same. Addison’s place in the Resistance Army was, in a word, hawkish. He was bent on unifying the Resistance Army and then proceeding to deal with the Dark Temple.

Naturally, opposite the hawks were the doves. These doves think that maintaining the present situation would be best. These two sides weren’t peaceful to each other. On the other hand, there was Kampala’s group, the free and unfettered faction.

The so-called free and unfettered faction were actually people who belong to the middle. They don’t belong to either faction, they just stayed neutral and guarded their territory. If people from the Dark Temple attack, only then would they go into war. Being people in the middle, there were no doves nor hawks among them, all they want was to protect their land.

In the Underworld, the Resistance Army controls over 100 cities. On the other hand, the Dark Temple held several thousand. If it wasn’t because of the strong beings inside the Resistance Army, then the Dark Temple would’ve already gotten control of the Underworld.

Addison was the representative of the hawk faction in the Resistance Army. Not to mention the opposition from the doves, even the other hawks would look covetously at his cities. Therefore, Addison’s camp was still somewhat unstable.

Addison wanted to stabilize his side so that Zhao Hai could rest assured. And the reason why Addison was confident in doing so was because he now had Zhao Hai’s support.

One shouldn’t underestimate the help that Zhao Hai can provide. How much military strength does Zhao Hai have? He had more then 1 billion high-ranked Undead. With this support at his back, Addison was completely able to stabilize his backyard.

Zhao Hai knew this so he didn’t interfere. He already told Addison that he would support him. Therefore, Addison having this confidence was nothing unusual.

Zhao Hai was fully confident of the Space’s abilities. Addison had been subdued by the Space, and since this was so, Addison wouldn’t betray him. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t hold back in sending Undead to Addison. There was no need for suspicion and doubt.

Addison had now left Three Saint City, leading Undead to the cities that had surrendered to him.

Addison’s methods were working very well. In the following month, Addison led his undead and reconquered the cities that he had conquered.

It might sound redundant, but it wasn’t redundant at all. Back then, Addison only conquered the strongest beings in those cities, the ordinary people haven’t been subdued. This time, Addison took the Undead army and swept through those cities. All of the Undead have been sent to the Space, becoming Zhao Hai’s subordinate.

Actually, Zhao Hai didn’t expect Addison to use this method. After Addison captured all of the Undead inside the cities, the Undead inside Zhao Hai’s Space had multiplied several times. This is to say that Zhao Hai now had several billion Undead inside his Space.

Naturally, these billions of Undead weren’t all inside the Space, some of them were replaced back into the Underworld. But this time, they were loyal to Zhao Hai. By having these Undead, this meant that Addison’s cities were nigh impregnable.

If other Undead arrived at the cities at this time, then they would find a very strange phenomenon. The Undead inside these cities weren’t as bustling as the others, the city was like a well-oiled machine.

The Undead inside these cities would go out and find things that they see as valuable. Then they would hand them over to the city manager and in turn they would be given rewards.

It was impossible for the other Undead to know that this was Zhao Hai’s idea. After seeing Addison’s actions, Zhao Hai decided to copy the system inside the Space and implement it on these Undead cities.

It took about a month before these cities have been processed. In this month’s time, the battle between the O’Neal family and the Foreign Races has ended. Who won and who lost was still unclear. If talking about casualties, then the O’Neal family won, the ratio of casualties between the two parties was an astonishing 10,000 to 1 in favor of the O’Neal family. However, this didn’t mean that the O’Neal family was victorious. One should know that training magic armor pilots in the Atlanta Plane wasn’t an easy matter. They took a lot more resources compared to a similarly ranked warriors.

Because of this, although the O’Neal family had repelled the Foreign Races, their ability to expand has been hindered. At this moment, they can only defend the Taurus Continent as well as seize the planes belonging the the Thunder Clan, Barbarians, and the Winged Pegasus.

Although this was the case, the O’Neal family didn’t term it as a loss. They wanted the resources of the Taurus Continent, and they managed to get it, albeit after paying a high price.

However, there was a particular phenomenon in the Atlanta Plane. If you have money, then you will not lack people working for you, you can even buy people.

Actually, the Atlanta Plane had once abolished slavery, nobody could buy nor sell people. However, this rule became useless when opening other planes became prevalent.

In the end, the Atlanta Plane could only amend the law. The people from the Atlanta Plane were allowed to buy and sell people, but those people needed to be from other planes. Humans from the Atlanta Plane couldn’t be sold. If one was found violating this law, then they would be severely punished.

This amendment was akin to the Atlanta Plane agreeing to the existence of slavery. This was because the people from the Atlanta Plane didn’t look any different compared to the people from the other planes. One would just need to label a person as someone from another plane and they could be bought or sold.

This condition has been placed in the dark by the higher people from the Atlanta Plane. Because of this, the masses were celebrating that their lords were being magnanimous when in fact they were doing dishonest matters in the dark.

Because of this, the O’Neal family wasn’t worried that nobody would come to the Taurus Continent and act as their labor force. In fact, the ores they gained in the Taurus Continent was enough to buy people and train a lot of magic armor pilots. The only other thing they needed was time.

Since the O’Neal family had no way to attack the Foreign Races and the Foreign Races had no way to attack the O’Neal family, the Taurus Continent had unexpectedly become peaceful.

However, this wasn’t the thing that Zhao Hai wanted to happen. This was because Zhao Hai wanted to see a higher level magic armor from the O’Neal family. The O’Neal family had yet to invest greatly in this war.

Instead of the fight, Zhao Hai’s attention was placed on the O’Neal family’s Patriarch. And through this, Zhao Hai can affirm that the O’Neal family had a more powerful magic armor than their God-rank magic armors. However, it was the same as the Supreme Weapons, they couldn’t be easily used.

The battle with the Foreign Races was beyond the O’Neal family’s expectations. Because of this, they didn’t bring the more powerful magic armor into the Taurus Continent. After experiencing the fierce battle, the magic armor had began its transport. But since it took time to transport this magic armor, and since the fight was in a standoff for a long time, the two sides retreated even before the magic armor arrived.

Because this magic armor didn’t arrive, Zhao Hai had no way to see how it performs in a fight. However, Zhao Hai wasn’t too anxious about this matter. This was because Zhao hai knew that the Foreign Races wouldn’t just let the O’Neal family freely take the Taurus Continent. And at the same time, the O’Neal family wouldn’t just accept having a hidden enemy at all times. A war would happen sooner or later. When that time comes, the O’Neal family would surely use that magic armor, and Zhao Hai would be able to see its might.

Zhao Hai also heard why the O’Neal family couldn’t freely use that magic armor. It was because of its energy consumption. If the magic armor wants to exert its strength, then it would need a strong energy source. Ordinary energy converters might be fine but they wouldn’t be enough. Not only could ordinary energy converters restrict the performance of the magic armor, it could also dramatically shorten the time it can be used.

Take an ordinary magic armor, for example. If it uses an energy converter, then it can remain operational for six hours. If it was in an intense fight, then it can function for four hours. As for that magic armor, an ordinary energy converter would only be enough for it to normally function for one hour. But if it was going to enter a battle, then it would need a special energy block. This energy block was something that was rare even in the Atlanta Plane.

This piece of information stoked Zhao Hai’s interest. He wanted to see that energy block that the O’Neal family Patriarch was talking about.

Peace has been restored in the Divine Realm. This made Zhao Hai turn his full attention to the matters of the Underworld. At this time, Addison’s 20 cities had become under his control. All of the Undead in those cities had been converted. As long as it keeps going smoothly, then Zhao Hai would be able to look for that Lich alongside Addison.

Zhao Hai was full of curiosity towards that Lich. He wanted to know the character of such a being. However, Zhao Hai wasn’t in a hurry, he knew that being anxious would just be useless.

Zhao Hai had already asked Addison about the position of that Lich. Addison said that the Lich was in a very secret place. It would be impossible for ordinary undead to reach that place. Since the place was not dangerous to the Lich, he theoretically wouldn’t leave.

After getting a guarantee from Addison, Zhao Hai relaxed. They needed to unify the Resistance Army and cultivate a stable base. Because of this, it was important for Zhao Hai to stabilize the places that Addison conquered first.

After a month and ten days, Addison finally took care of the cities under his rule. Each city had one or two beings as powerful as Guli and Jiang Zheng managing it. The rest of the Undead were Zhao Hai’s men. With this, the cities wouldn’t be in any danger.

And because of the Space, those cities would support each other all the time. Once a city experiences a problem, then the other cities would immediately offer reinforcements.

After everything has been taken care of, Zhao Hai and Addison left the territory to find that formidable Lich!

Chapter 1009: High-rank Bone-shaped Plants

Zhao Hai calmly sat inside Guli’s bone carriage. Outside the carriage, one could see that the ones pulling it weren’t ordinary human-shaped skeletons. Instead, it was lifted by four giant bone beasts as they flew in the sky. These four bone beasts had roughly the same bone structure as a human. However, they had four strong limbs as well as long and sharp fangs. One could see from this that the beasts were four giant apes.

Inside the carriage were several bone furniture covered by some beastskin. On a table were two glasses filled with red wine. Addison was sitting opposite Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai looked at Addison and smiled, “Addison, you need to learn how to indulge. Taste this, it’s the best red wine the Space can produce.”

Because Addison had more contact with Zhao Hai, he wasn’t as polite and respectful compared to before. He was now acting more comfortably in front of Zhao Hai. Naturally, his loyalty to Zhao Hai remained unchanged, he just held back his reverence.

After all, Addison was a king, and he was also an intelligent being. Although he has been subdued by the Space, his memories weren’t altered, the only thing that changed was the fact that he was now loyal to Zhao Hai.

Addison took up a glass of red wine and took a sip. After he placed his glass back down, he smiled and said, “It’s pretty good, very tasty. In the Underworld, we could only drink the blood from the Blood Ponds or blood of magic beasts. Those things simply have no flavor.”

Zhao Hai looked at Addison and said, “Don’t Vampires rely on drinking blood to live? Do you have any other choice?”

Addison smiled and said, “Young Master, we Vampires are actually a type of Undead. During our early lives, we are weak Vampire Bats. At that time, we can only survive by drinking on Blood Ponds. After drinking enough blood from the Blood pond, we slowly transition into becoming Undead. Although blood can provide us with energy, after becoming Vampires, we can survive by directly absorbing the Dark Mist. Only when we are injured or just want to drink blood do we drink it.”

Zhao Hai nodded. It seems like the Vampires in the Underworld were different than the ones on Earth. This also made it known to Zhao Hai that this place was disconnected from Earth. After all, Vampires on Earth only exist in legend, in people’s fantasy. But in this universe, one was sitting right opposite him.

This time, the two came out in order to find the Lich that Addision mentioned. The two didn’t bring anybody else. Naturally, Zhao Hai was still able to bring his army out. After all, there was the Space.

Addison looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Moreover, in my current level, I don’t need blood anymore. As long as I absorb the Dark Mist, I can have endless strength.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Good, the Underworld’s Dark Mist is truly mysterious. Right, how far are we from reaching the next city?”

Addison’s spiritual force swept out before he said, “It’s not far away. In half a day, we should reach Dry Bone City.”

Zhao Hai had a curious expression as he asked, “Addison, how does the Underworld tell the time? Also, how do you distinguish between night and day?”

Addison smiled and said, “Young Master, there are many methods in the Underworld, and each one of them is different. Time has no use to the Undead, so nobody really takes note of the time. But as for day and night, we can see it from the concentration of the Dark MIst. When the density of the mist is strong, then it’s night, if it is thin, then it’s day.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He knew that the Undead would be the most sensitive to the changes to the Dark Mist. Since the Dark Mist was everywhere, using this method to tell the time was quite convenient.

Zhao Hai also swept the outside with his spiritual force, then he sighed, “I didn’t expect plants to be able to survive in the Underworld. Also, those plants look very strange. This is my first time seeing plants growing to look like bones.”

In the past several days, Zhao Hai had gained some understanding regarding the strange things in the Underworld. There were plenty of plants here, and all of them look very foreign to Zhao Hai. Some of these plants were pitch black. Although they had leaves growing, these leaves were also black. It wasn’t a very dark shade of green, but completely black. There were also some plants that were pure red, and also some that were completely blood red.

But one of the strangest plants that Zhao Hai saw were these bone plants. The trunk of the plant was a huge bone with its branches being thinner versions. Its leaves were made out of bones as well. In short, the plant looked like a piece of art made purely out of bones stuck together. It didn’t resemble anything that can be called alive.

When Zhao Hai saw these plants, his first thought was that they were fake. But afterwards he discovered that they weren’t. This plant had roots. And when they were sent to the Space, the Space issued a prompt. According to the Space, this plant was a type of High-ranked fauna. It seems like these plants would have great use in the future. This was because the Space only identified it as high-rank, nothing else. This meant that the Space’s level was not enough to describe the properties of the plant.

Upon hearing the Space’s prompt, Zhao Hai immediately knew that these bone plants were great items. And being low-level was a sign of a good thing, this was what Zhao Hai learned after having the Space this long.

What made Zhao Hai more surprised was the fact that this plant could only survive on Bone Mountains. If you change its location, then it wouldn’t grow.

Zhao Hai had no choice but to go outside and take that Bone Mountain into the Space. But Zhao Hai didn’t expect that upon taking that Bone Mountain into the Space, the Space issued a prompt. It said that the Bone Mountain had improved the Hell Space. Not only that, it actually increased the Space’s level by one. At the same time, it was stated that the Bone Mountain could grow up. Once it becomes big enough, then it would automatically produce skeletons on its own. This was definitely an unexpected surprise for Zhao Hai.

Zhao Haid didn’t think that the Space would have a function. He immediately took a bigger Bone Mountain to the Space. However, this time, the Space didn’t issue any prompt, the Bone Mountain didn’t produce any skeletons either. In the end, Zhao Hai could only give up. Now he was wondering what other things he can see in the Underworld.

When Addison heard Zhao Hai’s comments, he smiled and said, “There are a lot of strange things in the Underworld. In fact, there aren’t a lot of bone plants existing here. This is because the Undead would immediately eat them since it can increase their level.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he really didn’t know what uses these plants had. But Zhao Hai still had the Undead stroll around the cities and collect any strange things they come across.

Addison looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, although there aren’t a lot of plants in the Underworld, each one of them are very useful. And even if Dark Creatures generally eat plants, they can swallow fiery souls as well. At the same time, they could survive by consuming the blood in Blood Ponds. It was for this reason that their bodies produce spirit stones.”

Zhao Hai nodded. After a long period of evolution, it wouldn’t be unreasonable for the Dark Creatures to find ways in order to survive. They had no eyes, they can drink from poisonous Blood Pounds, and they can even absorb fiery souls. It was obvious that these were all for survival. After all, fiery souls and blood ponds were the most common things in the Underworld.

Just like Addison said, there weren’t a lot of plants in the Underworld. Zhao Hai believes that this was because of the Underworld being devoid of life. Even these mutant plants found it difficult to survive.

While the two men were chatting, Zhao Hai could suddenly feel the presence of a city in front of them. Addison discovered it as well. After using his spiritual force, Addison turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, Dry Bone City is in front of us. It’s a city that is very important for the Undead. Do you want to go there to rest?”

Actually, with their strengths, they don’t need to take a rest. However, Zhao Hai wanted to take a look at Dry Bone City so he nodded and said, “Alright, let’s take some rest. I also want to see how different Dry Bone City is compared to Three Saint City.”

Addison smiled and said, “It is definitely different. Dry Bone City is quite an important city for the Rebel Alliance. Three Saint City isn’t as significant. Three Saint City is a place constructed by Kampala and the others, so its location is quite remote. On the other hand, Dry Bone City has connections to the Resistance Army and the Dark Temple. Because of this, the city is quite large. At the same time, since there are a lot of undead doing transactions here, hotels are built. They’re quite rare in the underworld.”

When he heard Addison, Zhao Hai said, “The Underworld has hotels? This is the first time I’ve heard of this. Interesting. We need to take a look inside the city and see if there are good things inside.”

Addison smiled and said, “You can bump into something good once in a while, but the probability of that happening is very low. After all, there aren’t a lot of good things in the barren Underworld.” While he said that, the bone carriage proceeded towards Dry Bone City.

Chapter 1010: Merchant Lich City Lord

Dry Bone City was structurally similar to Three Saint City. However, its city wall was much higher in comparison. Its gate was bigger as well. Just like Three Saint City, Dry Bone City only had a main gate, there were no other gates present. At the same time, carriages were rarely seen entering and leaving the gate. There simply wasn’t that much carriages in the Underworld.

In a city like this, although there were a lot of Undead going through the city gates, no entry tax was collected. The trade in the city was much more open than other groups. The Undead system didn’t have things such as tax collection.

Zhao Hai and Addison rode their bone carriage to enter the city. The guards on the city gate couldn’t help but look at the bone carriage. It was clear that they don’t often see high-ranked people entering Dry Bone City.

In the Underworld, as long as an Undead goes to a city and makes a transaction, then it meant that they held intellect. In other words, these Undead were like people, they can think for themselves and trade like a human would. It was just because of their living environment that their cultures were very different.

Zhao Hai and Addison proceeded to enter Dry Bone City. It was clear that Addison had some understanding regarding the city. Upon entering, Addison immediately led Zhao Hai to a building. Zhao Hai inspected the building, it was made by flat stone while the floor was blood red soil. Zhao Hai knew that this soil must be made out of clay found near Blood Ponds, its blood energy was actually quite strong.

But what made it surprising for Zhao Hai was the fact that the roof of the Underworld’s houses were made out of bones. The Undead of the Underworld seem to have become skilled when it came to using bones. When Zhao Hai saw this for the first time, he couldn’t help but be astonished since these roof didn’t leak at all.

Zhao Hai and Addison entered the hotel. When they entered, Zhao Hai saw that the furniture were all made out of bones. Also, Zhao Hai was surprised to see that there were Lich among the Skeletons that were working here.

As soon as they entered the hotel, a Lich immediately floated over. The Lich bowed and said, “Welcome to Dry Bone Hotel.”

Addison looked at the Lich, then he tossed a spirit stone and said, “Prepare the best rooms.” The Lich looked at the spirit stone on his hand, his two eyes couldn’t help but turn bright as he immediately said, “Alright, please come with me.” Then he fluttered towards the hotel.

Although the hotel looked very ordinary, its interior was actually very wide. After the Lich lead Zhao hai and Addison to their room, he proceeded to turn around and left.

Zhao Hai entered the room and inspected it. It was an ordinary suite with three rooms, one living room and one bathroom. However, what surprised Zhao Hai was the small blood pond in the bathroom.

Inside the living room was a chair made with bones. The chair was actually quite good, it was covered in beastskin making it comfortable to sit on.

After Zhao Hai had sat down, Addison said, “Young Master, I’m afraid we wouldn’t be able to rest for long. Now that we’ve arrived, the City Lord of Dry Bone City will surely come to visit.”

Zhao Hai replied, “You know the City Lord?”

Addison smiled and said, “I realized I haven’t talked about it but I’ve been in Dry Bone City two times. There are five City Lords here, three of them are Lich while the other two are beings with the same strength as Guli. The most common people in this city are Lich and Skeletons. The last time I came here, I bought a lot of high-level fiery souls from one City Lord.”

Zhao Hai looked at Addison and said, “Do they sell a lot of  high-level fiery souls here?”

Addison nodded and said, “They do. Since this is an important location, they store a lot of those things here. Naturally, they don’t have very high-level fiery souls. However, if you want up to Gold Skeleton level, then you won’t have problems finding them here. Both us and the Dark Temple need massive amounts of high-level fiery souls in order to enhance the strength of our subordinates.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he didn’t expect this city to have this huge business. Interesting, it seems like these people were war merchants.

While Zhao Hai was thinking, a sound was suddenly heard outside, “Is Mister Addison here? This is Yuri, I’d like to seek an audience with Mister Addison.”

Zhao Hai turned his head to look at Addison. Addison smiled faintly and said, “It’s the City Lord of Dry Bone City. The boss of this hotel is his subordinate.” Zhao Hai nodded and waved his hand.

Addison immediately said, “City Lord Yuri, please come in.”

Just as his voice fell, a person from outside floated over, this person was a Lich. From what Zhao Hai can see, this Lich’s strength was worse than Kampala, but not by a lot.

When the Lich came in and saw Zhao Hai sitting there, he couldn’t help but stay still, then his eyes flashed a quick glimmer. Earlier, the Lich didn’t dare to use his spiritual force to scan the room lest he make Addison think that he was hostile. This was a rule in the Underworld. If you wanted someone to be a friend and not an enemy, then you best not use your spiritual force to scan their dwelling, or it will certainly cause some conflict.

Although the Lich gawked, he managed to recover immediately. Then he bowed to Addison and Zhao Hai and said, “Yuri has seen Mister Addison and Mister. Might I know who Mister is?”

Zhao Hai stood up and returned the courtesy as he answered ,”I’m Mister Addison’s friend. I have seen city Lord Yuri.”

Yuri quickly made another bow before Addison asked him to sit down. Actually, this was just a formality since Yuri was always floating, there was no need for him to sit down at all. Yuri just floated on top of a chair as the group sat down. After that, Yuri immediately turned to Addison and said, “Can I know why Mister Addison came by this place? If you need anything, then please don’t hesitate to tell me.”

Addison smiled and said, “We don’t have anything to trouble the City lord at this time. Me and my friend are just passing by. This friend of mine hasn’t visited the Alliance before, so I took him here to see.”

When Yuri heard Addison, he couldn’t help but give a strange look towards Zhao Hai. Although Yuri wasn’t as strong as Addison, he could see that Zhao Hai’s strength wasn’t worse than Addison. Naturally, from the appearance of Zhao Hai, Yuri was able to know that he was a Dark Pharoah.

Yuri didn’t expect an expert on a level like Zhao Hai to have never visited the Alliance before. Where did he come from? Did he practice by himself all this time in order to gain his strength? It’s too inconceivable.

Addison looked at Yuri and knew what the Lich was thinking. However, Addison didn’t bother to explain, too much words would just make things worse. Also, with Addison’s status, there was no need to explain to someone like Yuri. Addison just looked at Yuri and smiled, “Since City Lord Yuri is here, what good things have you got recently? Although we’re only passing by this time, my friend actually wants to collect weird things. Does City Lord have things that can catch his interest?”

When Yuri heard Addison, his eyes lit up. Zhao Hai was startled by Yuri’s performance. He always thought that the Lich were like Kampala who liked to do research. However, Yuri was actually acting like a merchant. This wasn’t what Zhao Hai expected.

Yuri quickly turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister came at the right time. The City had just gained a lot of good items. Does Mister want to take a look?”

Zhao Hai stared at what Yuri told him, then he said, “Really? That’s good. When can I take a look?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Yuri knew that Zhao Hai was a type of crazed collector. This wasn’t the first time that Yuri had seen this type of person. In fact, a lot of high-ranked Undead in the Underworld had some sort of collection of their own. It wasn’t a strange thing.

Yuri immediately said, “At any time. Mister can see them whenever you want.”

At this time, Addison opened his mouth and said, “Then we’ll go see it now. City Lord Yuri, we still have things to do, so we can’t stay here for long.”

Naturally, Yuri was happy, so he immediately nodded and said, “Good, then come follow me.” After he said that, he turned around and fluttered out with Zhao Hai and Addison following behind him.

Yuri didn’t come with his own carriage, therefore Addison invited him to ride inside the bone carriage. Of course, Zhao Hai didn’t take his red wine out. It was impossible for the Underworld to produce red wine. If Zhao Hai revealed that he had red wine, then it would only stir up suspicions from Yuri.

There was no custom of asking people to drink in the Underworld. If one wants to offer their hospitality, then one would offer some fiery souls instead. But few people would actually use this, especially with high-ranked people like Addison.

Zhao Hai experienced the merchant skills of City Lord Yuri when he got on the bone carriage, it didn’t take long before the Lich let out a dizzying barrage of complements.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t look down on Yuri because of this. Instead, Zhao Hai was more interested in the Lich. Yuri’s versatility and speech was definitely a mark of a great merchant.

Addison didn’t know what Zhao Hai thought, but he looked down on Yuri. After all, Addison wasn’t a businessman nor did he want to be. With his status, it was natural for him to look down on Yuri.

Experts like Addison looked down on people like Yuri because, to them, strength was everything. Slick people like Yuri weren’t people that they can see eye to eye.

Chapter 1011: Huge Skull and Small Beast Skeleton

Different living conditions affect how a person looks at things. Zhao Hai came from Earth, and on Earth, businessmen were quite good. Moreover, a good businessman was very well respected.

Not to mention Earth, even those Nobles from the Ark Continent who traded could be said to be merchants. And similarly, great merchants from the Ark Continent were also well respected.

However, Zhao Hai was currently in the Underworld. In this place, the people only believe in strength, other things were superficial. Because of this, merchants like Yuri were part of the group who weren’t respected. Although Yuri was quite strong, to Addison’s eyes, if Yuri used the time he used for business to cultivate instead, then Yuri would have been much stronger.

The group quickly arrived at a tower inside the city. Zhao Hai also discovered that almost every city in the Underworld would have these towers. Naturally, all of these towers were occupied by City Lord characters.

The group exited the carriage and entered Yuri’s tower. Upon entering, Zhao Hai could feel the interior of the tower. Its layout was not much different compared to Kampala’s tower, however it can be seen that Yuri’s decorations were much better compared to Kampala.

Naturally, almost all of the decorations inside the tower were made out of bones. There were bones of all kinds here, it would make one feel like they were walking inside a demonic altar.

Even so, Zhao Hai knew that bones were essential items in the Underworld. In the minds of the residents of the Underworld, bones were things that could be used on all things, much like how people from other planes look at wood.

Yuri swiftly led the two towards a room inside the tower. Upon entering this room, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. It was actually a warehouse full of items.

Zhao Hai looked at the items inside. The things stored here range from a special looking bone to a huge skull that was taller than a person. It seems like everything was here.

Zhao Hai shifted his gaze to the other parts of the room including that huge skull. However, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately state what he wanted, instead he turned to Yuri and said, “Is this everything?”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Yuri quickly replied, “Of course not. This is only one my warehouses, there are plenty of others like this. If Mister is unsatisfied, then we can go to another place.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Let’s take a look at the others. Let’s hope that I can find something that can satisfy me.”

Yuri also brought Zhao Hai to another room. However, this room wasn’t any different, making Zhao Hai somewhat disappointed. But Yuri still had plenty of rooms, so Zhao Hai decided to take a look at them.

On the eighth room, Zhao Hai suddenly turned his gaze toward the skeleton of a small beast. It seems like it’s from a tiger but it actually had a single horn. The aura of the skeleton was quite strange, it seemed lifelike. When Zhao Hai saw this skeleton, his eyes couldn’t help but shine. Although he didn’t know what use this small skeleton had, Zhao Hai could feel that this small beast wasn’t simple.

After Yuri saw that Zhao Hai was paying attention to the small beast skeleton, he couldn’t help but stare. This was because he managed to obtain this skeleton a very long time ago. However, since the people from the Underworld rarely had any artistic taste, this small beast skeleton was never sold. Yuri wasn’t optimistic about this thing. He just thought that it was a dark beast that lived a little longer. And as an undead, Yuri didn’t care. Yuri just casually stored this skeleton in this warehouse. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be interested in it.

Zhao Hai gently lifted the skeleton and looked at it. This skeleton was made of bones yet it was heavier than one, Zhao Hai felt like he was lifting a skeleton made out of metal. Zhao Hai looked at it for some time before putting it down, then he looked at Yuri and said, “City Lord Yuri, I’ll have to politely ask you to lead me to your other warehouses. Afterwards, as long as I want something, then I will list them out. Naturally, you need to give me a fair price. To tell you the truth, I already had some items that I want from your collection.”

When Yuri heard Zhao Hai, his eyes shone, then he replied, “Alright, Mister Zhao Hai can rest assured, this Yuri is very fair in doing business. If people buy expensive items from me, then I would even give them a  ten percent discount.”

Upon hearing Yuri’s words, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. He discovered that no matter where, a merchant’s essence was the same. Discounts would certainly appear anywhere.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect that Yuri would have so many warehouses, up to 15. After exploring these warehouses, Zhao Hai immediately gave Yuri a list.

There were a lot of items that Zhao Hai wanted from these 15 warehouses, numbering at about 2000. It was almost a fifth of Yuri’s overall collection.

Yuri was extremely excited, he didn’t think that he would be able to do a huge transaction today. This was probably the biggest trade that he’s done in his life.

Zhao Hai used low-level fiery souls and low-grade spirit stones in order to exchange for these goods. One shouldn’t think that Yuri would oppose it, on the contrary, this was the best outcome for Yuri. This was because these low-ranked items would make him earn more money.

Although low-level fiery souls and low-grade spirit stones were the most common currency in the Underworld, this also meant that they were the most in-demand, their value was irreplaceable. For Yuri, he would use his status in Dry Bone City to sell some goods to people like Zhao Hai in exchange for these low-ranked fiery souls and low-grade spirit stones. Then he would use these to buy even more goods to sell. Yuri wouldn’t do anything and just earn the mark-up he placed on the items.

On the other hand, the reason why Zhao Hai paid using low-ranked fiery souls and spirit stones was because these two things can now be made inside the Space.

The first time that Zhao Hai brought fiery souls and spirit stones to the Space, the Space identified them as sources of energy. The Space could extract their energy and shape them according to what Zhao Hai wants. This meant that Zhao Hai could turn low-ranked fiery souls and spirit stones into high-ranked ones, and vice-versa.

Upon hearing this prompt, Zhao Hai knew that he wouldn’t be short on money in the Underworld. As long as he wanted something, then he could immediately buy it.

For these 2000 items, Zhao Hai paid Yuri 200 thousand fiery souls and spirit stones. While Yuri was celebrating the transaction, Zhao Hai took the 2000 items to the Space.

When Zhao Hai received the items into the Space, Yuri couldn’t help but look at him with envy. There weren’t a lot of spatial items in the Underworld, only those with special status would have them. Although Yuri’s status wasn’t low, even he didn’t have spatial equipment. Because of this, he could only look at Zhao Hai with envy.

Zhao Hai began to pay attention the moment he received the items into the Space. Aside from the unique plants in the Underworld, there were two things that held his interest. One of them were huge bones, the same as the skull that Zhao Hai saw in the first warehouse. The prompt the Space gave for these bones made Zhao Hai stare. The Space said that Zhao Hai’s level was too low to examine them. Zhao Hai didn’t think that the bones would be advanced level items. Zhao Hai knew at this time that he would need to be more mindful towards these kinds of bones in the future.

The second thing was none other than the small beast skeleton. When Zhao Hai placed it into the Space, he immediately heard a prompt, “Darkness-element beast skeleton armor for Undead use detected. This full body armor can strengthen the abilities of the Undead and Dark Creatures. Any Dark Creature and Undead can use it. Armor can be planted. After being planted, the seed can be purchased on the Space’s store. This armor can only be planted on black soil. Asking host for permission to plant the armor. If Host agrees, 100 thousand gold coins will be deducted.”

When Zhao Hai heard this prompt, his mind couldn’t help but pause. He didn’t expect this beast skeleton to actually be a full-body armor. In other words, this armor was something similar to the Twelve Constellation combat suits, but instead they could be used by the Undead. For Zhao Hai, this was exceptionally good news.

.However, Zhao Hai didn’t show his glee, his face was still calm. After the trade has been completed, Zhao Hai looked at Yuri and said, “City Lord Yuri, I didn’t think that you would have this much items, they’re very good. I’m very satisfied with this exchange. City Lord Yuri, can I ask you for a favor?”

Yuri was very satisfied as well. After all, he gained a very healthy profit. When he heard Zhao Hai, Yuri immediately said, “Mister, please say it. For such a valuable client like you, I will certainly try my best to help.”

Zhao Hai replied, “I like plants in the Underworld. As long as you have them, I’ll buy it. Also, I’m interested in things like the giant skull and small skeleton from before. You should be aware that I’m a Dark Pharaoh. We Dark Pharoah have particular taste for art like that small skeleton. Because of this, I’d want more things like that skeleton. I’d want things related to that giant skull as well. I want to see whether I would be able to make a full body out of it. Think about it, if I can assemble a few servants made out of those skeletons, wouldn’t I look more imposing?”

Yuri stared after hearing ZHao Hai’s words, he was truly shocked. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have such a request. To be honest, this request wasn’t too difficult for Yuri. Although plants were rarely found in the Underworld, Dry Bone City was an important commercial hub, it wouldn’t be difficult to get plants inside the city.

And as for the huge skull, it wasn’t something special as well. In fact, there were a lot of people who had the same thoughts as Zhao Hai. However, none of them succeeded. The huge skull seemed to be truly dead, one couldn’t even place a fiery soul inside it. Because of this, the skull was left to be a decoration, nothing else.

On the other hand, Yuri hasn’t seen that small beast skeleton before, and he only had one in his collection. Also, he hadn’t heard of anybody else having the same skeleton. It can be said that among the things Zhao Hai requested, this small beast skeleton would be the most difficult one.

However, this still wasn’t a problem for Yuri. He was  a qualified merchant and if there’s profit, he would find a way. So upon hearing Zhao Hai, Yuri immediately said, “Alright, Mister can rest assured, I will surely fulfil your request. But Mister must know that things like plants don’t last for long. If Mister doesn’t come here to pick them up, then they will die.”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and said, “Then I’ll come here once a month. As long as you collect the things I want, then I will buy them all. However, I have one thing to remind you. I don’t have problems when it comes to the plants and that giant skull, you could see which ones are real or fake. But as for that small beast skeleton, not only was it beautifully crafted, it is quite heavy as well. Most importantly, it seems like the small beast isn’t from the Underworld. When City Lord Yuri collects those skeletons, be sure to pay attention to its shape. I don’t care what shape it came in, but make sure that its craftsmanship and material is the same as the one I just bought. Otherwise, I won’t buy it. As a Dark Pharoah, buying second-rate items would greatly affect my image”

When Yuri heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but stare for a moment. Then a glint of light flashed by his eyes. Initially, he had an idea to have his undead create something like that small beast skeleton and then sell it to Zhao Hai. But now that Zhao Hai said so, Yuri scrapped that idea. This was because Yuri had never seen materials that were the same as the ones used to make that small skeleton. It would be impossible for Yuri to duplicate it.

Yuri didn’t display any changes to his expression, he immediately nodded and said ,”Mister can rest assured, doing business with this Yuri has a certain guarantee.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “Then we’re settled. City Lord Yuri, here’s to a happy cooperation.”

Yuri replied, “To a happy cooperation!” Then the two of them laughed. Both were satisfied with today’s result!

Chapter 1012: Cultivation Realm’s Strength.

Zhao Hai was currently sitting inside the bone carriage. He took a glass of wine, took a sip, then closed his eyes as he said, “Addison, are you wondering why I am so interested in that giant skull and small beast skeleton?”

Addison was truly wondering. He didn’t know why Zhao Hai needed to set a cooperation with Yuri. That huge skull wasn’t anything rare in the Underworld. And although that small beast skeleton wasn’t common, is it necessary to place a price on it? Was an agreement really needed?

Addison suppressed this thought for quite some time. Upon leaving Dry Bone City, Zhao Hai and Yuri had already signed a business contract, even if it was unnecessary in Addison’s view.

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Addison recovered from his thoughts. He looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, I don’t understand why you would need to do that. Although the Space can produce fiery souls and spirit stones, wasting it like this isn’t good.”

Zhao Hai still had his eyes closed, then he gently waved his hand. Addison suddenly felt that another set of clothes has donned on his body. Addison was stunned, he looked down and found out that he was now wearing a piece of armor. This armor was bone-shaped but it was very light, it also felt like it wasn’t that hard. Addison found out that wearing it on his body felt very comfortable.

Addison gawked, then he looked at Zhao Hai in confusion. He didn’t understand what Zhao Hai wanted to do. At this time, Zhao Hai waved his hand once more as a huge mirror appeared in front of Addison.

Addison looked at the mirror. There was a place-faced man on the mirror wearing an uncommon bone armor. The armor covered the whole body and didn’t leave any place unprotected. Although his face can be seen, this was because the visor of the helmet was opened. Most importantly. Addison felt that the man on the image looked familiar.

It didn’t take more than a minute for Addison to know why the figure was familiar. This was because the pale-faced man wearing the armor was him. The helmet that he was wearing seems to be a tiger skull with one sharp horn on top. It looked very much like the small beast skeleton that they acquired earlier on.

Addison understood that the armor was made out of that small beast skeleton. While Addison was looking at the armor, Zhao Hai suddenly said, “Addison, go try it. See how the armor performs.”

Addison complied with a nod, then he left the carriage and headed towards the Dark Mist. Zhao Hai didn’t worry and just continued drinking his red wine. After a while, explosions began to sound out in the Dark Mist. When the explosions stopped, Addsion appeared inside the carriage once more.

Zhao Hai opened his eyes and said, “So how was it?”

Addison gently caressed the armor as though he was holding a lover. Upon hearing Zhao Hai’s question, Addison replied, “Young Master, this armor is fantastic, it’s very good. It was able to enhance my strength by 20%. At the same time, my defense and speed has also been increased by 20%.”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled. He was very clear, to people that reached his level, increasing by a rank was extremely difficult, not to say about improving one’s strength. Because of this, Zhao Hai can understand Addison’s happiness.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “So do you know why I wanted to buy those skeletons? Remember, if you discover one of these things, buy them at any cost.”

Addison immediately said, “Yes, Young Master. I know what to do.”

Zhao Hai waved his hand. Addison’s armor disappeared and was replaced by a pendant. The pendant was made out of thin bone chain and a pendant modelled after the small beast skeleton that was bought by Zhao Hai.

This pendant was hanging on Addison’s neck. Zhao Hai looked at Addison and said, “Addison, I shall bestow this armor to you. If you want to use the armor, just send a trace of energy to it.”

Addison was impatient to try it, so he sent a trace of energy to the pendant. After doing that, the full body armor was equipped on his body once more. Addison made another thought and the armor vanished into a pendant.

Addison tried it several times more, he was moved as he thanked Zhao Hai, “Young Master, thank you.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, there’s no need to be too polite. Your strength has been improved, isn’t that good for me as well? If you encounter something in the future, then I wouldn’t have to make a move that much. Right, which direction is the Lich?”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Addison immediately swept the place around him with his spiritual force. Then he commanded the undead to fly towards a direction.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about which direction they were headed. He turned to Addison and said, “If we go at this speed, how long do you think we’ll take to reach that Lich?”

Addison turned his head back to Zhao Hai and said, “We should arrive in about two days. But the place we’re going to is the place where that Lich is located before. I’m not sure if he is still there at this time. I haven’t seen him in a while.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “It doesn’t matter, we will slowly look for him, I always find things I want to find. Alright, let’s take a rest.” Addison nodded, then he lowered his head and fiddled with the pendant. It seems like he can’t get tired just looking at it.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about Addison’s actions as his figure flashed and returned to the Space. He just received a lot of plants today, so he wanted to have a good look at them.

Although the huge bones were good things for Zhao Hai, he can’t use them right now. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t bother with them for now. For him, those plants were more important.

Most importantly, after discussing with Cai’er, the bone armor was ready to be planted. The bone armor could enhance the strength of the Undead. And right now, Zhao Hai’s main fighting force were the Undead creatures. If the Undead’s power could be improved, then it would definitely be good news for Zhao Hai.

However, the black soil available for Zhao Hai was very limited. Even if all of the black soil were used to plant the bone armors, who knows how many they could grow in one year.

Zhao Hai wanted to enter the Space in order to discuss this matter in detail. However, after entering the room Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gawk. This was because Laura and the others were looking at the huge bones.

After scanning Yuri’s warehouse, Zhao Hai was able to get some parts of the huge skull. However, it was still incomplete in the end, so Zhao Hai just left them on the side. But Zhao Hai didn’t expect Laura and the others to play with it.

Although Laura and the others weren’t disgusted by the Undead and had even used it often, this was the first time for them to examine one this closely.

When Laura saw Zhao Hai arrive, she immediately said, “Brother Hai, come here quick. This skeleton is quite special, it’s even harder than the Space’s undead. It’s amazing.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare upon hearing this, then he quickly went towards the big skeleton. The skeleton was naturally incomplete, other than the skull and ribs, the other parts were absent.

Back when Zhao Hai acquired these bones, they were all stained with dirt. They didn’t look anything special. Only the huge skull caught Zhao Hai’s attention.

But now the skeleton looked different. When it has been cleaned up, the bones were very white. It wasn’t an ordinary pale white but inside it was like jade as it exuded a faint white light, it looked like a work of art.

Zhao Hai went towards the skeleton and took a careful look at it. He discovered that there was a scratch on a portion of the rib. Although this scratch wasn’t very big, it can be seen that the position of this scratch was at the place where the heart should be.

Zhao Hai looked at the other ribs and discovered that they were complete and without any blemishes. Zhao Hai’s gaze couldn’t help but shrink. Then his staff turned into a sword as he slashed the skeleton.

After a clanging sound, the sword got deflected, leaving no mark on the skeleton. Zhao Hai, as well as the others, were surprised, this result was far from their expectation.

Zhao Hai was especially startled, he used 60% of his strength yet the skeleton remained undamaged. This was an evidence to how formidable this skeleton was.

Zhao Hai tried using 80% of his strength and was finally able to see a result. Zhao Hai waved his hand, receiving the skeleton as they went back inside the living room.

After having sat down, Zhao Hai said, “These skeletons shouldn’t be the only ones in the Underworld. We saw a scratch on the skeleton, and that wasn’t a simple scratch, it was something that was left behind by a sharp blade. The owners of the skeleton should have been killed while they were alive. We don’t know for how long the skeleton have existed, but despite such a long time, they remained hard. Who knows how strong they were when they were still alive, yet they were still killed. This means that there is a more powerful existence than them. It seems like this isn’t a simple matter.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Laura and the others stared, their expressions changed. But Laura quickly said, “Brother Hia, don’t worry too much about it. Just as you said, we don’t know how long this skeleton existed. Since we aren’t sure if they still exist now, there’s no need to think about it at this time.”

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “Naturally I wasn’t worried in the Underworld. In this plane, the strongest beings should be on Addison’s level. However, I suspect that these skeletons didn’t come from the Underworld. If these skeletons are from the Cultivation World, then we might have to readjust how we see the Cultivators.”

Chapter 1013: Cai’er’s Gradual Maturity

Laura and the others were stunned upon hearing Zhao Hai. After that, they all frowned. They understood what Zhao Hai meant. In the Underworld, all experts were almost immortal, this was because they were Undead.

And those large skeletons, from the hardness of their bones, it was enough to prove that they were certainly experts before they died, it wasn’t easy for them to die. Moreover, it was impossible for experts like them to appear in the Underworld. In other words, these huge skeletons didn’t originate in the Underworld.

If they weren’t from the Underworld, then it only meant that they came from a more formidable plane. And presently, the only thing that comes to Zhao Hai’s mind was the Cultivation World.

If these skeletons belong to the Cultivation Realm, then Zhao Hai has to readjust his views regarding the strength of the realm. This was because Zhao Hai’s second slash carried 80% of his strength. With Zhao Hai’s strength, 80% of it was already very huge. And even so, he was only able to make a mark on the bone. Wasn’t that enough to explain the strength of these skeletons?

Laura and the others didn’t expect that Zhao Hai would think so far. Now that Zhao Hai brought it up, this caused a small sense of fear to emerge inside them.

Laura frowned and said, “Brother Hai, you mean?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “I don’t mean anything for now. At this time, the Space doesn’t have the means to appraise those skeletons, let alone us. I just had some understanding with regards to the Cultivation Realm.”

Laura and the others could understand what Zhao Hai wanted to say. At this moment, they still have little understanding with regards to the Cultivation Realm. It was useless for them to think about it right now. The only thing they could do was to improve their strengths as much as possible.

Zhao Hai let out a long breath and decided to not think about this matter. Just as what Laura said, thinking about it at this time was useless. They can only go step by step according to their plan. Even if they wanted to do anything about it, they couldn’t do so.

Zhao Hai moved on as he turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, if we plant the bone armor, how much will it affect the twelve constellation combat suits?”

When Cai’er heard Zhao Hai, she smiled and said, “Young Master, actually, we already have a lot of twelve constellations combat suits. You shouldn’t underestimate the production rate of the Space. Although its output each day isn’t much, it could add up to a lot. And now that time accelerated regions had appeared, I had some of those regions placed on top of black soil. We can plant the combat suits there, immensely boosting their production. And don’t forget, the black soil can accelerate plant growth.”

Zhao Hai asked, “Time-accelerated regions can be placed on top of black soil? Will it affect the growth of the herbs? Also, I’m planning to grow years on some plants on the black soil, not just accelerate their growth.”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master can rest assured, even if the time accelerated region is much stronger than the black soil, there is no actual conflict between the two of them. The black soil only accelerates the growth of plants while the time accelerated region just speeds up time, so there’s no overlap. There won’t be something like the plants in the black soil halting their growth. After all, the time accelerated region must honor the rules, the same is true for the black soil.”

Cai’er’s words almost confused Zhao Hai, but he could faintly understand it. What Cai’er basically said was the time accelerated region and the black soil could be paired with one another. The effect of this overlap would be additive when it came to crops. And when it came to people, only the time accelerated region would act.”

Zhao Hai was glad with this information, “Good, then I’ll trust your decisions. We still need bone armors and twelve constellation combat suits. Right, we’ve just levelled up. You must process where to plant and to place the time accelerated regions.”

Cai’er gave a nod, “Young Master, I know what to do. In fact, I have already planted the twelve constellation combat suits on the time accelerated regions. At this point, almost everyone from the Devil Legion is equipped with the combat suits. The Young Master doesn’t need to worry about this.”

While listening to Cai’er, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel happy as he said, “Good, good! Cai’er, you’re the best. Hahahaha” Then he grabbed Cai’er and gave her a kiss. Cai’er gave a scream, she scrambled to have Zhao Hai let go of her before she flew away. Nobody knew where she had run off to.

When Zhao Hai saw this result, he couldn’t help but stare. But when he remembered what he had just done, he became embarrassed. And with the look that Laura and the others were giving him, Zhao Hai felt distressed.

Zhao Hai didn’t really have any intentions towards Cai’er when he did that, he just did so reflexively. After seeing the expression on Laura and the others’ faces, Zhao Hai felt that he may have been rash in his decision.

However, Zhao Hai discovered that Laura and the others weren’t mad at him. This caused Zhao Hai to feel relieved. But after that, Zhao Hai began to discover that Cai’er’s manner had become more and more mature.

Zhao Hai looked back at the time when he first saw Cai’er. Although it can be said that Cai’er was very strong and Zhao Hai wasn’t aware for how long she has been alive for, Cai’er was still childlike at that time. However, without Zhao Hai noticing, Cai’er was maturing as time went on. As her body got bigger and bigger, she became to learn how to be shy, completely different compared to the playful Cai’er from before.

……………………………………………………………

Two days quickly went past. Over these two days, Zhao Hai spent the majority of his time inside the bone carriage observing the Underworld alongside Addison. The two drank and had a chat, passing the time with comfort.

After two days of travelling, a bone mountain appeared in front of Zhao Hai. It was a very huge bone mountain, it could even be described as a mountain range. At this time, the carriage stopped at the foot of the mountain.

From what Zhao Hai felt, this bone mountain seems to be as high as several kilometers. There were some low-level skeletons walking along the mountain. These skeletons didn’t have any consciousness, they just walked aimlessly in all directions. But some of these skeletons were hunting the others and absorbed their fiery souls, becoming stronger in the process.

Addison swept the mountain with his spiritual force, then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, this is where I met that Lich. That Lich is very formidable, even in my current state, I am still not confident in being able to deal with him.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he turned his head towards the mountain before he said, “Alright, let’s go. I hope we can look for him smoothly. The sooner we find him, the better.” After saying that, the four beast Undead pulled the carriage to traverse the mountain.

Before long, Zhao Hai and the others appeared on the summit. The low-ranked skeletons didn’t dare approach Zhao Hai’s group. Although these small skeletons didn’t have any intellect, their instincts told them that they couldn’t just approach people like Zhao Hai.

Along the way, Zhao Hai kept scanning the mountain for things that he might be able to bring to the Space. But unfortunately, he didn’t find too much in this huge mountain. Although there were plants here, these plants were either already in the Space or weren’t high-ranked enough.

Although Zhao Hai was a little disappointed, he just shook it off. After all, he can get bone-shaped plants whenever he wanted.

When Zhao Hai arrived at the summit, he took the chance to take a look at the horizon. Behind this mountain were never-ending peaks.

After seeing this situation, Zhao Hai couldn’t bear but force a smile. Then he turned his head to Addison and said, “Addison, do you know which direction that Lich might be?”

Addison smiled bitterly and said, “Young Master, honestly, I don’t know. At that time, I was too weak. I didn’t dare to stop here. After I made a transaction with that Lich, I left immediately.”

Zhao Hai gave a helpless smile and said, “It seems like we’ll have to scour the mountain to find him. Alright, let’s go back to the Space. If only the two of us look for him, then who knows when we’ll be finished.” Then after Zhao Hai sent Addison back to the Space, he put his hand outside and had the Blood Ghost Staff transform into small needles and had them fly around. This was the method that Zhao Hai thought of in order to find the Lich as soon as possible. Zhao Hai believed that as long as the Lich was in this mountain range, he would be able to find him.

Meanwhile, Addison went straight towards the Hell Space. He couldn’t adapt to Zhao Hai’s living space, there was too much sunlight. Although Addison didn’t fear sunlight, it still made him feel uncomfortable.

On the other hand, when Zhao Hai returned to the Space, he began to carefully examine the images on the monitor. At this time, the display has been divided into many smaller images, each one pertaining to a small Blood Ghost Staff needle. At this moment, aside from the bone mountain, nothing special has been spotted.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t worry. Worrying was useless in this case. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t get too anxious. Conversely, Zhao Hai had the needles slow down, he didn’t want to miss any good items just because the needles were going too fast.

The bone mountain was very big. Zhao Hai didn’t believe that such a huge structure wouldn’t have one or two great things. From what Zhao Hai can see, this bone mountain was just like a virgin forest on Earth, there was bound to be a treasure here somewhere.

And just like Zhao Hai thought, the search yielded a few harvests. Among them were more huge skeletons as well as bone plants.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wasn’t polite and immediately took the skeletons and plants directly to the Space. Moreover, he also took in some strange items like iron swords and damaged shields.

This didn’t mean that Zhao Hai was just sorting through junk. This was because these things were indeed rare in the Underworld. In this plane, the weapons the Undead used were mostly made out of bone while weapons made by high-ranked beings were made out of their own body. Things like iron and wood weapons were almost nonexistent here. Because of this, Zhao Hai wanted to investigate the origin of these items.

Chapter 1014: A Field Inside The Mountains!

But much to Zhao Hai’s disappointment, the rusted swords and broken shields didn’t provide any useful information for him. Moreover, after going through the scanner, the materials used for these weapons were substandard. It can be said that they were practically worthless.

So Zhao Hai had to throw these things out again. After all, he can just casually take out something much stronger than that broken sword. He wasn’t the king of trash.

In the beginning, Zhao Hai had no sense of how large this bone mountain was. But after an hour of exploration, Zhao Hai finally got an idea. After an hour, the needles that went to all directions had yet to find an end. This caused Zhao Hai to be surprised.

Although Zhao Hai had the small needles slow down, this slowing down was relative. Compared to an average person flying, the speed of the needles was still very fast.

For such a speed to be unable to reach the ends of the Bone Mountain, this meant that this Bone Mountain was enormous. It has exceeded Zhao Hai’s expectation.

Laura and the others were similarly startled. Just like Zhao Hai, they didn’t think that this bone mountain would actually be this big. Zhao Hai had already collected ten bone plants in the Space. This wasn’t a small number in the Underworld, after all, these kinds of plants were not very easy to come upon.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai began to accumulate more and more huge skeletons into the Space. In addition to a human form, Zhao Hai also collected an animal-shaped skeleton. He took them because they had the same texture as the human-shaped ones.

When Zhao Hai discovered that this animal-shaped skeleton had the same build as the human skeleton, he was taken aback. He didn’t think that a beast would have the same skeletal build as that huge skull. Naturally, after Zhao Hai took that skeleton to the Space, the Space issued a prompt saying that Zhao Hai’s level was insufficient. This caused Zhao Hai to be more curious about the Underworld.

Zhao Hai knew that the Underworld had more secrets left for him to uncover. However, Zhao Hai didn’t think about them for now. At this time, Zhao Hai was determined to get more of those mysterious bones into the Space, maybe he’ll find a use for them in the future.

Five hours went by, Zhao Hai’s needles had already flown to the sides of the bone mountain. They had yet to discover anything suspicious. However, Zhao Hai was able to get more plants and huge skeletons in the meantime.

Presently, only the south had yet to be explored. But even so, there were still no special places spotted. Even traces of ordinary skeletons couldn’t be seen here.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get anxious. He didn’t know if the Lich was still in this mountain. If the Lich was still here, then that would save some trouble for Zhao Hia. If he wasn’t, then Zhao Hai would be disappointed.

Another hour passed by, Zhao Hai was still persistent. Laura and the others had already gone to sleep. Zhao Hai was starting to get bored as he drank tea and observed the monitor from time to time.

Then at this moment, an image in the monitor began to change, causing Zhao Hai to stare. He immediately placed down the book he was holding and focused on the monitor. The other images on the monitor disappeared, making space for only one image.

Zhao Hai carefully scrutinized the display and unexpectedly saw a stretch of field!

Zhao Hai didn’t mistakenly see it, it was actually a stretch of field in the middle of the huge bone mountain range. The field was about ten mu(6667 sq.m.) in size. There was a fence surrounding this field and there were plants planted inside. Most importantly, Zhao Hai hadn’t seen most of these plants before. And in this field, Zhao Hai couldn’t see any piece of broken bone anywhere.

In this ten mu of land were very small shards of bone, the biggest was about a fingernail in size while most were basically dust.

The area wasn’t very big, but what’s most important to Zhao Hai was the fact that this place existed. He couldn’t help but feel surprised.

There were no such things as oases in the Underworld. The Undead rely on blood from the Blood Ponds and the Dark Mist in order to survive, so they really didn’t need fertile land to live off of. Since entering the Underworld, this was Zhao Hai’s first time seeing a piece of land like this. Zhao Hai even thought that there was only one such land in the entirety of the Underworld.

Zhao Hai’s heart skipped a beat, he knew that he had found the place. Zhao Hai made the needle stop as he took a careful look at the field. On the field, Zhao Hai could see plants that he had and hadn’t seen before, and all of them were neatly planted in their own regions.

Zhao Hai scanned through the field and saw that other than the plants, there was nothing else. After that, Zhao Hai directed the needle, as well as the other needles, to scan the surroundings of the field.

Before long, Zhao Hai discovered a cave on a side of the bone mountain. This cave wasn’t very big, its entrance was just enough for a person to enter and exit. However, the entrance of the cave was carefully laid out. There was a flat land in front of it, paved with stones and was properly flattened.

Zhao Hai knew that he had found the place. He didn’t call Laura and the others out and instead took Addison with him to leave the Space.

After Addison saw the cave, he immediately understood what was going on. He turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, do you think that this is the place?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “This should be it. Try and call him out. However, don’t use your spiritual force to scan the place, we don’t want the other party to think that we came here with malice.”

Addison nodded before turning his head towards the entrance and said, “Is someone inside?”

The entrance remained still, no sound was heard back, so Addison increased the volume of his voice, “Is Senior here? Addison came to visit!”

Just as he said that, a sound was transmitted from inside the cave, “Addison? Why does that name sound familiar? I heard that somewhere.” The voice got closer and closer before a Lich appeared in the entrance.

The Lich looked very ancient, white hair end-to-end, the same was true for his beard. He was wearing a robe that covered the rest of his body, giving out an ethereal feeling. His lower body was floating amidst the Dark Mist.

The Lich looked at Zhao Hai and Addison and couldn’t help but pause. After sweeping his gaze on Zhao Hai and turning to Addison, he knitted his brows and said, “You seem to be a Vampire. Have you been here before? I don’t seem to remember.”

Addison turned to glance at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, this is Senior Lich.” Then he turned to the Lich and said, “Senior, do you remember me? I was fortunate to meet senior outside the mountain. I also helped Senior acquire a blood butterfly, and in exchange, Senior gave me a technique as a reward.”

When the Lich heard Addison, he stayed silent for some time before he nodded and said, “Hmm, that seems to be more than 1 thousand years ago. At that time, you are still a Marquis. Becoming a Vampire King in such a short time is quite an achievement.”

Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. One thousand years was actually just a short time for this old Lich. If other intelligent lifeforms heard this, then they might get mad.

Addison bowed to the Lich and said, “Right, right. It is an honor that Senior actually still remembers me. Just like you said, I was just a Vampire Marquis at that time.”

The old Lich nodded and then he looked at Addison and said, “Why did you come here? And who is this? For a Vampire King to call you Young Master, it seems like you aren’t a simple character.”

While he said that, the old Lich’s bright eyes sized Zhao Hai up. Zhao Hai took a step forward and bowed, “I heard Addison talk about Senior some time ago. I have great admiration for characters like Senior, so we made a special trip in order to visit you. Me and Addison has been travelling for some time.”

The Old Lich looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Visit me? Why?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “We want to invite Senior to join us. I have established a special Magic Formation Research Laboratory. We need brilliant minds like Senior in the laboratory.”

The Old Lich knit his brows and said, “Magic formations? But it has been some time since I researched magic formations. I’m currently researching the fire inside one’s soul. I’m not interested in magic formations right now.”

When he heard the Old Lich, Zhao Hai quickly replied, “Senior, please wait. I have something to show Senior. After seeing it, I will ask Senior to make your decision.” Then Zhao Hai waved his hand and took a laptop out.

Zhao Hai’s people were still rarely equipped with a laptop. It might only be Karen’s group who were using laptops extensively. Let alone using it, it was even rarer to see one. Take Addison for example, he had never seen a computer before.

Zhao Hai took out a closed laptop and didn’t immediately open it. The laptop looked very sleek. It’s frame was made out of metal and was brightly polished.

Addison and the Old Lich were puzzled at why Zhao Hai would take out a strangle looking metal box.

Zhao Hai smile faintly before opening the laptop. And just as expected, Addison and the Lich stared since they had never seen the insides of a laptop before.

Zhao Hai pushed some buttons and keys on the laptop in order to open a file. In this file were records about the magic armor research; magic formations, videos of magic armor battles, a 3D model of a magic armor, amongst others.

The Old Lich and Addison couldn’t hide the surprise in their eyes. This was the first time they had seen a mystical thing like this. After fiddling a few buttons, it could actually show some patterns and words on it surface.

Zhao Hai didn’t show magic armor battles at first, instead he showed the 3D model of the magic armor. Naturally, this image rotated on the screen along with the descriptions that Karen and the others put in.

Zhao Hai turned to the Old Lich and gestured at the laptop, “Senior, this is an item we discovered outside a spatial rift. There are a lot of these things on the other side of that Spatial Rift. These things hold formidable fighting strength. These things are full of never before seen magic formations.”

Actually, Karen’t explanations could already be seen on the screen. While Karen’s explanation was being played, the old Lich’s attention was basically glued on the computer.

It was only until Zhao Hai took the laptop back did the Old Lich recover. The Old Lich looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Do those things really exist? How is their combat strength?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Senior, take a look at this and you’ll understand.” Then he opened the video of the fight between the magic armors and the foreign races. This video was something that Cai’er made. The editing made it possible to showcase the various aspects of the magic armor.

It wasn’t only the Old Lich who was glued to the monitor, Addison was the same. In the video, there were a thousand Foreign Race warriors fighting against the magic armors.

However, the Old Lich and Addison was somewhat unmoved. This was because, in their eyes, the fighting power of the Foreign Races wasn’t any good.

Zhao Hai looked at the expressions of the two men and said, “Are you thinking that these magic armors aren’t any good? But what if I tell you that their enemies aren’t weak people? Moreover, these magic armors are driven by people, much like carriages. Also, the people driving these magic armors had fairly the same strength as an ordinary person.”

As soon as they heard Zhao Hai, the two couldn’t help but change their thoughts. Naturally they knew that if ordinary people could man these things, then its overall utility was certainly great.

Zhao Hai continued, “If we can figure out the magic formations on these magic armors, even if we don’t use it for magic armors, it is already a huge benefit to us. After we figure it out, then we could use them in a lot of things. If we can use it on weapons, then the weapons would experience a qualitative change.”

Then Zhao Hai opened a text document. Depicted on the document were the various designs of magic formations as well as the current progress in figuring them out. Beside each magic formation were detailed lists of their potential use. However, majority of these portions were blank as they had yet to be cracked.

Actually, Zhao Hai taking the laptop out was part of his plan regarding the Old Lich. He knew that the Old Lich would find the laptop’s novelty interesting and would definitely feel curious about it. And sure enough, the Old Lich was very curious about this metallic box.

Moreover, with the laptop having magic formations saved inside, it would be impossible for the Old Lich to remain unmoved. As long as the Old Lich bites the bait, then Zhao Hai would be able to lead him into the Space. And when the ancient Lich enters the Space, the discussion would begin.

Chapter 1015: Collection of the Old Lich

The Old Lich was obviously attracted to Zhao Hai’s computer. Besides the computer, the Lich was also thinking about the magic formations inside. Since he was dissatisfied with the amount of formations that Zhao Hai presented, the Lich snatched the laptop away from Zhao Hai’s hands and looked through the contents of the document himself.

The Old Lich watched  the magic formations for some time, when he wanted to see the next magic formation, he suddenly found out that there was no more left. The Old LIch recovered as he turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “Is this it? Where are the other magic formations? I want to see them.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Of course there’s more, the magic formations inside the laptop aren’t all of them. If Senior is willing to join us, then I will surely make Senior take a look at those formations.”

The Old Lich gawked, then his expression changed as he looked straight into Zhao Hai’s eyes and said, “If I join you, can I research other things besides magic formations?”

When he heard the Old Lich, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile, “Of course. Please rest assured that you have full freedom. We wouldn’t interfere with what you are studying.”

The Old Lich paused, then he turned to look at his field and said, “What about my field? I want to use all of the plants here.”

Zhao Hai was still smiling when he replied, “Senior can feel relieved. I will have a supply of all of your plants here. You can have as much of them as you want.”

Old Lich looked at Zhao Hai with disbelief, “Impossible. How much could you have? I’ve had this land for thousands of years, and I took care of the plants every day. How can you have the same?”

Zhao Hai replied, “Senior, if you don’t believe me, then you can take a look for yourself. If Senior thinks that I am being anxious, then I will take my leave.”

The Old Lich looked at Zhao Hai. He felt that something was wrong, but as to what it was, he had no idea. But then he remembered that he has a method to dissolve contracts. Even if Zhao Hai was scheming, it wouldn’t do well, so the Old Lich shook away his worries as he nodded and said, “Alright, then I’ll go and take a look.”

One has to recognize that the Lich had been solitary for so long, so his mindfulness towards other people had dulled. This made him easily believe Zhao Hai’s words.

Zhao Hai gave a faint smile and said, “Senior, I have a Spatial Divergent Ability. I can use it to make a spatial rift towards my place. This way, we would be able to travel quicker. What does Senior think?”

The Old Lich gawked, his two eyes shone as he looked at Zhao Hai, “You can use spatial techniques? Fantastic. Show me.”

Although Zhao Hai didn’t understand the Old Lich’s enthusiasm, he complied, he waved his hand and a spatial rift appeared on his side. Zhao Hai turned to the Old Lich and said, “Senior, please.”

The Old LIch stared at the spatial rift and muttered, “Space Magic, it’s really Space Magic. Fantastic, fantastic.” Then he didn’t hesitate as he floated into the Space.

Zhao Hai stared as the Old Lich unhesitatingly entered the Space. At the same time, the Space issued a prompt about subjugation. Zhao Hai let out a breath of relief before he went to the Space along with Addison.

The Old Lich was waiting for Zhao Hai inside. Upon seeing Zhao Hai the Old Lich gave his greetings, “I have seen the Young Master.”

Zhao Hia nodded, then he smiled and said, “Right, what is your name?”

The Old Lich replied, “Answering to the Young Master, I’m called Gimreden.”[1]

Zhao Hai nodded, “Good. So what have you been researching lately?”

Gimreden replied, “I have been studying the fire inside the souls for some time. I want to try joining a fiery soul with another thing, like swords of shields.”

Zhao Hai listened to the Old Lich and couldn’t help but stare. Then his heart was moved. Zhao Hai was aware that fiery souls in the Underworld were the same as the soul of a person. And Gimreden’s research on joining fiery souls to weapons was akin to making an artificial Artifact Spirit. This was cutting-edge research, who knows what implications it might have upon completion. Zhao Hai inquired, “So how was the research? Did you manage to get any achievements?”

Gimreden shook his head and said, “I haven’t had much progress yet, my research time was too short. Moreover, I’m short of plants. The ones planted in the field just isn’t enough.”

Zhao Hai looked at the Lich and said, “How long have you been researching?”

Gimreden looked embarrassed as he replied, “Young Master, it’s a very short time, just about less than 1500 years!”

When Zhao Hai heard this, he couldn’t help but roll his eyes. Less than 1500 years was short? Then how many years would ‘long’ be? How many lifetimes would this take? Even people’s bones would turn to dust during that period.

Zhao Hai looked at Gimreden and said, “Did you say that there’s no great progress in those 1500 years?”

Gimreden shook his head and said, “There’s not much progress. In those 1500 years, I’ve spent most of the time collecting plants. I used that time to collect and find methods to grow them properly. Because of that, I haven’t made much progress.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I will have Cai’er send you to Wild Dragon Island in a while. After that, you can do your research in the lab. There are also other Lich who can aid you in doing research. As for the plants, I will take care of it. In the future, you just have to worry about your research. If you need anything else, don’t hesitate to tell me.”

Gimreden gave a nod. Then Zhao Hai said, “Cai’er, come here. Please deliver Gimreden to Wild Dragon Island and arrange for a place for him to live in. Gimreden, do you have things you need to bring with you?”

Gimreden immediately responded, “Young Master, I have a lot of beastskin scrolls back in the Underworld. I also have some bone books compiled. Those things hold a record of my research over the years. You’ll have to help me bring those things into the Space.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Rest assured, I will help you bring them into the Space. I’ll even take those things that you don’t want.”

Gimreden smiled and said, “Then that would be great. But Young Master, I’m also interested in that magic armor. If there’s a chance, I’d like to try combining fiery souls and magic armors. I reckon it would produce a great result.”

Upon hearing Gimreded, Zhao Hai gawked, then he gave a long stare at the Lich. He didn’t expect the Lich to develop such an idea. Unifying fiery souls and magic armors? What will it make? Transformers? This Lich is truly crazy!

Zhao Hai took a deep breath to calm his mood, then he nodded and said, “Alright. You can research whatever you like. You can go.” At this time, Cai’er came in and took Gimreden away.

After that, Zhao Hai and Addison returned to the cave in the Underworld where Gimreden used to live. Upon entering, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gawk. The inside of the cave was greatly disproportionate compared to its entrance. The cave was divided into three regions. The first region was Gimreden’s laboratory. The lab was another large cave that was hundreds of square meters in floor area. Inside the laboratory were devices used for experimentation, most of them being made out of bones. However, it can be seen that Gimreden was very serious in his work, each and every apparatus was meticulously and beautifully made.

Zhao Hai took these things into the Space. Although the Space can provide Gimreden with much better glass apparatus, Zhao Hai still collected them since he didn’t know whether Gimreden has any special use for them.

After taking a look at the laboratory, Zhao Hai went to the second region. This region was basically Gimreden’s study. The study didn’t just have one or two rooms, but instead it had five. The first room wasn’t any smaller than the laboratory, it was a hundred square meters of floor space filled with bone shelves stacked with beastkin scrolls and bone books.

A bone book was another record used in the Underworld. One would have to use a knife in order to engrave their records into the books. It was a bit like bamboo strips used by the ancient Chinese. One could see how much research Gimreden did by looking at the records present in this study. Zhao Hai could see the Gimreden’s records were much more formal compared to Kampala. Instead of casually storing them, Gimreden divided the records into areas. Inside the study were regions pertaining to magic, magic formations, martial arts, bone classification, and others. The way it was compiled was very detailed.

And in each region were labels describing the general content of the books. It was basically the same system used in a library.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but praise Gimreden’s methods. It seems like Gimreden was more meticulous in his research compared to Kampala.

Zhao Hai took everything from the study into the Space. After that, Zhao Hai went to the cave’s third region. This region was much more extraordinary, taking up 15 caves on their own. Moreover, each cave was much bigger than the study, at around a thousand square meters in floor area. They were really big.

What was most important about this region was that it was a warehouse. Zhao Hai had to recognize Gimreden’s extensive years of existence and foundation. Gimreden on his own was akin to an ancient Noble family. The contents of this warehouse was much more valuable than Yuri’s collection. Also, inside this region, two of the warehouses were stocked full of giant skeletons. Not only were there human-shaped skeletons, there were also piles of beast shaped skeletons. From Zhao Hai’s estimates, in these two warehouses, the quantity of skeletons would reach about 2000 sets. Naturally, Zhao Hai took all of these skeletons into the Space. In addition to the ones taken in by the Space before, Zhao Hai now had 5000 large skeletons.

And besides the huge skeletons, what made Zhao Hai happy the most was the fact that he found several small beast skeletons inside, eight of them to be exact.

Although eight  small beast skeletons might not look a lot, to Zhao Hai it was already a huge harvest.

Moreover, Zhao Hai hadn’t seen the appearance of these small beasts before. Zhao Hai didn’t know how many more forms the small beast skeletons had, but he was very happy to take them all into the Space and plant them as seeds.

* * *

Transliteration says ‘Jim Ryden’. But fck that. xD

Chapter 1016: Bone Field and Blood Spirit Beast

A bountiful harvest! It was an absolutely rich harvest!

Zhao Hai didn’t expect Gimreden to acquire this much treasures. Besides the small beast skeleton and giant skeletons, there were also a lot of plants. Naturally, these plants were either preserved or already turned to powder. Zhao Hai wasn’t too excited about these things, he just saw them as useful. After all, only living plants could give the Space experience.

After everything had been sent to the Space, Zhao Hai and Addison walked out of the cave and headed towards the field.

This medicine field was the same one that Zhao Hai spotted before. There were about a total of 20 different plants here. This was the most amount of plants that Zhao Hai saw while in the Underworld. Zhao Hai hadn’t seen over half of these plants.

Zhao Hai looked at these plants before turning his head to Addison, “Addison, do you recognize these plants?”

Addison smiled bitterly and said, “Young Master, you don’t need to ask me. I couldn’t identify most of these plants. I really don’t know where old Gimreden got them from.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I can see that Gimreden really looks after this field. It wouldn’t be strange if the people from the Underworld would go crazy if they heard about this field. I didn’t expect there to be this many plants here. We need to take them to the Space, it’s much safer for these plants to be there.” Addison agreed. Zhao Hai looked at the stretch of field ten mu in size. Naturally, it would be impossible for Zhao Hai to take all of this land in one go. But fortunately, Gimreden divided the land into lots. This way, Zhao Hai wouldn’t have any trouble taking them bit by bit.”

After taking a careful look at the field, Zhao Hai opened a spatial rift and took a piece of land one mu at a time.

Upon receiving the land into the Space, ZHao Hai immediately arranged for this lot to be transferred to the Hell Space since there was also a Bone Mountain there. In this case, the field’s environment wouldn’t change that much.

Just as the patch of field was relocated, the Space immediately issued a prompt, “Special-attribute plot detected. Plot exclusively used for darkness-type plants. May plant darkness-attribute plants on plot. Darkness-attribute plants planted in new plot would experience the same benefits as planting in black soil. Since host has introduced a new type of farmland, the Space has been upgraded to level 102. Hoping for the Host to continue working hard!”

Zhao Hai stared, then a burst of happiness welled inside him. He never thought of acquiring such a huge benefit. He didn’t think that this patch of field that Gimreden made would actually be classified as a special attribute plot by the Space. This was the first time that Zhao Hai experienced such a phenomenon.

In any case, this was an absolutely great matter for Zhao Hai. This plot had the same benefits as the black soil for dark-attribute plants. This was essentially increasing the amount of black soil that Zhao Hai could use.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai immediately received the rest of the field into the Space. When the second batch of land was sent, the Space didn’t issue a prompt. However, Zhao Hai didn’t worry about it. He knew the characteristic of the Space. If there were two of the same things, the Space would only issue a prompt on the first one.

After all ten mu of the field was relocated, Zhao Hai took Addison with him and entered the Space. Upon returning, Zhao Hai let Addison return to the Hell Space while he called Cai’er over.

When Cai’er saw Zhao Hai, she was a bit embarrassed. Her face was a little red as she said, “Young Master, do you need me for anything?”

Upon seeing Cai’er’s reaction, Zhao Hai couldnt’ help but feel a headache. However, he just nodded and said, “I need to ask you something. Can that bone field be expanded?”

Cai’er immediately understood what Zhao Hai meant, so she nodded and said, “You can, Young Master, since the bone field and black soil are different to one another. The black soil has all attributes while the bone field belonged to the darkness-attribute. Because of this, only plants with the darkness attribute can be planted on bone fields. Since the bone field can be collected from outside and can be controlled, then it’s natural for us to be able to expand it. However, this field is built on top of bone mountains and also need a blood pond nearby. Although there are several bone mountains inside the Space, if you want to expand, then we would need to collect more.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, leave it to me. I’ll take care of it right away.” After that, Zhao Hai appeared in the Underworld and received the bone mountain where Gimreden stayed in.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t take the entire mountain range. He just took a few bone mountains without any skeleton activity around it. But even so, Zhao Hai calculated that 10 thousand mu of bones would be enough.

10 thousand mu of bone field wasn’t a small number. And with these fields, Zhao Hai would be able to plant all of the darkness-attribute plants here. In turn, this would free up a lot of space in a black soil elsewhere. Being able to plant more things on those fields was a very big thing for Zhao Hai.

After this matter has been taken care of, Zhao Hai proceeded to bring Addison back to Three Saint City. Zhao Hai decided to live in Three Saint City while Addison would take care of the other matters. No matter what, Addison’s reputation in the Underworld was much better compared to Zhao Hai. The Resistance Army, Neutral Alliance, and even the Dark Temple knew about him.

When Zhao Hai returned to Three Saint City, the most happy were Guli and Jiang Zheng. They liked staying beside Zhao Hai. Moreover, for Zhao Hai stay in Three Saint City, this meant that Zhao Hai had a great relationship with them. How could the two not be happy with this?

However, Zhao Hai didn’t care about what the two thought. He just gave an order to Addison to quicken up the unification of the Resistance Army. This duty wasn’t easy, but it was a task appropriate for Addison since this was what he intended to do from the start.

Aside from being appropriate for this task, Addison also had enough strength to do it. Because of this, Addison would be able to quicken his speed in conquering the Underworld. In just about five days from returning to Three Saint City, Zhao Hai heard that Addison already managed to conquer another city. This caused Zhao Hai to be startled, but he still couldn’t help but frown..

Addison was very strong, but he was too strong. Being this explosive in his performance didn’t necessarily mean that it was a good thing. Doing this would only push Addison to the opposite side of the Resistance Army. Zhao Hai can be sure that if it weren’t for him, then Addison certainly wouldn’t have a happy ending.

Not to say about the collective opposition of the Resistance Army, even the people from the Dark Temple wouldn’t want Addison to unify the Rebels. They would certainly stop the Resistance Army from gaining more strength.

One shouldn’t think that the Dark Temple wouldn’t use schemes. Perhaps the temple’s undead wouldn’t, but one shouldn’t forget about the fellow that manages the plane. That person wasn’t necessarily an Undead, who could tell what he was capable of doing?

With so many opposing forces, Addison’s unification of the Resistance Army would almost be impossible. However, now that Zhao Hai had appeared, everything became different. Not only was Zhao Hai strong, he also had formidable military strength. These factors would allow Addison to unify the Resistance Army in a short time.

Just like Zhao Hai thought, upon hearing Addison take another city, the remaining members of the Resistance Army began to make an unexpected alliance in order to deal with the Vampire King. However, Addison was also prepared to deal with the Resistance Army in one fell swoop.

But then, at this time, a report came in that the Dark Temple was attacking. This caused Addison to feel helpless. On the other hand, Zhao Hai expected this result. If the Dark Temple didn’t seize the opportunity to interfere, then they wouldn’t be the Dark Temple.

Under such circumstances, the Resistance Army had to stop their infighting and form one army to confront the Dark Temple in the frontlines.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t just stay inside Three Saint City while all of this was happening. He took Guli and Jiang Zheng with him to the frontline. The frontline that the two sides would be fighting on would be on both sides of a blood river.

This Blood River can be said to be the only river in the Underworld. Up until the present, nobody knew the river’s source as well as where it flows to. The liquid flowing through this river was the same as the ones inside Blood Ponds. The widest part of the river was ten li (5km) wide while its narrowest part was 5 li(2.5km). Nobody knew how deep the river was, but the people in the Underworld knew that there were rare beings living in the river, and they’re called Blood Spirit Beasts.

Blood Spirit Beasts were the residents of the Blood River. The people in the Underworld couldn’t figure out whether these Blood Spirit Beasts were dark creatures or undead. This was because the shapes of these beasts were just too strange.

No one knew the real appearance of these Blood Spirit Beasts. These beasts would attack anybody who flew over the river of blood. Moreover, each time they appeared, they looked different. Sometimes they would look like bats, and in some times tigers, dragons and some would even appear humanoid. But no matter what their form was, they all had a similar characteristic. All of the blood spirit beasts were recognizable by their blood red bodies. And when they were exposed to great damage, their bodies would instantly liquify and return to the blood river.

It has been a legend in the Underworld that nobody had killed any blood spirit beast. Perhaps some people had killed some of them, but nobody would be able to prove it. This was because in all cases these beasts would turn to blood and become part of the river.

The attacking strength of these blood spirit beasts was quite formidable. A single attack from them would be stronger than a Gold Skeleton and some even reaching Crystal Skeleton level. Although this attacking strength wasn’t overwhelmingly great, these blood spirit beasts were all from the blood river. As long as the blood river exists, then these blood spirit beasts would be inexhaustible. Nobody knew how many blood spirit beasts lived in the entire Blood River.

Chapter 1017: Plot and Scheme

The Blood River looked like a natural barrier dividing the Resistance Army and the Dark Temple. It can be said that without the Blood River, then the Resistance Army would have already been wiped out by the Dark Temple. If the Dark Temple wanted to attack the Resistance Army, then they would have to pass through the Blood River. Because of this, the Resistance Army was able to block the Dark Temple time and time again.

At this time, both banks of the blood river became giant military compounds. But these military compounds weren’t very well set up. This was because there was no need to make an elaborate camp. There were only a few tents and carriages present for those high-ranked undead. As for the other soldiers, they were eight standing or sitting on the ground.

Zhao Hai swept both banks of the river with his spiritual force. Currently there were billions of undead present, with more coming still.

Naturally, the Resistance Army were at a disadvantage when it came to numbers. Zhao Hai didn’t give Addison the forces in his hands, this way he wouldn’t be too eye-catching.

Addison’s reputation was quite huge, so how could people be unaware of how many people he had in his hands? If a billion high-rank undead suddenly emerged under Addison’s command, then wouldn’t people be suspicious? Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t send his Undead to Addison. And even the Undead on the conquered cities stayed put. These Undead were a potential force, and Zhao Hai wouldn’t want to show all of his cards.

It has to be said that the Undead that had surrendered to the Space had already reached more than six billion. The reason why there were so many was because Zhao Hai also took low-ranked Undead into the Space. Because of this, the Undead inside the Space experienced a violent increase in number.

But all of these Undead weren’t inside the Space. Some were let out by Zhao Hai in order to scour the areas near their cities and look for any useful things.

Currently following Addison were 500 million advanced-level undead, and this was already a powerful force. One must know that these 500 million Undead had a fighting strength comparable to a Divergent Skeletons.

Divergent Skeletons were beings before Crystal Skeletons, and above Crystal Skeletons were the Skeleton Kings, Guli’s level. This meant that Addison’s undead had strength only lower than Guli by two ranks. Such strength shouldn’t be underestimated.

Zhao Hai was currently sitting inside Guli’s carriage. The place that he was right now was in Addison’s camp. After all, Three Saint City being conquered by Addison was a well known matter in the Resistance Army. Since Zhao Hai belonged to Three Saint City, it was natural for him to be inside Addison’s camp.

Addison was currently in a meeting with the other leaders. Zhao Hai didn’t participate since there was no need. He just handed a blood needle to Addison so that he could hear anything that Addison could.

The Resistance Army meeting was actually very simple. Compared to Human wars, the wars in the Underworld were very basic. They hardly pay attention to tactics and just rush towards the enemies. The deciding factor of the war lay in the hands of the high-ranked undead. As for the low-ranks, they were used as cannon fodder.

This was the reason why war meetings in the Underworld were very simple. It was just a matter of assigning an area to be guarded by each person. If a region looks difficult, they would discuss reinforcements. The other things weren’t discussed.

One advantage in doing war in the Underworld was the fact that there was no need for logistics. This was because the Undead didn’t need to eat nor did they use weapons and armor.

At this time, Addison’s region has already been decided. The region wasn’t out of what Zhao Hai expected, Addison was placed into the most dangerous place in the conflict. And most of the Undead agreed to this assignment. When Addison returned, his expression wasn’t very good.

Upon entering the bone carriage, Addison’s expression was still bad. Addison gave Zhao Hai a bow before complaining, “Young Master, those fellows are being too excessive. I want to kill them all.”

Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “Forget it. Those guys just want to borrow the Dark Temple’s strength in order to suppress you. It’s your fault for being too famous.”

Addison coldly snorted and said, “Those guys want to deal with the Dark Spirit Temple yet they do things like this. If the Resistance Army was united, then situations like this wouldn’t have appeared.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and didn’t respond to Addison’s rant, he just said, “Addison, prepare our defenses well. It’s possible that the Dark Temple’s main attack would be centered on you.”

When Addison heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but stare, then he said, “Young Master, why do you say that?”

Zhao Hai replied, “The Dark Temple’s timing is too good. Although a lot of people in the Resistance Army have united to deal with you, there is still a good chance that you’ll succeed. A united Resistance Army isn’t something that the Dark Temple wants to see. Therefore, they will definitely find a way to stop you from your goal. So they chose to attack this time. This way, the Resistance Army would be forced to face them. This isn’t the first time that the Dark Temple fought against you, so they are very aware of your defense. They would surely launch a strong attack against your region, causing you to lose the most. If you lose your forces, then it would make it harder for you to unite the Resistance Army. A disunited Resistance Army isn’t a threat to the Dark Temple.”

Addison thought about what Zhao Hai said. He never really analyzed the situation through. Addison didn’t neglect Zhao Hai’s words as he gave a nod and prepared to ready his defense.

Naturally, Zhao Hai would follow behind. But this time Addison was outside while Zhao Hai was inside the bone carriage along with Guli and Jiang Zheng.

Guli looked at Zhao Hai who was drinking and said, “Young Master, is it really like what you said? Will the Dark Temple do that?’

Zhao Hai placed his teacup down and smiled, “You’ll know when the time comes.” Then after he said that, Zhao Hai closed his eyes and let out a long breath. Upon seeing this, Guli decided not to disturb him anymore.

It didn’t take long before the group arrived at the place Addison would be defending. The Blood River in this area was very narrow at about six li(3km). This made it the most dangerous place in the frontlines.

The narrower the river, the smaller the chance of being attacked by the Blood Spirit Beasts. This made the region more likely to be the place being attacked the most. Those who were assigned to defend this place often failed in their task. There were a lot of undead on the level of Guli and Jiang Zheng that perished here.

After Zhao Hai and the others arrived at the region, Addison entered entered the carriage. Naturally, he was here to see Zhao Hai.

Although Addison’s men were also Zhao Hai’s subordinates, Zhao Hai still had the best relationship with Addison, Guli, and Jiang Zheng. The other Undead simply had no qualifications to see Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai looked at Addison and said, “What is it? Is everything prepared?”

Addison smiled and said, “We still need to arrange which people gets assigned where. There’s no need to worry about anything else when the battle starts, giving the signal to attack would be enough. Right, Young Master, do you want to capture some Blood Spirit Beasts for the Space?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Of course. But I cannot do that now. I’ll do it when the battle starts. If we move at this time, we would be making a huge scene. It might even be possible to alert the opposite party. Waiting for the battle to take off wouldn’t be took late to take action.”

Addison nodded, he could understand Zhao Hai’s decision. Capturing Blood Spirit Beasts at this time truly wasn’t a good idea.

Guli looked at the opposite bank of the Blood River, his tone seemed to be hopeful as he said, “Just wait, sooner or later the whole Underworld would be under Young Master’s control.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, it’s still too early to talk about that. Let’s think about today’s battle first. This time, when you are in a critical situation, you are not allowed to use the bone armor. The bone armor can be said to be a trump card of our side, we cannot let the enemy know that we have it. Let some of the Undead serve as cannon fodder, make it look like we are losing heavily to the point that we need others to support us. If the Dark Temple is truly targeting Addison, then they would certainly retreat after seeing our heavy losses. This way, our losses wouldn’t be too heavy while making the others in the Resistance Army lose some. Their strength should certainly be damaged. When the Dark Temple retreats, then that would be our time to move.”

Guli and the other weren’t fools, they just haven’t experienced schemes before. But now that Zhao Hai had stated it clearly, the group quickly understood and began preparing things out.

After seeing Addison’s actions, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. He needed to take the Underworld, the implications of this goal was very heavy. Because of this, Zhao Hai needed to be careful.

Quite opposite to the Underworld, Zhao Hai wasn’t too focused on the Atlanta Plane. This was because he already gained most of what he wanted there. Things like the production method of energy converters, civilian magic armors, unique metals, etc. as long as it was publicly sold in the Atlanta Plane, Zhao Hai already had it. As for the rest, they belonged to restricted goods, and those things would take time to acquire. Therefore, Zhao Hai wasn’t too worried about the Atlanta Plane and just handed everything for Bluewell to deal with.

In fact, ever since the factory has been established, Zhao Hai didn’t look at it again. What he needed to do was just give money and leave it to Bluewell to handle.

Bluewell was very happy about this situation. He was an ambitious person and wanted a factory that was completely managed by him, but he had no money to open a factory of his own. Now that Zhao Hai had given him the opportunity, it wasn’t a mystery why Bluewell always woke up with a smile on his face.

Although Zhao Hai appeared very mysterious to Bluewell, he didn’t bother to investigate. Zhao Hai had already obtained Bluewell’s loyalty through his actions. Even if Zhao Hai told Bluewell about his true identity, Bluewell still wouldn’t betray him. A true gentleman would keep a friend’s secrets to the grave!

Zhao Hai also knew Bluewell’s situation so he had given Bluewell absolute control of the factory. Therefore, there was very little for Zhao Hai to do in the Atlanta Plane.

But the Underworld was different. There were so many things that Zhao Hai needed in the Underworld. Not to consider anything else, but those Undead, no matter how many, was needed by Zhao Hai. And then there were those plants. And lastly, people like Gimreden who liked to research. This was because these people can often create miracles. Just like Gimreden’s study on adding souls to weapons.

It was precisely because of this discovery of Kampala and Gimreden’s research that Zhao Hai decided to pay more attention to the Underworld. For Zhao Hai, the Underworld was an endless treasure trove itself, and it might become a treasure trove that belonged to him.

Guli and Jiang Zheng stayed behind while Addison left, it was useless for them to head out. Guli looked at the other regions of the Resistance Army and laughed, “Those guys think that they had schemed against us. They didn’t expect the Young Master to plot against them instead. This will make it sooner for them to become Young Master’s subordinates.”

Jiang Zheng said, “Young Master, I think we should make a move now. Almost all of the Experts in the Resistance Army are here. Their rear areas should certainly be empty. If we dispatch troops now, then their cities would be easily taken.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “It’s not the right time. We should wait until the battle ends. If we attack this time and these people knew about it, then the frontline would be plunged into chaos. When that happens, the Dark Temple would be able to use this opportunity to attack us. We don’t need to be anxious, let’s just wait.”

Jiang Zheng nodded and said, “I’ve been unfair to the Young Master. I was too impatient.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s fine. You’re idea is good, this means that you had thought about it. That’s good. Alright, you guys need to prepare as well. From what I can see, the Dark Temple is getting impatient.”

When Jiang Zheng and Guli heard Zhao Hai, they immediately nodded and left the bone carriage. They could also note that the other bank had started to get ready, they would certainly attack soon.

Zhao Hai swept the opposite bank with his spiritual force once more before he left the Space. Lizzy and Megan were already looking at the monitor, preparing to take command of the Undead to do battle.

Zhao Hai looked at the two and said, “Lizzy, Megan, don’t try too hard in commanding the Undead this time. Don’t make the enemy see that we can use battle formations. Attract the least possible suspicion from the enemy and the Resistance Army. This time, we need to show weakness. I’m afraid we have to sacrifice some of the 500 million Undead. Show weakness, understand?”

Lizzy and Megan understood what Zhao Hai wanted to do, so they gave him a nod. Zhao Hai felt relieved and after leaving a few more words, he returned to the Underworld. The Dark Temple’s attack had begun.

Chapter 1018: The Might of the Blood Spirit Beasts

Standing calmly outside the carriage, Zhao Hai was holding a cup of tea in his hand. The tea was the one produced by the Space, so its taste was quite fragrant. Also, Zhao Hai’s tool for drinking tea was very special. Instead of being called a teacup, it was much more appropriate to call it a small teapot.

This kind of small pot was specifically used for steeping tea to drink. Such a small pot can’t be used alongside a cup, so one could only drink directly from the pot. Zhao Hai liked this way of drinking before, so after the pot can be produced by the Space, he immediately had the processing machine make one for him.

In front of Zhao Hai were Guli and Jiang Zheng. The three people atop the bone carriage were stopped about two li(one kim) away from the blood river. In front of them was Addison and his Undead Army.

Zhao Hai already told Addison about his plan, and Addison also understood what Zhao Hai wanted to do. Because of this, there was no need to command the Undead. They would just have the Undead clash with the enemy head-on.

By now, the Dark Temple had already started their charge. They needed to pass the Blood River before they could make an attack.

Zhao Hai now had the chance to see the Blood Spirit Beasts. And he also wanted to know why such a river had become the biggest obstacle to the unification of the Underworld.

Under Zhao Hai’s gaze, a team of the Dark Temple’s undead began to fly across the Blood River. These Undead didn’t have any organization and just directly rushed over.

Before long, these Undead were now over the Blood River. At this moment, the Blood River’s surface seems to boil. One after another, the bubbles emerged. It seemed like the Undead were being plunged into boiling water.

Just as the fastest Undead had flown 50% of the way, flying red figures went out of the river. These figures were very fast. And like red arrows, they went to shoot towards the fiery souls.

The speed of these Undead weren’t slow, and the worst of them were at the Gold Skeleton level. But compared to these red figures, they were too slow. It didn’t take too long before a first batch of Undead were shot down.

When these Undead fell down into the blood river, they immediately plunged to the bottom, there wasn’t even a wave caused by a struggle. It was also at this time that the red arrows began to show their true self.

Just as what Addison and the others said, these Blood Spirit Beasts assume whatever form they decided to. Naturally, they were still blood red in color, but their looks were different. Their shapes ranged from tigers to wolves, octopus to squid, and in any form you could think of. They also had differing body sizes, some of them were big and some were also small.

Among these Blood Spirit Beasts, the least seen form were the humanoid ones. However, Zhao Hai could see that although these humanoid Blood Spirit Beasts were in the minority, their status seemed to be the highest. Each humanoid Blood Spirit Beast had a group of Blood Spirit Beasts surrounding them.

The Blood Spirit Beasts’ attacks were very barbaric. They didn’t hesitate to throw themselves into the remaining Undead. The remaining Undead have also begun to counter attack.

When the two sides began to exchange moves, Zhao Hai finally understood why the Blood Spirit beasts were very hard to kill. Their bodies were simply fluids, changing form at will. They could be soft like water and then hard like ice. Their attacks had very formidable range of actions.

Zhao Hai drank some tea before he opened his eyes and muttered, “No wonder this Blood River became the Dark Temple’s greatest obstacle in uniting the whole Underworld. These Blood Spirit Beasts have really good combat power. If we receive them into the Space, then we might gain another attacking method.”

Guli and Jiang Zheng were similarly looking at the fight occurring above the Blood River. As soon as they heard Zhao Hai, both of them looked over. Then Guli said, “Young Master, these Blood Spirit Beast are very strong. Moreover, it seems like they also have their own power division. These humanoid shaped beasts, for example, they have the strongest attack, similar to Crystal Skeleton level. They’re very difficult to deal with.”

Just as Guli said this, the humanoid Blood Spirit Beasts began to make a move. These humanoid Blood Spirit Beasts have different combat forms. Some of these humanoid beasts stood far away and kept waving their hands. As they waved their arms, blood would fly out of the river to attack their targets. It seems like these were magic spells that would control the blood from the Blood River.

On the other hand, there were humanoid beasts that stretched their arms into the Blood River and turning the blood into weapons. These humanoid beasts preferred to fight close-combat.

The first batch sent by the Dark Temple to traverse the Blood river weren’t strong Experts. Under the attacks of the Blood Spirit Beasts, this batch was annihilated quickly. This was something out of Zhao Hai’s expectation.

However, after these Blood Spirit Beasts killed the Undead, they immediately fell into the Blood River. Then the river resumed its silence, it was as if the Blood Spirit Beasts never appeared in the first place.

Just as the Bloody River quieted down, a huge batch of Dark Temple undead immediately flew over. Zhao Hai could also see that these Undead were higher-ranked than the previous batch.

The speed of these Undead was also faster. When they reached the middle of the Blood River, the river was still quiet, no Blood Beasts emerged. Only when the quickest Undead of this batch flew over three-quarters of the river did the Blood Spirit Beasts return.

When Zhao Hai saw this situation, he knew that the Dark Temple was playing with the Blood River’s cooldown. From what was seen, it was clear that the Blood River’s Blood Spirit Beasts needed some time before they could re-emerge. And since the Dark Temple had grasped this time difference, they immediately sent a large amount of Undead into the second batch.

Zhao Hai knew that this experience was paid for by the Dark Temple using the lives of countless Undead. But even if these Undead had rushed over, their troubles weren’t finished. This was because there was still an Undead army waiting for them on the other side.

Addison immediately commanded his Undead to overrun the Dark Temple’s Undead. It didn’t take too long before the two sides fought against each other.

Including Vampires, the Undead rarely bleed, they didn’t have any blood inside them. In this war, one couldn’t see a single splash of blood. However, the brutality of the scene was something that couldn’t be seen in any human war.

At the same time, the Dark Temple on the opposite bank was sending a constant stream of Undead to cross the river. Although the Blood Spirit Beasts were causing them trouble, it was completely impossible to block all of the Undead. Because of this, more and more Undead began to embark on the opposite shore.

Zhao Hai just sat there and didn’t make a move. The Undead they brought out this time was about 500 million. Even the Dark Temple would have a hard time killing all of these Undead.

On the other hand, Guli and the others were already anxious. This was because the Undead coming over were getting stronger and stronger.

Zhao Hai saw this and couldn’t help but smile. He waved his hand and grabbed a huge stone from his side. Then he turned this stone into a chair. Zhao Hai also put away his teapot. Now that the Dark Temple had attacked, his teapot would be too eye-catching.

Zhao Hai continued to sit outside and looked at the fight in front. Then at this time, several strong spiritual forces began sweeping in from the opposite bank. Naturally, Zhao Hai felt these spiritual forces. His brow couldn’t help but go up, he knew that the Experts of the Dark Temple were finally going in.

Zhao Hai didn’t worry as he just met those spiritual forces with his own. The spiritual forces slammed into each other in the air. After a loud bang, the Dark Mist about 100 meters away from Zhao Hai was cleared for a moment. One could see how strong the forces were just by looking at the impact.

Guli, Jiang Zheng, and the others also felt these opposing forces and also sent their own to clash with it. Although the two sides have yet to meet each other, the clash between spiritual forces was clearly felt.

After the spiritual forces of both sides clashed for several times, they all retreated. Battling with spiritual forces wasn’t a good thing. It was too dangerous, it was even more dangerous than close-combat fighting. Because of this, both sides decided to retreat and save their spiritual force.

Not long after that, the Dark Temple’s experts flew over the Blood River. The Blood Spirit Beasts simply couldn’t stop these Experts, the only thing they could do at most was cause some trouble.

The Experts coming over numbered around ten, and two of them were at Addison’s level. One of these Experts was a Skeleton, while the other was a Lich. Besides these two, the other eight people had levels not lower than Guli and Jiang Zheng.

Addison also led his men as well as Guli and Jiang Zheng to meet the enemy. Zhao Hai didn’t think about going along with them. Although the people sent by the Dark Temple were strong, Addison himself wasn’t a soft persimmon. With Addison’s strength as well as his subordinates, stopping these Experts was completely doable. There was no need for Zhao Hai to make a move.

Although it hasn’t been a long time since Zhao Hai and Addison’s fight, Zhao Hai’s current strength had already completely exceeded Addison. If they fight right now, Addison wouldn’t be able to last for more than 50 moves.

With the help of the Space, as well as the Dao Lotus, Gold Core, and Spirit Avatar, Zhao Hai’s cultivation strength was increasing every second. Although Zhao Hai didn’t deliberately practice lately, slowing his cultivation down, this didn’t mean that Zhao Hai wasn’t getting stronger. Because of this, compared to before, Zhao Hai’s strength had increased.

Also, Zhao Hai’s body had absorbed a lot of experience lately. Since he had little fighting experience in the past, Zhao Hai was almost forced to a corner than Addison. But now, after gaining battle experience, Zhao Hai’s usage of his energy had become more sophisticated. This caused Zhao Hai’s overall fighting prowess to undergo an increase. At this point, characters like Addison wouldn’t be able to clash against him. Zhao Hai would need a stronger enemy to use his strength on.

Chapter 1019: Devil Witch and Blood Bones

Because of these reasons, Zhao Hai didn’t bother to make a move. In any case, Addison was fully able to deal with the people sent by the Dark Temple. Things wouldn’t be different if Zhao Hai didn’t make a move.

Addison looked at the two Experts in front of him. He didn’t doubt Zhao Hai’s words at all, but he believed that the Dark Temple would at most send one person at his level. But now, two actually came. And more importantly, he knew about these two experts, they were famous Experts from the Dark Temple. It seems like the Dark Temple was truly prepared to suppress him and his goal of unifying the Resistance Army.

Addison looked at the two Experts and said, “Devil Witch, Blood Bones, I didn’t think that the two of you would actually team up against me. What? You think you can kill me with just the two of you?”

The Skeleton Blood Bones smiled and said, “Addison, why would you think that? This time, we’ve risked a lot to attack you, and we also know that the two of us aren’t enough to kill you. But as long as you’re seriously injured, then everything would be easy, isn’t it?”

What Blood Bones said was reasonable. The risk he was talking about pertains to the Blood River. One shouldn’t think that the Blood River’s attacks were just like the ones before. There were even more advanced Blood Spirit Beasts present. But those beasts generally wouldn’t easily go out.

After many years of experimentation, the Dark Temple had figured out some rules. If one King-level Expert passes through the river, then the river would not send a King-level Blood Spirit Beast. But if there were two or more King-level experts, the Blood River would have a chance to send King-level beasts. If two King-level Experts wanted to cross the river at the same time, then they would need to be at least ten li(5km) away from each other to not cause the Blood River to send King-level beasts to attack. This was also one of the reasons why the Resistance Army was able to defend for a long time.

Because of this situation, the Resistance Army would only need to station a King-level Expert every ten li along the river. And at the same time, these Experts wouldn’t worry about having two or more King-level experts attacking them.

Naturally, a place where two Experts attack at the same time wouldn’t necessarily encounter an attack. The chance of the Blood River sending a King-level Beast was about 50%. That was to say that Devil Witch and Blood Bones had indeed risked getting in danger in order to attack Addison. The two had a 50% chance of being attacked by six to eight Experts of the same level when crossing the river. Of course, they also had a 50% chance of going through successfully.

But from what was seen, it was very obvious that they were very lucky, they managed to get through without getting attacked.

However, if there were three King-level Experts attacking Addison, then their chances of being attacked would increase to about 80%. And if there were four King-level Experts, the chance of being attacked would become 100%. This meant that as long as there were four King-level Experts above the Blood River, they would definitely be attacked by King-level Blood Spirit Beasts.

It was because of all these reasons added together that Blood Bones said that they were risking a lot when attacking Addison. But two King-level Experts were still not enough to kill another King-level Expert, only enough to seriously injure. Therefore, Addison wasn’t too afraid of the two.

Addison might be seriously injured after fighting these two and he might need to recuperate for a long time, but don’t forget that Addison can return to the Space. As long as he returns, he can ask the Space to give him treatment. Addison could reset his state at any time, naturally this made him unafraid of any injury.

Addison looked at Blood Bone and Devil Witch before he coldly snorted and said, “You Dark Temple fellows really like to plot and scheme. You don’t want me to unify the Resistance Army? Then let me tell you, I will certainly have the entire Resistance Army under my control.”

The Lich coldly replied, “You actually still think that you can live properly after today.”

After saying that, the Lich’s body slowly faded before it blended into the Dark Fog. On the other hand, Blood Bone’s crystal-like skeleton changed color and turned blood red. Then on Blood Bone’s left hand, a thick greatsword appeared. On the hilt of the sword was an image of a malicious ghost. It looked like it could take a bite out of anyone at any time.

This greatsword was also blood red. The body of this sword was very thick, giving it a very heavy aura. It’s handle was very long, enough for one to use both of their hands to hold it. One could see at a glance that Blood Bones’ attacking power was something not to be underestimated.

The weapon of an Undead generally came from their own body. This function had been an instinct imbued onto the souls of the Undead. As long as an Undead reaches Silver-rank, they could make a weapon out of their own body. The hardness of this weapon would be directly proportional to their rank.

After Blood Bones took his weapon out, he smirked and charged towards Addison. And this attack also acted as a signal to the ther high-rank Undead to launch an attack against Addison’s men. There were only two people among the group who didn’t move, and they were Guli and Jiang Zheng.

Although Guli and Jiang Zheng had yet to be considered to be equal to King-level characters such as Addison, they were already half a step away from reaching that level. The reason why they didn’t move was because they were preparing to deal with the second King-level expert going after Addison.

One shouldn’t be complacent upon seeing that the Lich had disappeared. In fact, this was one of the moves the Lich race use. They would vanish into the Dark Mist and only appear when they attack, until then, nobody would know where they were. Because of this, not only were the Lich formidable Mages, they were also terrifying Assassins in the presence of the Dark Mist.

Since the Lich were immune to any physical damage, they were able to stealthily blend into the Dark Mist to attack their enemies. But because of their physical immunity, their ability to attack had also been taken away. Therefore, they could only command the Dark Mist or use magic attacks. But even so, their enemies wouldn’t dare to underestimate them.

Addison already took his snake sword out and clashed with Blood Bones. Since both were very familiar with fighting and also had the same strength, they didn’t go all out despite clashing multiple times.

Addison needed to make some room for himself to counter the Lich while Blood Bones needed to make room for himself to defend against Guli and Jiang Zheng. After all, Guli and Jiang Zheng’s strength have also been noted by the Dark Temple.

Blood Bones was also wondering about Kampala who was always with Guli and Jiang Zheng. It was because of Kampala’s absence that Blood Bones needed to be more careful. Kampala was also a Lich and was able to hide in the Dark Mist.

Zhao Hai kept sitting in his stone chair without the intention of entering the fight. Even the Lich hiding the Dark Mist wasn’t a threat to his current strength.

Devil Witch and Blood Bones were able to note Zhao Hai’s presence. After all, Zhao Hai didn’t deliberately hide his figure as he just sat there and spectated the entire battle. Zhao Hai’s lack of action made him even more noticeable. Everyone was fighting while Zhao Hai was sitting alone. It would be difficult for anyone to not notice Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about any of these thoughts. However, this temperament made him look very arrogant. This attracted the ire of Devil Witch. The Lich didn’t attack Addison and instead slowly went over to Zhao Hai.

His speed was very slow, seemingly afraid of making too big of a move and alert Zhao Hai. This was also another characteristic of the Lich. Although they can integrate into the Dark Mist, their bodies weren’t one with the Dark Mist. Therefore, if they make a sudden movement, they would cause the Dark Mist to be disturbed, making other people discover their trail. Because of this, the Lich moved very slowly in the Dark Mist.

When Zhao Hai saw that Devil Witch was heading towards him, he couldn’t help but smile. Then he immediately told Guili and Jiang Zheng about Devil Witch’s location through his mind.

Guli and Jiang Zheng were now equal to Zhao Hai’s summoned creatures. Because of this, Zhao Hai can directly talk to them using his mind. He used this method to relay to them the exact location of the Lich.

Although Guli and Jiang Zheng were known for their physical attacks, this didn’t mean that they don’t have any attacks that use magic. Upon reaching their current level, they were also able to freely convert their attacks between physical and magical attributes.

Guli’s weapon was his double-edged sword while Jiang Zheng had his nails. After the two received Zhao Hai’s instructions, they immediately attacked Devil Witch.

Devil Witch was planning on attacking Zhao Hai, but he didn’t expect Guli and Jiang Zheng to discover his location. Moreover, it seems like their positioning was very accurate. When he saw their attack, Devil Witch felt a sense of danger. The Lich immediately made a strange sound before he casted a magic shield in front of him and at the same time dodging to the side.

But because of this movement, Guli and Jiang Zheng were even more able to chase Devil Witch around. Addison and Blood Bones were also able to notice this situation. When Addison saw Guli and Jiang Zheng’s action, he immediately knew that it was Zhao Hai making a move. On the other hand, Blood Bones was puzzled. How could Guli and Jiang Zheng sense Devil Witch’s location? Then he began to think about Kampala, he might be the one who told Guli and Jiang Zheng about Devil Witch.

Actually, the people in the Underworld knew that the best counter to a Lich was another Lich. This was because when two Lich were stealthed in the Dark Mist, both of them would be able to sense each other’s location. Because of this, a Lich was the best means to find another Lich. And because of this knowledge, Blood Bones thought that Kampala was the one to discover Devil Witch.

But now that this happened, Blood Bones began to worry. This was because Devil Witch was now being pursued by Guli and Jiang Zheng, but Kampala has yet to emerge. This caused Kampala to be a hidden thorn that Blood Bones needed to be careful of.

Chapter 1020: The Great Demon King’s Request

In a battle between Experts, once one side gets the momentum, then the other would start to feel pressured. In this case, the winner and the loser could be seen at a glance. At this time, Addison’s attacking rhythm was doing smoothly while Blood Bones can only passively defend.

Although Addison was in the upper hand, the same thing cannot be said about his subordinates. It must be said that the strength of Addison’s men weren’t bad, and they weren’t that far off from Guli and Jiang Zheng. However, the people they were up against were on Guli and Jiang Zheng’s level. And even if they had the numerical advantage, they fell short when it came to quality.

And if we go down by another rank, Addison’s Undead were even worse. Even if there were quite a lot of them, the area they needed to defend was quite big in comparison to the amount of Undead that were coming. And although they had surrendered to the Space, they weren’t commanded by Lizzy and Megan. These Undead didn’t have any understanding with regards to battle formations. Therefore, they could only do primal battles without any proper control.

In this case, upon facing the seemingly unending Dark Temple Undead, it didn’t take long for them to be on the back foot.

Zhao Hai still didn’t make a move. They had already reached an agreement about this matter. Zhao Hai also felt that there were a lot of people on both sides of the Blood River using their spiritual force to check the situation in this place. At this time, Zhao Hai had already used a portion of his mental power to shroud himself, making others feel like Zhao Hai was just a piece of stone.

This wasn’t a difficult thing for Zhao Hai. After all, the Space had a lot of elements in it, unlike the Underworld where the Dark Element was the most prevalent. Zhao Hai could just take some earth element energy from the Space and wrap himself with it. If he was scanned with spiritual force, then the others would only see a rock.

Zhao Hai knew that the Dark Temple wouldn’t put too much pressure on the other regions. This was because their only target this time was Addison and his Undead. They just wanted to damage Addison’s vitality. As for the other defensive regions, the Dark Temple would just make sure that they wouldn’t be able to send support to Addison’s region.

But this was also where the Resistance Army wanted Addison to be. They planned failing to send any reinforcements for Addison, and the Dark Temple provided them with an excuse. This allowed the others in the Resistance Army to take advantage of the situation and back down without losing face. In dealing with Addison’s matter, it seems like the Dark Temple and the Resistance Army had reached an unexpected understanding.

Zhao Hai had already anticipated this result. He also allowed the Dark Temple and Resistance Army do this. Addison’s advancement was too quick, causing the Dark Temple and the Resistance Army to be vigilant. Now that the Resistance Army has united, this caused Addison’s unification plan to decelerate. But this battle was actually a good opportunity to make the Resistance Army and Dark Temple feel relieved.

It can be said that except Addison, Guli, and Jiang Zheng, Zhao Hai was prepared to sacrifice the other Undead. Only when these people die would the other parties feel relaxed regarding Addison.

The fight was getting more and more brutal. Of the eight other experts that Blood Bones and Devil Witch brought, only four of them were left. And of the 40 other Experts that Addison had, only about 20 remained. At the same time, of the 500 million Undead that the Space had converted, 300 million remain in the battlefield. Although there weren’t any much blood in the battleground, broken bones and desecrated corpses littered everywhere. These were the Skeletons and Zombies that perished in the battle.

Fluttering around the battlefield were massive amounts of fiery souls. These souls were floating above the remains of the Undead. But for the fiery souls near the blood river, all of them were sucked into the river. Who knows if they were being eaten by the Blood Spirit Beasts or being made into new Blood Spirit Beasts. Fiery souls were also continuing to slowly flow towards the river.

Of course, how could Zhao Hai let this opportunity off. He waved his hand and stealthily took the fiery souls into the Space. The levels of the fiery souls weren’t low, he might be able to upgrade his Undead using these in the future.

Addison and Blood Bones were still in battle, with Addison still having the upper hand. But after a long battle, Bloody Bones was almost certain that Kampala wasn’t present, so he began to exert his full effort. However, Addison already gained the momentum. For Bloody Bones to try to shift the situation would be almost impossible. The strength of the two were fairly even, it would be difficult for Blood Bones to go back from being at a disadvantage.

Guli and Jiang Zheng’s battle against Devil Witch was also doing well. The two sides were at a tie, with Guli and Jiang Zheng having a little bit of an advantage. However, it was still impossible for them to deal with Devil Witch in a short time.

Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about them. The Undead had more endurance compared to other people. From what can be seen, the battle should last for a couple of days more.

After seeing that there wouldn’t be that much change soon, Zhao Hai’s figure flashed as he entered the Space. Zhao Hai was certain that the Resistance Army wouldn’t let Addison die. This was because of Addison’s strength. If Addison died here, then the one who would benefit the most would be the Dark Temple. The Resistance Army didn’t want to lose an Expert, they only want to suppress Addison. Because of this, Zhao Hai was assured that Addison would be safe.

When he entered the Space, Zhao Hai saw that Laura and the others weren’t looking at the battle on the monitor. Instead, they went to the Hell Space to see the bone fields.

Currently there were a lot of dark-attributed plants being grown in the bone fields. Naturally, most of these were bone armors, followed by bone plants.

Although they didn’t know what bone plants could do, the most important thing was their essence. Cai’er knew this so she chose to plant a lot of them as well.

Laura and the others were full of enthusiasm while looking at the bone field. They were still chatting when Zhao Hai arrived. Zhao Hai looked at the group and said, “What are you chatting about? Did you see Addison’s fight?”

Laura and the others turned their heads and saw Zhao Hai. Lizzy pouted her lips and said, “What is there to watch? From what I can see, the battle would still take a couple of days. It’s too boring to watch them all the time.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’m quite bored as well, so I came back. Why are you here? Don’t you dislike the environment?” To be honest, apart from the Undead, very few people liked the Hell Space. Even Zhao Hai was the same.

Laura smiled and said, “It’s nothing, we just wanted to see what the bone fields are like. We want to see it for ourselves so that if we find fields like these in the future, we can take them to the Space.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, these kinds of things can only be met and not always available. There’s nothing else to look at here, let’s go back.” Laura and the others nodded and followed Zhao Hai back to the villa. Then Zhao Hai took the group and headed to Wild Dragon Island to see how Gimreden and the others were doing.

Although Gimreden was doing magic formation research, his direction was completely different from Kampala. His research still hinges on joining fiery souls and other items, not just pure magic formation research.

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything about this matter. Zhao Hai already told Gimreden that he would give the Lich absolute freedom when it came to research.

Gimreden was quite delighted with his current situation. Whatever he needed was being provided here. The test materials were also high-grade goods made of glass, which was easier to use than his apparatus back in the Underworld.

Most importantly, his research included a lot of other subjects. If he studied these things by himself, then who knows how many years it would take him. In Wild Dragon island, however, there were a lot of other Lich who has worked or were working in different topics. And with the data the others managed to get, Gimreden saved a lot of years of effort. This kind of research sharing was something that Gimreden welcomed the most.

Besides these, Gimreden also found other Lich who were interested in his study, allowing him to establish his own laboratory. At this time, Gimreden was high-spirited and quite motivated, as well as incomparably happy. Zhao Hai felt relief upon seeing this situation. Everything was good as long as Gimreden and the other Lich enjoyed their lives here.

After that, Zhao Hai went to visit the Demon Space. It’s been a while since Zhao Hai and the others visited the Demons. As soon as the group arrived in the Demon Space, all of them couldn’t help but think that they had come to the wrong place. Instead of being the Demon Space, it was more appropriate to call it an Elven Forest.

Zhao Hai discovered that the Demon Realm’s residents had already gone to the point of insanity when it came to plants. In their eyes, any plant was a treasure. Because of this, the Demon Realm was full of plants. Zhao Hai didn’t expect them to get this crazy. Zhao Hai almost couldn’t see the buildings among the multitude of plants covering them. Even the houses of the Demons were filled with vines, but they still looked simple and natural.

Zhao Hai was left not speechless. But after a while, Zhao Hai didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. Not only the commoner Demons were doing this, even the Great Demon King’s royal palace had this appearance.

When Zhao Hai went to the Great Demon King’s palace, the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King were currently working on paperwork. They still needed to do their job. Of those entering the Space, only the Demons made Zhao Hai feel the most assured. This was because Zhao Hai discovered that the Demons were the most united group. Yes there were a lot of conflicts back in the Demon Realm, but those fights were because of land. The various races needed to live. But inside the Space, there was no need for them to fight for land. Therefore, all of them were living very well, nobody went to war. Although the Demons still couldn’t shake of the ferociousness in their nature, they didn’t fight with anyone. The crime rate of the Demons was very low.

Zhao Hai was very surprised with this result. He didn’t really expect it. The Demons had always been the synonym for aggression and evil. It was even said that they weren’t easy to get along with.

When the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King saw Zhao Hai arrive, they immediately welcomed him into the room. At the same time, they had people prepare some food and wine. Zhao Hai looked at the two and could see that they had gained some weight. It seems like they were living much better compared to before.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile and said, “Good. It seems like you two had been living well. You’re putting on more weight.”

The Great Demon King laughed and said, “This is because of Mister’s blessing. We never even dreamed of being in our current situation.”

Zhao Hai looked at them and smiled, “Alright, let’s move on from the small talk. Your Majesty, I came here to ask you something. It seems like the Demons have taken a liking to plants. Do you have talented Potions Masters now?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the Great Demon King’s eyes couldn’t help but shine as he replied, “Does Mister want to recruit Potion Masters to be your subordinates? Good, good, the Demons have a lot Potion Masters. Moreover, their understanding regarding plants is very deep. They can set out at any time.”

Zhao Hai replied, “Is that so? Then that’s fantastic. You can choose 100 people for me to bring to Wild Dragon Island. I want them to research Potions. If they’re interested in other matters, they can also do it there.”

The Great Demon King quickly nodded and said, “Mister, rest assured, 100 people is not a problem. Not to say 100, even 1000 or 10 thousand people would be fine. But Mister, I also have something to ask you. I hope you can help us with this.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “There’s no need to be polite. Just tell me.”

The Great Demon King said, “Mister, you should know that the Demon Race has a very powerful clan. The Demon Ogres aren’t smart people, but they have great talent when it came to battles. Because of this, making them learn potion making is very difficult. However, there are some Demon Ogres who are interested in smelting. I hope Mister can provide a good teacher for them.”

When Zhao Hai heard the Great Demon King, he couldn’t help but stare. Then he began to get lost in his thoughts. He didn’t oppose the idea of the Demons learning how to smelt. Conversely, Zhao Hai was very glad to help the Demon Ogres. However, the Great Demon King’s request made Zhao Hai think of another matter.

Currently, there were a lot of races in the Space. And each race had their own specialty. But even so, not everybody in a race liked to do what they were good at. For example, there were Elves who didn’t’ want to make art, they wanted to do other things.

But if they depend on their race’s resources, their development would be very slow. Moreover, it was easy for these people to go down a wrong path. One shouldn’t underestimate the wisdom of these people, a lot of their ideas had been helpful to Karen’s research.

Zhao Hai wanted his people to live a good life, but what he did was just provide them with things that they would need and want. Zhao Hai failed to look at the matter of their education.

Zhao Hai was like a kind fisherman. He wanted to help others so he gave them some fish he caught. However, he failed to teach these people how to fish, and this wasn’t a very wise move.

Chapter 1021: Inter-Space Academy Alliance

Don’t just give people fish, teach them how to fish instead!

These words had been said since ancient times, but Zhao Hai was only able to think about it at this moment. He had been continuously failing to see the educational problems of the people in the Space.

This problem didn’t refer to the teachings of the people inside the Space. In fact, the Space made education mandatory in all of the races. Therefore, the problem wasn’t in the main education sector.

The problem that Zhao Hai had thought of was the issue of the level of education. Things like magic formations of the Atlanta Plane being higher compared to the Ark Continent. They are the same magic formations, but one was at a higher level than the other.

There were already a lot of races inside the Space, but the degree of civilization differed from race to race, their development weren’t the same. If this development continues, then the disparity would be wider and wider. This wasn’t what Zhao Hai wanted to see, he wanted all of the races to develop at a balanced rate.

Zhao Hai can bluntly say that the most powerful military, magic, research, and overall quality of life was in Wild Dragon island. The best teachers could also be seen there. This was because all of the talents of the various races had been concentrated there.

When his thoughts reached this point, Zhao Hai’s eyes shone, he thought about an idea. If he made Cai’er take the most essential things about each subject and then made them into books to distribute to the different Spaces, wouldn’t civilizations throughout the Space be balanced?

There has yet to be academies in other Spaces. If people could go to these academies and learn, wouldn’t that be better? And if talents were found, Zhao Hai could take them to Wild Dragon Island for further study. This way, there would be more and more talents in Wild Dragon Island. The impact on this to the future would be very huge!

While Zhao Hai was thinking about an Inter-Space Academy Alliance. The Great Demon King on the side couldn’t help but get anxious. He didn’t think that his proposal would make Zhao Hai think for a very long time.

The Great Demon King was truly independent when he entered the Space, he will bargain back and forth with Zhao Hai. But now it had changed. After staying inside the Space, he had already favored the Space and wanted to give benefit to Zhao Hai. Proposing for the Demon Ogres to study blacksmithing wasn’t an excessive request. This was because the Great Demon King knew about the Dwarves in the Space. Zhao Hai can just have the Dwarves teach the Demon Ogres how to smith, there was no need to think much about it.

But now, after seeing Zhao Hai falling deep into thought, the Great Demon King couldn’t help but get nervous. He was afraid that he had touched Zhao Hai’s hidden bottomline. He was afraid that Zhao Hai would get offended.

On the other hand, Laura and the other knew that Zhao Hai must have thought about something significant, thus explaining his current state. Laura turned her head to the Great Demon King and said, “Your Majesty, there’s no need to worry. Brother Hai is just thinking about something. It isn’t because of the Demon Ogres, you can rest assured.”

The Great Demon King felt relieved when he heard this. At this time, Zhao Hai had consolidated his thoughts as he looked up to the Great Demon King and said, “Your Majesty’s proposal is very good. I just thought about a certain issue. Currently, the Space has a lot of advanced things. No matter magic or battle qi, both are advanced. However, everyone has been independently studying. Because of this, the levels of each race is uneven. Your Majesty’s request reminded me that we can make a collaboration between different Spaces, unifying the educational material so that we can reach the same standard. And because of that, we can make the teachers more focused. For example, the Dwarves are naturally best for blacksmithing. So those who want to study blacksmithing, no matter which race, would be able to study from the Dwarves. As for other things, like the Demons, you are skilled in warfare and fighting, so you can instruct other races on that regard. In the same way, the Elves can teach art, the other Space had their own specialties as well. With this, the attainment of the people inside the Space would be unified. What do you think?”

Although Zhao Hai said a lot of things, all present here were wise people, so they were able to immediately understand Zhao Hai’s point. Those present in the room couldn’t help but blink, then they nodded at the same time. The Great Demon King was very happy as he said, “Mister’s idea is very good. Except for battle tactics, the Demon Space is really lacking in other aspects. Back in the Demon Realm, even if you wanted to learn, you wouldn’t be able to. Now that there is a chance, there is no way that people would ignore it.”

Laura also nodded as she added, “Also, there’s no need to worry about advanced teaching manuals, we have already too many in our hands. The researches of the Lich wouldn’t be wasted. There are still some Spaces that don’t have an established magic theory. We can make books for them to learn from. This would increase their magic and martial skills.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Right, as long as we can raise their levels, then the overall state of the Space would improve. Everyone working together is much better than us doing our own things. However, we can’t take subjects that are too advanced. Even if we do take them out, the others wouldn’t be able to understand it. We’ll wait for a bit. After all the schools are united, then we can choose some talented students from these schools and have them study in Wild Dragon Island. After they learn, they can go back and teach the others. This way, the level of education on all the Spaces would slowly reach Wild Dragon Island’s level. This would make the Space develop even faster!”

“Good, good. This idea is good. Hahahaha. Fantastic!” When the Great Demon King heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but stand out and stomp the ground from excitement. Everyone could see how motivated he was.

There was a reason why the Great Demon King was so motivated. Although they didn’t need to worry about food and clothing after entering the Space, the Great Demon King discovered that the Demons had started to forget about a lot of things. At this time, the Demons didn’t think about making progress since they could no longer be hungry. The Great Demon King was worried about this situation.

A nation that does not think will be doomed to be eliminated. The Great Demon King was very clear about this statement. He was worried that the Demons would continue to develop this way and would one day be driven out of the Space by Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai’s proposition was actually very important for the Demons since this happened to solve this very matter. When the Great Demon King discovered the current state of the Demons, he immediately tried to find a solution. He wanted to enhance the overall state of the Demon Race. After some investigation, he discovered that it wasn’t the fact that the Demons had lost their ambition, it was actually because their educational level couldn’t  allow them to progress.

Back in the Demon Realm, the Demon Ogres deemed strength to be the most important thing. This was because of the constant danger they encounter on a daily basis. If one doesn’t learn how to fight, then they would be courting death. However, now that there was no longer any danger inside the Space, their skills on warfare were now useless. Now there were a lot of Demon Ogres who wanted to study blacksmithing. Although blacksmithing needed high technical skills, the most important thing to a blacksmith was their strength. And strength wasn’t something that the Demon Ogres lacked. Althuogh they weren’t that stupid, the Demon Ogres just weren’t interested in potion making.

If this was on Earth, then even if the Demon Ogres didn’t want to study magic formations or potions, then they would have to endure. Otherwise, they would have no money to survive with.

However, the same cannot be true for the Space. Even if you cannot learn these things, then you would still be able to survive. Because of this, others can just live their days eating and practically doing nothing. With this, it’s natural for there to be no ambition that would bloom.

The Demon Realm had no research about other disciplines, so it was almost impossible to teach the Demons about things that they were interested in. Even magic formations and potion making would have to be studied from books. Their educational level was much worse compared to the Goblins and the people from the Ark Continent.

But now, Zhao Hai had solved this problem. The Demons can now choose what they want to study. Even if they cannot learn it in the Demon Space, the other Spaces can teach them. And most importantly, Zhao Hai’s plan had a certain hint of competition. One shouldn’t forget that the most outstanding students would be sent to Wild Dragon Island for further studies. This was definitely great for the people inside the Space.

In fact, all races inside the Space were now aware about Wild Dragon Island’s existence. Even the Divines who had a grudge with Zhao Hai knew about it. This was also what Zhao Hai wanted, to make Wild Dragon Island the most sacred location inside the Space. This would also give him some advantages in his rule of the Space.

Actually, the number of Divines who hated Zhao Hai has been dwindling. It can be said that they had already accepted their fate, there was no use if they kept their hatred. This place was now where they would live and die, they were completely under Zhao Hai’s hand. Not accepting their current situation would just be detrimental to their future.

Additionally, they were able to eat and drink properly inside the Space, there was even no taxation. The commoner Divines began to discover that their living standards didn’t worsen, in fact, it was even better compared to before.

In any place, a commoner’s life was never easy. Take the Divine Realm for example. The Divines wanted to wage war and conquer other planes. However, they would need logistical supplies to do so. Soldiers need food, weapons, armor, all of these costs resources. And where would the resources come from? Part of it would be supplied by the vassal races while the other part would be shouldered by the commoners. It was precisely because of this that the commoner Divines were taxed, and this tax wasn’t low.

However, there was no such issue inside the Space. Nobody came to collect tax. Every work they did was all for their own benefit. This was a great motivating force.

Chapter 1022: Unexpected Benefit?

The commoner Divines were quick to discover the advantages of the Space. Although it seems like nobody was managing the Space, it was actually bound by certain laws. And the laws of the Space were complete. Breaking a certain law had a certain punishment to it. The most severe punishment being confined to the closed room.

That dark, closed room became a nightmare to all lawbreakers inside the Space. Nobody wanted to go there, even strong Experts. Upon entering that closed room, one would rather die than continue on. Because of this punishment, nobody inside the Space dared to break the laws.

And such a restraint not only made people do less crime, it also helped erase the hatred in their hearts. Since there were less conflict around, the environment became peaceful, making people eager to work harder. In this case, they would forget the hatred and would instead look towards the future. They would start to yearn for the time where they can live a much better life.

This was the situation inside the Space. If one was holding on to their hatred, then they would spend their time cultivating, only to find out one day that their neighbors didn’t cultivate. Instead, what the neighbor did was work hard every day in order to exchange for things that could make their lives better. Meanwhile, you, who was cultivating, was only working to get by. In this case, would your heart feel fine? Of course not. Therefore, you would have to work hard for yourself and make your life better. When this happens, the hatred inside your heart would slowly fade away.

The Divines also discovered that in some areas where people were behaving, books started to appear on their churches. Meanwhile, for those areas with people who had vengeful hearts, no books ever appeared.

This segregation made the Divines even more behaved. After all, it was eventually be just a hatred of their ancestors. As for the children, this hatred had nothing to do with them.

The reason why the Divines became aware of Wild Dragon Island was precisely these books. To let the Divines have a better understanding of the Space, Zhao Hai provided them with these specially-made books. Inside these books were things about the Buda Clan, the Ark Continent, and the war between the Ark Continent and the Divines. These were materials that made the Divines understand why they reached their current situation.

It can be said that these books were very successful. One must know that the Divines inside the Space weren’t only composed of Taurus Divines, there were also Divines from the other continents. After reading the books, the other Divines shifted their hatred towards the Taurus Divines. Some even shifted their hatred to the dead Supreme Elders.

People were like this. Once they find out that their enemy was too strong and that there was no way to take revenge, then they would find another target for their ire. Zhao Hai seized this psychology to shift the hatred towards the Taurus Divines.

After discussing the matter of the academy with the Great Demon King for some time, Zhao Hai and the others returned to the Space’s villa. After that, Zhao Hai had Cai’er arrange a set of standard books before going to each Space to talk about the academy with the other races.

Every race inside the Space, excluding the Divine Dwarves, Thunder Clan, Winged Pegasus, and Barbarians, had been inside the Space for some time. They had already been slowly influenced by the Space. Even if they didn’t completely change their thoughts, at the very least they wouldn’t dislike Zhao Hai.

As long as they don’t dislike Zhao Hai, then these people wouldn’t oppose to the establishment of the Academies. After all, these academies would greatly benefit their descendants.

While Addison and the others were battling it out in the Underworld, the Space was actually thriving well. Naturally, since Zhao Hai was establishing the academies, he wouldn’t forget about the Undead. At this time, there were a lot of Undead living inside the Space. In addition, some of these Undead had intelligence no worse than ordinary people. Because of this, Zhao Hai was prepared to make them into their own independent race.

Raising the status of the Undead was Zhao Hai’s example to the other people inside the Space. Since the Undead were his most loyal subjects, then Zhao Hai would improve their status. This would inform all of those inside the Space that as long as they were loyal to Zhao Hai, their status could improve. If the Undead could do it, then they could as well!

This sounded absurd, and it caused some resistance inside the Space. Both the Ark Space and the Demon Space didn’t lack Dark Mages. These Mages had always regarded the Undead as their slaves. Now that Zhao Hai had changed the Undead’s status, it caused quite the amount of ripples on all the races.

But what made Zhao Hai surprised the most was the impact on this decision to the Undead. The Undead were very grateful about this matter and some even directly evolved upon hearing the news.

At first, Zhao Hai couldn’t understand why these Undead evolved. Later on, after further analysis by Cai’er and Laura, they were able to guess the reason. This was because of the gratitude that these Undead felt. Because of this gratitude, the Undead wanted to be able to do more things for Zhao Hai. And in order to do this, the only way was to evolve!

This result made Zhao Hai speechless. But he soon understood that he had always underestimated the wisdom of the Undead inside the Space. He also underestimated their potential.

Zhao Hai had the absolute loyalty of the Undead. And some of Undead developed intellect and were able to have thoughts of their own. Although these Undead didn’t have any regrets about being treated as a slave and they just wanted to contribute to their master, it was still quite normal for the Undead to just slack off.

However, after the news that Zhao Hai was elevating their status, the hearts of these Undead were moved. The Undead who were loyal to Zhao Hai became even more loyal. They wanted to do more for Zhao Hai, they wanted to become stronger. This was completely different from before when Zhao Hai told them to cultivate. This time, it was on their own decision that they wanted to get more powerful. A lot of Undead who had great potential had their strength immediately soar!

After knowing this result, Zhao Hai didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. He didn’t think that his decision would actually birth an unexpected benefit. It was truly surprising.

Zhao Hai used seven days to handle the matters inside the Space. Actually, Zhao Hai didn’t need to spend seven days for this matter. The textbook matters were handed over to Cai’er. However, Cai’er wanted things to be thorough, so she had Zhao Hai look into the specific situation inside each Space. After that, Zhao Hai had to take already made manuals and had them analyzed by the Universal Scanner. The scanner would help Zhao Hai make the most suitable book for each Space. Although this cost Zhao Hao some gold coins, Zhao Hai didn’t care. He just wanted to finish things properly.

After using the scanner to find suitable teaching materials for the various Spaces, Cai’er used the processing machine to replicate the first set of books and mass produce them. With this, the issue with teaching material has been solved.

As for constructing the various academies in each Space, Zhao Hai didn’t have to worry about it. This was because some Space already had their own academies. And even if the Dwarves didn’t have one, after hearing Zhao Hai’s proposal, they can build their own.

In seven days, the basic framework for the Inter-Space Academy Alliance has been built. Now that Zhao Hai had some breathing room, he returned to the Underworld.

The war in the Underworld had actually ended five days ago. Just like Zhao Hai expected, Addison’s side had suffered heavy losses. Aside from Addison, Guli, and Jiang Zheng, of the forty experts, only 16 of them were left. And as for the 500 million Undead army, only 100 million remained. In other people’s view, Addison’s vitality was severely injured. Wanting to return to his previous state would take who knows how long.

Now that both the Resistance Army and the Dark Temple were relieved, the war came to an end. Addison didn’t gain anything from this battle. Blood Bones and Devil Witch, whom the Dark Temple sent, were severely injured and were forced to retreat. It can be said that in the battle between high-ranks, Addison won.

Addison also did what Zhao Hai instructed him to do. After returning to his territory, Addison stopped expanding and instead began to act low-key, going full defensive.

Upon seeing Addison’s actions, the Resistance Army felt relief once more. They wanted to see this result, they didn’t want Addison to keep expanding. A behaved Addison was the best. But the cities under Addison’s hands were still difficult to take back. After all, Addison wasn’t injured this time. Being a King-level expert, nobody would dare to nonchalantly challenge Addison and take his cities.

Although Zhao Hai has been inside the Space in these past few days, he was still concerned about the Underworld. After seeing Addison’s arrangements, Zhao Hai began to feel relieved. He wanted to see this result. However, it wasn’t the time to unify the Resistance Army. The Resistance Army was still vigilant against Addison. An attack at this time wouldn’t be very successful.

Because of this, Zhao Hai had Addison act low-key. His surveillance on other cities also went low-key. This way, the people from the Resistance Army would be relieved of Addison’s withdrawal. When the Resistance Army finally lowers their guard, then Zhao Hai would make a move.

When Zhao Hai returned to the Underworld, he discovered that Addison’s cities had more Undead coming to visit. Although these Undead seems to be doing business, they were actually exploring the entire city. However, they didn’t cause any disturbance, they were just observing. Naturally, the whereabouts of these Undead couldn’t be hidden. After all, all of the city’s residents were Zhao Hai’s subordinates. Zhao Hai also knew that these visiting Undead were spies from the other forces in the Resistance Army.

Chapter 1023: Witness This Historical Moment

Addison was currently waiting for Zhao Hai in Three Saint City. The reason he didn’t return to the Space was because he still needed to assume personal command. Also, post-war matters needs to be taken care of.

Addison’s decision was also a deterrence for the Resistance Army. If Addison, Guli, and Jiang Zheng were separated, then the Resistance Army were most likely to group up and attack the three. In the eyes of the army, as long as they kill the three and acquire their fiery souls, then they would be able to make three other Experts by relying on those fiery souls.

The was also the reason why the Resistance Army wouldn’t allow Addison to die under the Dark Temple’s hand. They didn’t want his fiery soul to get into the hands of the Dark Temple. If this happens, a new Expert would emerge from the Dark Temple. However, if the Resistance Army can kill Addison themselves, then they would be the make an Expert who wasn’t as ambitious.

This wasn’t just Zhao Hai’s wild guess, it was likely to be a fact. Addison’s ambition and strength was dreaded by the others in the Resistance Army. Because of this, they were even more eager to kill Addison.

They had offended Addison greatly this time. They also knew that as long as Addison wasn’t a fool, he would definitely know that he was plotted against. With Addison’s temper, he would not let this matter go. Instead of Addison attacking them in the future, then they might as well attack him first. This way, they would not wait to be killed.

And since Addison had thought about this point, he decided to remain in Three Saint City together with Guli and Jiang Zheng. Those who wanted to attack them would have to think hard about their decision.

When he arrived at Three Saint City, Zhao Hai discovered that the place wasn’t doing too well. There were a lot of new Undead present here. Not only were these Undead scouting, some of them had also become very arrogant. It can be said that they were getting rampant while Addison was holding back.

After seeing that Zhao Hai had arrived, Addison and the others immediately gathered in Zhao Hai’s tower. Zhao Hai looked at Addison, the Vampire King’s expression wasn’t very good. Naturally, he wasn’t injured, instead Addison was seething.

When Zhao Hai saw Addison’s expression, he immediately knew what he was thinking. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Addison, what’s wrong? Feeling very angry?”

Addison snorted and replied, “Young Master, I’ve been really thinking of killing those fellows now. Look at their arrogant expressions, when have I become a target to bully?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You three fools. I want you to go low-key, but this didn’t mean that you have to be completely passive. Take this situation, for example, if you don’t teach them a lesson, they will become more and more arrogant. Moreover, it’s possible they would suspect that you’re planning something big. Therefore, what you need to do is kill people in order to show that you still have your power and prestige. As long as you don’t expand, the others wouldn’t make a move.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Addison stared for a moment, then his two eyes shone. He looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, please wait for a moment.” Then he flew out the window. Before long, sounds of rumbling was heard in the city. Naturally, Addison was making mincemeat out of those arrogant fellows.

Zhao Hai looked at Addison’s actions and smiled, he didn’t stop him. Just as he said, if Addison made himself look weak, then the Resistance Army might suspect something. Therefore, Addison needed to balance how he exerts his prestige.

Addison showing his strength would make the others think twice. As long as Addison didn’t expand, then the Resistance Army could still feel relieved.

It didn’t take long before Addison flew back. His expression was now looking much better. Then he bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “I’ve been unfair to Young Master. I cannot complete the matters you arranged.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, he waved his hand and said, “Forget it, you actually did quite well. I cannot blame you. You haven’t experienced this before so it’s understandable that you don’t know what to do. Sit, I need to discuss something with you.”

After the group had sat down, Zhao Hai calmly said, “Our plan has been successful. We’ve already made the Dark Temple and the Resistance Army lower their guards. What we need to do now is to find an opportunity to dispatch troops.”

Addison nodded, “By looking at the present situation, the Resistance Army has been fooled by us. And the Dark Temple shouldn’t be making an attack soon after. The next few days should be appropriate for us to make a move.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Good. Then we’ll use these days to conquer the Resistance Army. As for now, since the two sides had just retreated, I won’t be able to collect some Blood Spirit Beasts, so I’ll just map out the Resistance Army’s territory. After that, we can send troops to each city at any time. Not only would we catch them off guard, they also wouldn’t be able to spread the news easily.”

Addison and the others nodded. They had some understanding regarding the Space, but they still knew too little. So in this aspect, they would have to listen to Zhao Hai.

Addison looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, so what should we do right now?”

Zhao Hai thought about it and said, “We don’t have to do anything else. You just have to keep your cities in check. If some people stir any trouble, then deal with them using force. With this, the opposite parties wouldn’t suspect anything. After all, this goes along with your overbearing character. Show a little impatience. If you suddenly go full low-key, then the thoughts of those fellows might wander. Understood?”

Addison nodded, “Yes, Young Master. Rest assured.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then said, “I won’t come out in the meantime. If I go out, then those people might prepare, this would be bad for our future plans.”

Addison smiled and said, “Young Master doesn’t need to make a move. If you do, then we would be useless. Rest assured, we will take care of it.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Good. Then I will hand this matter over to you. I’ll be making a map inside the Space while you take care of things here.”

Addison nodded. Then Zhao Hai waved his hand, allowing Addison and the others to leave. After the three left, Zhao Hai took his magic staff and made some needles out of it before having the needles fly out.

Although these needles were small, they could essentially do what the Blood Ghost Staff could. They could allow the Space to make a map of the surroundings, and this was what Zhao Hai wanted

Most importantly, Zhao Hai didn’t dare make things that were larger, like tokens. In the Underworld, almost everyone used spiritual force, especially the Lich; and they could use stealth in the Dark Mist, making them difficult to see. If Zhao Hai sent out anything bigger, then it would be troublesome if they were discovered by the Underworld’s residents.

After releasing the blood needles, Zhao Hai felt relieved. Anything else regarding the Underworld would be handled by Addison and the others, Zhao Hai didn’t need to do anything else.

At this time, Zhao Hai really wanted to capture some Blood Spirit Beasts for the Space. However, he knew that it was still not time. The Dark Temple had just retreated and Zhao Hai was clear that there were still a lot of Undead left near the blood river. If he went to capture some Blood Spirit Beasts at this time, then he would definitely catch the attention of the Resistance Army and the Dark Temple. That wouldn’t be a good thing for Zhao Hai, it would inconvenience him in his further actions.

Because of this, Zhao Hai had nothing left to do in the Underworld. So instead of staying, he went to the Space and work with Cai’er in setting up the Academy Alliance.

It had been a busy half month. In this half-month, Addison resumed control over his 20 cities. In the past, Addison had at least one subordinate at Guli’s level looking after each city. But after the battle against the Dark Temple, some of these cities didn’t have any masters guarding it. This was unfavorable for Addison’s rule. Others in the Resistance Army might use this opportunity to take those cities. This matter needed to be handled well.

However, with Zhao Hai as his backer, manpower was not an issue. Zhao Hai currently had a lot of Undead with Guli’s level inside the Space. Because of this, Zhao Hai handed ten of them to Addison to use.

Actually, Zhao Hai can send more of these high-ranking undead to help Addison. However, Zhao Hai didn’t do it since it would certainly make the Resistance Army pay attention.

In the eyes of the Resistance Army, Addison was fully able to train ten Experts on the level of Guli and Jiang Zheng. After all, Addison had 20 cities under his control. And with their treasures, making these Experts was completely possible. As for more than that, who knows.

Although the addition of the ten high-ranked Undead enabled Addison to regain his control, in the eyes of those in the Underworld, Addison was now on the defense. At this point, Addison would no longer be able to attack, so the others can feel relieved.

At the same time, Addison’s move made the Resistance Army think that Addison had already pulled out all of his resources. And now, expanding for Addison was impossible. Using all of his resources in order to make these ten experts meant that he would have even less resources to train Gold Skeleton-level Undead for his armies.

However, Addison wanted this effect. Also, he discovered that after Zhao Hai handed him the ten experts, the scouting on his cities had significantly decreased, restoring the calmness to these places. This was probably because the other leaders of the Resistance Army thought that Addison would no longer be able to cause trouble. In fact, there were some in the Resistance Army who thought that Addison himself was no longer a threat.

Although he expected this result, Addison still couldn’t help but feel angry. When has Addison been looked down on? Even Zhao Hai has been courteous towards him. And now those bastards from the Resistance Army actually looked down on him, how could Addison not be incensed?

After stabilizing his cities for half a month, Zhao Hai suddenly called Addison into the Space.

Although Addison didn’t know why Zhao Hai decided to call him at this time, he didn’t decline. Upon returning to the Space, Addison discovered that Guli and Jiang Zheng were also here, even Kampala and Gimreden was present. Guli and Jiang Zheng were similarly puzzled while Gimreden and Kampala seem to know why they were here for. At this moment, everyone was looking at Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai looked at each one of their eyes before he smiled and said, “Addison, Guli, Jiang Zheng, I called you over since this has something to do with the Undead Race. I want you to act as witnesses to this event.”

The three Undead looked at Zhao Hai in confusion. Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “Today marks the completion of the Hell Space’s Academy. Also, on this day, there would teachers and foreign students coming from the other Spaces to study alongside the Undead that would be admitted. In the future, there would also be Undead students and teachers who would go to other Academies. It can be said that from today on, the Undead will have the same status as the other races. You can go to study like ordinary people, you don’t need to think about fighting every day.”

Boom! Zhao Hai’s words were without a doubt a huge bomb that exploded inside the heads of Addison, Guli, and Jiang Zheng. Although they had the same wisdom as the HUmans, they didn’t actually think that they would become equals. And because they had wisdom, they knew that having the same lives as the humans was impossible. The Undead were Undead, they can only be regarded as a different class by the other races. They would forever be looked at as a tool, something that would be used, never a race of their own.

Because they didn’t want to become tools, this was the reason why the Resistance Army formed. But in the end they were still conquered by Zhao Hai. Although they were loyal to Zhao Hai, their ambition to get stronger had been extinguished.

But at this time, Zhao Hai told them that the Undead can go to school and have other races as their teacher, they could even go to other Academies to study and sit alongside other races inside a room. Such an opportunity, such a treatment, was only something that they thought of in their dreams.

Chapter 1024: Sacred Land of the Undead

Addison, Jiang Zheng, and Guli stood still, they felt that their fiery souls might come out of their bodies. They didn’t expect this when Zhao Hai called them over today.

After some time, Addison recovered, he looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Young Master, are you telling the truth? Are you really building an Academy for us?”

Gimreden reprimanded him, “What do you mean build? It’s already built. Under Kampala and my supervision, the Academy is finished with no mistakes. You were called in today in order to see the people entering the Academy.”

The trio stared, then they laughed simultaneously as though they planned it beforehand. However, Zhao Hai can feel a bit of sadness from their laughter.

Zhao Hai doing this was equivalent to recognizing their status, recognizing the existence of their race, this made them laugh from happiness. However, Addison, Guli, and Jiang Zheng’s wisdom was no lower than an ordinary person. Because of this, they could understand the status of the Undead in the other planes.

After some time, the trio calmed down. Zhao Hai looked at them before turning his head to Kampala and said, “Let’s go. It’s time to begin.”

The group nodded and then they looked at Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai smiled before he called Laura and the others over before going towards the Hell Space.

To be honest, the Hell Space wasn’t suitable for building an Academy. This was because the place was too dark, it was a mirrored version of the Underworld and Demon Realm. So how could such a place be appropriate for an Academy? However, Zhao Hai still decided to build an Academy here. After all, the Space’s Undead regarded the Hell Space as their own home.

The Undead Academy was built on top of a Bone Mountain. This Bone Mountain was where Gimreden’s original bone field was, it surrounded the Academy itself.

On the skies of the Undead Academy were a group of giant lights. These lights changed their brightness according to the time outside. Allowing proper timekeeping for the people inside.

This was something that Zhao Hai put out. Also, when Zhao Hai recruited teachers from the other races to be sent to Hell Space, he made sure that these teachers didn’t have any malice towards the Undead. At the same time, they should be willing to adapt to the Hell Space’s environment.

Such people weren’t difficult to look for. Whether it be Humans, Dwarves, or Elves, all races had people who were willing to study and concentrate on their own fields. Such people would have a year or more where they wouldn’t leave too far from the place they were in. They were another form of nerds. There were no better than these people to teach in the Undead Academy. Although the Hell Space’s environment was quite difficult, the Undead Academy was the best location in the entire Hell Space. Compared to the other Spaces, it wasn’t bad. Because of this, as long as they can endure, these people could teach in the Undead Academy.

At the same time, Zhao Hai carefully selected the Undead who would be studying in the other Academies. It can be said that since the Undead’s status had been promoted, Zhao Hai needed to pay attention to the Undead Race’s reputation.

When Zhao Hai and the others appeared outside the Undead Academy, they couldn’t help but be shocked. Presently, in a circle all around the Academy, were Undead. These Undead didn’t make any noise nor did they needlessly move. Everyone was presently looking at the constructed Academy.

Zhao Hai used the processing machine in order to make a blueprint of the Academy. Then he had the Space build it. The main material of the Academy was bone. All commonly used facilities in the Academy were made out of bones. There were bone fences, bone houses, bone tables, bone chairs, all bones. But besides these things, the other items like cups, bowls and so on were made out of ordinarily used materials.

Although the Undead Academy let out a gloomy appearance, its beauty was something that one had to recognize. After all, it was a design that came out of the Universal Processing Machine.

The entire Academy was divided into four parts. The first part were the grounds, the second was the teaching building, the third were the laboratories, and the fourth being the dormitories. It was a simple division. However, each region could accommodate 50 thousand teachers and students. One could see how big the Academy was from this statistic.

At this time, the teachers from the other races had already arrived at the Academy and had been settled down. Still, they needed to attend the ceremony today. Even when Zhao Hai had yet to arrive, they were already in front of the Academy. When these teachers saw the dense number of Undead outside the Academy, their scalps couldn’t help but turn cold. This was true even for those researchers who cared for nothing else other than their studies.

When Zhao Hai arrived and saw the Undead, he immediately knew what the lecturers were thinking. However, Zhao Hai himself wasn’t afraid. After all, he dealt with Undead almost every day, and these Undead were also his subordinates. So what was there to be afraid of?

At the same time, even if Laura and the others were prone to being frightened, they saw Lizzy and Megan commanding the Undead. With them being at the side, it was impossible for them to be overly terrified of the Undead.

Just as Zhao Hai arrived in front of the Academy’s gate, All of the Undead in the surroundings knelt down at the same time, as though they were giving worship to Zhao Hai. After giving their respects, the Undead stood up once again. This action was completely spontaneous, nobody was directing them to do it.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect this to happen. However, he still received the gesture. After seeing the Undead stand up, Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “Ever since the day I came out to the world, the Undead Race has always been at my side. My most faithful ally, my most loyal subordinate, and my most powerful sword. However, the Undead Race has never been recognized by the other races, seemingly forgotten in the passage of time. I set up this Academy in order to give the Undead the same status as the other races. This is a message telling you that you are not forgotten. You are always my most trusted subordinates and my sharpest sword. Starting today, the Undead will be equal to the other races inside the Space. You can now go to the Academy and study what you like, do what the others do, and learn what you think is useful for your lives. With all of you as a witness, I declare the official opening of the Undead Academy!”

There was no applause. The Undead were looking dazedly at the Undead Academy while digesting Zhao Hai’s words. One could see the fiery souls on the eyes of the Skeletons shivering, showing that they were moved.

After Zhao Hai’s speech, the Undead knelt towards Zhao Hai at the same time. They gave three kowtows before standing up again. Although the Undead didn’t give any noise, Zhao Hai knew that starting this day, the Undead Academy would become a sacred land of the Space’s Undead.

When the Undead stood up again, Zhao Hai said, “Good. Now, the first batch of students can enter the Academy.”

Before long, the elected first batch of students proceeded to go into the Academy. When they passed by Zhao Hai and the instructors, these Undead gave a short bow before continuing.

The first batch of students numbered twenty thousand. In addition to the instructors from the various races, high-ranked Undead also acted as teachers in the Academy. These teachers would also be trained so that they could some day teach in the Academies of the other Spaces.

Among these Undead instructors, a large part of them were Lich, some were Skeletons, Zombies and Vampires. Lich were the best at researching, so they had quite a lot of research achievements under their belt. On the other hand, the Vampires and the other races were very good at combat. After many years of evolution, these Undead had formed their own combat system. Although it wasn’t necessarily applicable to other races, it was still useful as teaching material.

Before long, all students had finished moving in to the Academy. Under the gazes of the other Undead, the gates of the Academy slowly closed in. Even if all the Undead outside went out to fight, the students and the teachers inside the Academy would have to stay inside. They could only exit either by having permission or by graduating.

After seeing that the gates were done closing, Zhao Hai and the others also entered the Academy. The Undead outside were unwilling to depart for some time. For them, the significance of the Undead Academy was too huge. Just as Zhao Hai thought, it had become a sacred land inside their hearts.

After two hours, the Undead began to slowly disperse. On the other hand, Zhao Hai was currently sitting inside the Academy’s conference room. Inside the room, besides Laura and the others, there was also Gimreden, Kampala, Addison, Jiang Zheng, Guli. At the same time, the instructors sent by the various races were present. Zhao Hai wanted to meet the instructors today and see if they had any needs that needed to be met.

Although these instructors came from different races, all of them had incomparable respect towards Zhao Hai. Because of this, everyone was behaving their best inside the room.

Zhao Hai looked at the instructors and smiled, “Firstly, I need to thank you for coming to the Hell Space to teach. Without you, we wouldn’t be able to manage the Undead. Rest assured, by being in this Academy, you would be given the best allowance. All your needs would also be provided by me for free. Right, does anyone have anything to request?”

A Dwarf stood up and said, “Mister, we don’t have too much requirements. But since I came here to teach forging, I hope that I would have sufficient metals to work on.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “You don’t have to worry about it. The Academy is already prepared for it. It also has supply for your daily needs like food and necessities. You wouldn’t lack anything that you would otherwise have in your own home. Everybody would have to work here for three years. After the first batch of students graduate, you can choose to go home or stay here. I will not stop you if you decide to leave.”

Chapter 1025: Gibbon Brothers and the Five Element Skeletons

When these teachers heard Zhai Hai, they couldn’t help but gawk. Then they shook their heads as one of them said, “Thanks Mister, these things are enough.”

Zhao Hai didn’t think that it would be this simple. He looked at those present and said, “Everyone, if you have any requests, just raise it. I will certainly satisfy your needs.”

At this time, the Dwarf laughed, “Mister, you’re caring too much. All we wanted was a place to study. As for other things, we aren’t very concerned about them. Rest assured, as long as you supply us with materials for experiments, other things wouldn’t be a problem.”

Upon hearing the Dwarf, Zhao Hai smiled, “Everybody can rest assured. You will certainly have something to use in this Academy. There won’t be any shortages. Alright, you can go to your classes, I won’t be holding you here for long.”

The instructors stood up and left after giving Zhao Hai a salute. After the instructors left, Gimreden and Kamapal followed slowly behind. They also have a teaching status in the Academy. Therefore, they needed to go to their classes as well. They gave Zhao Hai a salute before leaving.

After everyone else had left, Zhao Hai turned his head to Addison and the others and said, “What do you think? Later on, there would be more students coming into the Undead Academy. I know that the Academy’s opening is a significant matter to the Undead, therefore I decided to call you here this time in order to witness the event.”

Addison, Guli, and Jiang Zheng stood up, then Addsion looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, thank you for this opportunity. Like you said, this is a significant matter to the Undead Race. Even if my fiery soul gets extinguished, I will never forget this event.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, there’s no need to be overly serious. I’ve been aware of how you’re managing our matters in the Underworld. You’ve done well. I reckon the Resistance Army has already lost their vigilance towards you. It seems like we can make our move soon.”

Addison smiled when he heard Zhao Hai, then he replied, “I’ve been waiting for this day. Young Master, when do we move?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Very soon. Tell me about the general situation of the Resistance Army first. How many opponents do we need to deal with? How many cities does the Resistance Army have? We also need to find which Experts are stationed in which city. Once we know about that, then we can act.”

Addison nodded, he understood what Zhao Hai wanted so he immediately replied, “Right now, the Resistance Army has a total of 121 cities. 21 cities are under my control. The remaining 100 are divided between seven other Great Experts. These seven Experts are the Gibbon Brothers and the Five Element Skeletons.” After he said this, Addison stopped and then looked at Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Continue.”

Addison nodded, “The Gibbon Brothers are two Lich. However, they are different from the other Lich. Ordinary Lich would generally use magic to attack the enemy. However, the Gibbon Brothers actually prefer close-combat assassinations.”

When he heard Addison, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown as he said, “Can the Lich really do successful close-combat assassinations? Tell me more.”

Addison nodded, “I don’t know where the brothers got their weapons, but their weapons are invisible. Mysteriously, these two brothers are Lich, and Lich cannot make physical attacks. Nobody alive has ever seen the weapons of the brothers. Those who have seen it are all dead. Their method of combat was hiding in the Dark Mist, approaching their target slowly. Then when they are about five to ten meters away, they would control their weapon and go for the kill. Even people in my level of strength would be seriously injured if not killed. Because of this, the Gibbon Brothers are considered to be rare Experts in the Resistance Army. They control 30 cities between the two of them.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he waved his hand. Addison continued on, “The Five Element Skeletons are five Skeleton Kings. The strongest one is the Metal-element Skeleton. Nobody knows his name, but he is called Metal Skeleton by everybody. We don’t know why, but he can control metal. Naturally, there isn’t much metal in the Underworld. However, who knows how he did it, but he had a lot of metals. He would attach a lot of metals to his body and during combat, he would command these metals to attack the enemy. He’s quite difficult to deal with.”

After he talked up to this point, Addison turned to Guli and said, “Guli has fought with Metal Skeleton before and had eaten a loss. Guli, tell us about that.”

Guli nodded, then he said, “Right, Metal Skeleton’s strength is very formidable. He uses his energy to attack alongside his metals. Not only could these metals attack, they could also defend and change forms.”

Zhao Hai nodded, Guli continued the introduction in place of Addison, “The second strongest would be the Earth-element Skeleton. This Skeleton is very strong and his defense is the greatest among the five. His attacks are extremely heavy. Average people couldn’t break his defense. His life weapons are huge hammers, his attacks are near unstoppable.”

Guli went on, “The third is the Fire-element Skeleton. He controls yin fire. However, his control is much better compared to other mages. He’s also very difficult to deal with.”

“The fourth is the Water-element Skeleton. It can control water, but not just ordinary water, he controls the blood from the Blood Ponds. The blood inside Blood Ponds already has massive amounts of  energy inside them, this made his water attacks unblockable by average people.”

“The fifth is the Wood-element Skeleton. This one is very special. As the Young Master saw in the past, plants are very hard to come by in the Underworld. Nobody knows where he found it, but the Wood-element Skeleton found a huge tree. This big tree didn’t need land to grow on. As long as you give it blood from the Blood Ponds, then it would be able to grow anywhere. This big tree is very tall at a height of 100 meters and a width of 40 meters. The tree’s body is entirely blood red, no leaf can be seen growing on top of it, only a hard trunk and several branches. When fighting, the Wood-element Skeleton would command the tree to attack and defend. Actually, he isn’t the weakest of the five. Besides Metal Skeleton and the Earth Skeleton, the other three are fairly equal in level.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “So that’s why they’re called the Five Element Skeletons. Interesting. If we take them to the Space, we would certainly experience a growth in power. As for the Gibbon Brothers, I want to have their weapons in my hands.”

Addison looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, where should we make a move first?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Let’s not be anxious. Come look at the map and mark which group owns which city. This is important for our future actions. Once we know which city they are in, then it would be easier to clean them up.”

After he said that, Zhao Hai waved his hand as a three-dimensional holographic map appeared. Naturally, this was just a projection, not an image of the real Underworld.

Addison looked at the projection and verified its accuracy from his memory. Then one by one, he pointed out which people controlled which city. In the hand of the seven Experts were 100 cities. Of the Gibbon Brothers’ 30 cities, five of them were bordering Addison. As for the Five Element Skeletons, the closest to Addison’s Domain were the Wood Skeleton and the Water Skeleton. Each one of them controlled ten cities each.

Actually, Addison originally controlled ten cities. The other 11 cities were from people like Guli and Jiang Zheng’s, experts who didn’t belong to any of the other two factions. Because of this, after conquering these cities, Addison managed to establish his own territory.

After waiting for Addison to mark the territories, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but nod. It can be said that their position wasn’t very advantageous. Addison’s territory was the closest one to the Blood River. If the Dark Temple manages to break through the river, then the first to be attacked would be Addison’s domain.

Zhao Hai looked at the territories belonging to the Wood Skeleton and the Water Skeleton, then he turned his head to Addison and said, “We’ll start with these two first. After dealing with the Wood Skeleton and the Water Skeleton, we’ll deal with the other three. Then after that, we attack the Gibbon Brothers. What do you think?”

Addison nodded and said, “I don’t have any problems with that. I reckon we should deal with the Wood Skeleton first. No matter where, that fellow’s tree is eye-catching. As long as we find that tree, then we can find him and clean him up. Then we can concentrate on dealing with Water Skeleton. As long as we take care of the two of them, the others wouldn’t be a threat.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Good, then we’ll do that. You return to the Underworld first. After determining the position of Wood Skeleton, we will start to deal with him.”

Addison nodded. Then Zhao Hai waved his hand, sending Addison and the others back to the Underworld. After that, he led Laura and the others back to the villa before scanning the cities controlled by Wood Skeleton. He was looking for the skeleton’s trail.

Zhao Hai first looked at what Addison called Blood Tree City. This city was named after Wood Skeleton’s tree, and it was also Wood Skeleton’s main base. But unfortunately, Zhao Hai didn’t see the skeleton there. However, he managed to find the huge tree at another city. At the same time, Zhao Hai was met by an unexpected surprise!!

Chapter 1026: Whoever Strikes First Will Gain The Advantage

Instead of Blood Tree City, Zhao Hai found Wood Skeleton in Blood Drop City. However, Blood Drop City was actually the city closest to Addison’s Domain.

It was at the border!

Blood Drop City was a border city between Addison and Wood Skeleton. Now that Addison’s strength has been greatly damaged, Wood Skeleton’s presence in Blood Drop city would make people come up with ideas.

Also, what Zhao Hai didn’t expect was that in Blood Drop City, Wood Skeleton wasn’t the only king-level Undead, there were four other skeletons present. These four looked different than the other skeletons. The five skeletons were present here.

One skeleton was golden yellow. He sat down on a huge iron chair. Who knows how many pieces of metal this iron chair had. One could see that this was Metal Skeleton.

The second was a purple skeleton. This skeleton was particularly large, he looked buffed and strong. He sat there as though he was an immovable mountain. One could see at first glance how strong this man could be. It was no doubt that this man was Earth Skeleton.

The third skeleton was blood red. It looked somewhat slender. Compared to Earth Skeleton who was beside it, the skeleton appeared even smaller. Moreover, from the skeleton’s shape, it was actually a female skeleton.

The fourth skeleton was a black one. It was pure black, there was no other point that wasn’t. However, on top of the skeleton’s head was a long silvery hair. The long hair gently swayed with the wind, but it was unexpectedly made out of Yin Fire. It was needless to say that this was Fire Skeleton.

Although the last skeleton was also blood red, he looked more manly compared to the female skeleton. Its height was no shorter than Earth Skeleton and on his hand was a blood red branch. Without a doubt, this was Wood Skeleton.

The Five Element Skeletons being in Blood Drop City was an even more thought-provoking scene. If they said that didn’t have any ideas on Addison’s territory, then even Grey Skeletons wouldn’t believe it.

When Zhao Hai saw this situation, his two eyes couldn’t help but narrow. Then he chuckled and said, “Interesting. Very interesting. They actually wanted to make the first move. Good, good, then there’s no need for us to wait. Lizzy, immediately assemble the army. Besides those in the Undead Academy, have everyone prepared for battle.”

Lizzy nodded before she began to prepare. Zhao Hai’s figure moved an reappeared in Three Saint City. Addison and the others were waiting for Zhao Hai’s news. However, they didn’t expect Zhao Hai to appear this soon.

Addison looked puzzled as Zhao Hai, “Young Master, why did you come?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “If I didn’t come, then you wouldn’t know that someone is already at your door. I just saw the Five Element Skeletons in Blood Drop City. If we don’t act, I’m afraid they would be able to make the first move. Immediately prepare for battle.”

Addison stared, his expression sank before he coldly snorted and said, “So those fellows actually dared to aim their claws at me. It seems like they really think that our losses have been very heavy. They want to take my cities by force.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Isn’t this alright? This way, we can catch all of them in one net. We can save ourselves from finding them one by one. Let’s go, we’ll be making our move.” Addison nodded. Then Zhao Hai waved his hands as they entered the Space. The next moment, they appeared outside Blood Drop City.

When they appeared in Blood Drop City, Addison couldn’t help but stare. The entire city was completely surrounded by undead. There were billions of high-ranked Undead, not even a fly would be able to fly through. Naturally, this was assuming that there were flies in the Underworld.

After looking at the dense Undead, even Addison felt his scalp go numb. This was true for the others as well. Zhao Hai looked at them, he smiled faintly and said, “Addison, you go and call them out.”

Addison complied, then he flew to the skies of Blood Drop City and shouted, “You five rotten slugs! You actually plan to attack me. Get out of here!” His sound travelled very far, reaching deep into Blood Drop City.

Naturally, this alarmed the five skeletons. They had just been discussing about how to deal with Addison. But even before they made a move, Addison was already outside their door. Also, Addison’s arrival was so quick that they weren’t even able to feel Addison coming. It was impossible for them to use their spiritual force at all times.. Of course, they didn’t know that Blood Drop City has already been surrounded.

But when they heard Addison, they immediately swept their spiritual force outwards. Upon using their spiritual force, they couldn’t help but stare, then quickly flew out of the city.

The Five Element Skeletons were stunned. They had never seen such a big scene. It has to be said that the five of them had secretly met with each other, so they didn’t bring any of their subordinates. And even if they did bring their subordinates, their high-ranked Undead could never reach such a number.

The five Skeletons quickly flew towards Addison. Wood Skeleton looked at Addison and said, “Addison, what do you want to do? Why did you bring your army in my city? Do you want war?”

Addison looked coldly at Wood Skeleton and said, “Don’t talk nonsense with me. You should know more than me about why you five are gathered here. I won’t waste my breath anymore. Submit to me or die!”

When the Five Element Skeletons heard this, they knew that Addison didn’t come today to make friends. Wood Skeleton coldly snorted and said, “Addison, although you are strong, there’s no way for you to fight all five of us. And as long as one of us escapes today, the Resistance Army certainly wouldn’t let you off.”

Addison gave out a loud laugh as he answered, “Hahaha, you’re too naive. Do you really think that you can escape? I’ve always been planning to go after all of you. Now that you’ve grouped yourselves up, you have given me the opportunity to save time. Don’t make me say it again, surrender or die”!

The worst temper out of the five, Earth Skeleton, coldly replied, “There’s so much nonsense, we’ll let our hands do the talking.” After saying that, he took two weapons out. His weapons were two huge hammers. The hammers roared as they aimed towards Addison. The other four Skeletons also made their moves. Each one of them used their own weapons to target Addison. Naturally, they had a plan of taking care of the leader first.

But at this time, Zhao Hai also made a move. In his hands were also two hammers. Moreover, these two hammers were much bigger compared to Earth Skeleton’s. Zhao Hai proceeded to dash towards Earth Skeleton.

Addison also took his weapon out as he went to attack Water Skeleton. Guli and the other Undead began to move as well.

Although the Five Element Skeletons didn’t bring a lot of soldiers, there were still a lot of troops inside the city. When they saw the confrontation, they naturally came out to fight.

Even if the Five Element Skeletons brought fewer troops, what they brought this time were their elite, just to ensure their safety. When these soldiers met with Lizzy and Megan’s Undead, they were almost immediately in a deadlock. This deadlock happened because Lizzy and Megan needed to allocate a portion of the Undead into stopping the Five Element Skeletons from escaping. Otherwise, these Undead would not be able to survive for long.

By this time, Zhao Hai had already clashed a few times with Earth Skeleton. One had to recognize that Earth Skeleton was truly very strong. He was innately stronger compared to the Barbarians. However, Zhao Hai’s strength wasn’t small either. Four hammers caused ear-splitting sounds in the air as they clashed.

Then at this moment, Metal Skeleton turned his metal chair into a huge rotating metal ball. Tiny shrapnels from this metallic sphere shot out towards Zhao Hai’s Undead.

Zhao Hai, who was fighting against Earth Skeleton, coldly snorted when he saw this. Then Metal Skeleton began to feel that the shrapnels he released had stopped, after that he began to lose control of these shrapnels as they formed a metallic sphere of their own.

Upon seeing this, Metal Skeleton couldn’t help but stare. The fiery soul on his eyes fluttered for a moment. Naturally he was very surprised. And since he was a man who went through many battles, he knew that there was only one explanation for this. Another Expert in metal manipulation was present, and the expert had a stronger grasp on the metal element.

After he thought about this, Metal Skeleton couldn’t help but stop the small sphere as he looked around him. However, he didn’t find any suspicious people.

It needs to be known that even if Zhao Hai was fighting with Earth Skeleton, he still had his control over the five elements. He rarely used these abilities. But after Metal Skeleton dared to show off in front of him, Zhao Hai decided to be impolite, going directly head to head with Metal Skeleton’s control.

On the other side, Wood Skeleton was controlling his own Blood Tree as he fought against the high-ranked Undead. Although these Undead were much weaker than him, their sheer number prevented Wood Skeleton from dealing with them in a short period of time.

This was Wood Skeleton’s firsthand experience in fighting against battle formations. However, Wood Skeleton began to feel strange. He couldn’t understand where these Undead came from. He didn’t believe that Addison hid this hand for so long. If Addison had such strength, then he wouldn’t have lost so much during the battle of Blood River.

Upon thinking about this, Wood Skeleton’s eyes turned towards Zhao Hai who was still fighting against Earth Skeleton. Wood Skeleton’s vision began to turn clear. The issue possibly had to do with the appearance of this mysterious Dark Pharoah. They hadn’t heard Addison having such a formidable Dark Pharoah as a subordinate before.

The one having the worst time of them all was Fire Skeleton. Fire Skeleton originally had very few flaws. After all, fire was always good to use when attacking an enemy.

Unfortunately for him, he was facing against Zhao Hai’s Undead. Fire Skeleton uses yin fire in order to attack. However, Zhao Hai managed to absorb yin fire before, improving the Hell King’s ship as well as making the Space’s undead unafraid to face it.

Being unafraid of yin fire was equal to breaking Fire Skeleton’s strongest attacks. Because of this, Fire Skeleton became distressed. It can be said that he was the one being pursued by the Space’s Undead.

Metal Skeletons attacking methods were restricted. Earth Skeleton was entangled with Zhao Hai. Water Skeleton was busy dealing with Addison, Fire Skeleton was being pursued by the Undead. And Wood Skeleton wouldn’t be able to look for help.

In this case, the Five Element Skeletons would suffer a defeat sooner or later. Actually, if Zhao Hai used his whole strength to attack, the skeletons would have already been dealt with. However, Zhao Hai didn’t want to use his full strength. He wanted to use this battle to gain fighting experience. Now that he was strong, there were very few opportunities for him have a proper fight with.  Because of this, Zhao Hai lacked proper battle experience. This would be disadvantageous as his enemies get stronger.

In the battle at Blood River, Zhao Hai didn’t make a move because at that time, they were planning to show their weakness. In that case, it was impossible for Zhao Hai to make a move. But now that Zhao Hai was prepared to conquer the Five Element Skeletons, it was natural for him to personally attack.

It didn’t take long before the Five Element Skeleton’s subordinates were taken care of. Then Zhao Hai’s Undead entered Blood Drop City and began to take the Undead. Those who were grasped were immediately thrown into the Space.

One must know that cities in the Underworld were anything but small, and it showed in the number of Undead inside each one. Take Blood Drop City, for example, there were nearly 100 million Undead inside. But upon facing billions of enemies no weaker than themselves, these Undead didn’t have any chance to escape. In less than an hour, the Undead inside the city had been caught and sent to the Space.

After seizing those Undead, Zhao Hai’s Undead army began to surround the Five Element Skeletons. At this moment, Fire Skeleton had been injured. Earth Skeleton wasn’t doing very well either. Zhao Hai had completely suppressed his actions. Although Metal Skeleton had turned his metal sphere into a giant axe, he was actually being tied down by Guli and Jiang Zheng, he simply couldn’t withdraw. At the same time, Water Skeleton was being pressed hard by Addison, it was evident that she wouldn’t last another 100 moves.

As for Wood Skeleton, he had yet to experience a huge threat. But upon seeing the number of Undead surrounding them, he knew that he couldn’t withdraw, nor could he save the others.

Upon seeing the fate of Blood Drop City, Wood Skeleton knew that it was the end, and he couldn’t find any chance for them to escape.

At this time, Fire Skeleton, who had been continuously hounded by the Undead, was about to get killed. When he saw this situation, Wood Skeleton couldn’t wait anymore. He immediately surrendered, “Mister Addison, please stop. I am willing to submit!”

Although he had surrendered, Wood Skeleton still kept swinging his tree towards the surrounding Undead. But this time, it wasn’t meant to attack, but as a means of self-preservation.

After his surrender was announced, the Undead attacking Wood Skeleton stopped. But they still surrounded him in all directions.

Chapter 1027: Subduing the Five Element Skeletons

When Earth Skeleton heard Wood Skeleton’s surrender, he couldn’t help but shout, “You spineless coward! You don’t deserve to be an Undead!” Although he was pressured by Zhao Hai, his defense was still very good. Therefore, he still had some room to shout to Wood Skeleton.

Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai said, “What, you don’t want to surrender? You want to die? Give up an almost immortal life just to become someone’s food? Is that what you want?”

Words can execute hearts!

Zhao Hai’s words could be said to be targeting the heart of the enemy, hitting the Undead’s weakness. An Undead’s life was almost endless. If they were like Gimreden who wholeheartedly delved themselves into research, then they wouldn’t care about life and death. They had already looked at both sides. To them, there was no difference between the two.

However, Earth Skeleton and the others were different. People like Gimreden haven’t tasted authority and power. For Earth Skeleton and the others, the longer they live, then the bigger their authority would become. Because of this, they didn’t want to die. This was also the reason why Wood Skeleton surrendered.

When Zhao Hai spoke his words, the aura of the Skeletons couldn’t help but weaken. After Zhao Hai spoke, Earth Skeleton didn’t make any noise. Although he was still defending, the defense had lost its fierce aura.

 Zhao Hai was Earth Skeleton’s opponent, so naturally he was able to sense the changes to the Skeleton’s mood. He also learned a trick. Sometimes, in battle, psychological pressure might just be the last straw to break the camel’s back.

After he found out about the changes to Earth Skeleton, Zhao Hai’s hammer changed after his next attack. As he hammered down on Earth Skeleton, the skeleton proceeded to block. However, the hammers in Zhao Hai’s hands were suddenly exchanged into a huge net, capturing Earth Skeleton in the process. Earth Skeleton was shocked and wanted to struggle, however, the net had completely tied him up, giving him no opportunity to fight back.

After seizing Earth Skeleton, Zhao Hai turned his attention towards Metal Skeleton. It can be said that among these group of people, Metal Skeleton was the most threatening one. But who knew that he would meet Zhao Hai? Because of this, the Skeleton’s threat was reduced to its lowest point. Metal Skeleton had turned his metal ball into a huge axe as he battle against Guli and Jiang Zheng in close combat.

After sensing that Zhao Hai’s attention was placed on him, Metal Skeleton knew that it was the end. After he thought about this, he couldn’t help but put his weapon down as he said, “I’m willing to surrender.”

When Water Skeleton saw that her peers were either on the verge of dying or had surrendered, leaving her alone to fend for herself, she also dropped her weapon. At this point, the battle was over.

Zhao Hai and the others also withdrew their weapons. Zhao Hai turned his head to Addison and nodded. Addison immediately understood what Zhao Hai meant. He turned to the Five Element Skeletons and said, “Since you submit, then follow me.” After he said that, a spatial rift opened up before he flew in.

The Five Element Skeletons couldn’t help but stare when they saw this. However, they couldn’t retreat even if they wanted to. Therefore, they could only clench their teeth as they also entered the rift.

When the Skeletons entered the rift, the Space immediately issued a prompt, “Five Yin Element Skeletons detected. Subduing. Subjugation complete. Extracting their abilities and strengthening the Host’s control abilities. Extraction complete, strengthening complete!”

Zhao Hai felt the energy inside his body grow a bit stronger, then there wasn’t anything else. Zhao Hai was also aware that he was already very strong, so the increase of the five elements could only do so much to him.

At this time, another prompt sounded out, “Variant ancient tree detected. Extracting seeds, seeds extracted. Seeds can now be bought in the Space’s store. Tree can be planted in the Hell Space. The tree’s main attack has yin attribute.”

When he heard this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gawk. But then he understood that this ancient tree was Wood Skeleton’s blood tree. Zhao Hai hadn’t thought about it before, he was only reminded when he heard the Space’s prompt.

Zhao Hai cured Fire Skeletons’ injuries first before taking them to the villa along with Addison’s group.

Laura and the others were currently having the Undead clean up the battlefield. Actually, there was nothing much to take care of. This time, they completely suppressed Blood Droop City. There weren’t that many Undead who got killed, most of them had been caught and sent to the Space.

After cleaning up, Laura and the others began to release Blood Drop City’s Undead back. With this, outsiders wouldn’t see anything wrong.

Zhao Hai entered the room and waved his hand as he said, “Everyone, please take a seat.” Addison and the others obediently sat, the Five Element Skeletons sat down as well. The skeletons had already been subdued by the Space.

When everyone had settled down, Zhao Hai said, “I didn’t expect to capture all of you at the same time. This saved me a lot of trouble. The next thing we have to do is to conquer your cities before we deal with the Gibbon Brothers. Addison, you discuss how to deal with this matter. But don’t make too big of a move.”

Addison and the others nodded before they turned around and left. After that, Zhao Hai turned his attention to Laura and the others who were currently looking at the monitor. At this time, the monitor was displaying Blood Drop City’s situation. The City’s Undead had been released back, naturally they were now Zhao Hai’s subordinates.

Zhao Hai looked at this and smiled as he said, “Good. You’re getting more and more adept at this. Cai’er, is there any possibility for the others to suspect us?”

Cai’er shook her head and said, “Young Master, you can rest assured. Since our action is too fast, nobody should have found out about it.”

Zhao Hai began to relax, then he turned to Laura and said, “Good, it seems like the Resistance Army would soon be under my control.”

Laura also smiled as she said, “I didn’t expect it to go this smoothly. Brother Hai, those people don’t look too powerful. Compared to your fight with Addison, they seem to fall short.”

Zhao Hai laughed, “You underestimate me. I’ve been constantly progressing ever since I acquired the Myriad Stellar Transformations Ying Yang Art. It took so long to fight Addison because one, it’s the first time I’ve ran into my match, and second, I have a lack of combat experience. At this time, Addison is no longer my opponent, even if I don’t use my Blood Ghost Staff.”

Laura replied, “Brother Hai, from what I can see, I suggest that you should be using the function of your staff more often. Otherwise, the fights would take too long. Brother Hai, you seem to have forgotten, the Blood Ghost Staff is your weapon, and nobody can take it away. Not using its transformations would be too wasteful. You should be transforming your staff appropriately in order to deal with your enemy. This should be how you fight in the future.”

Zhao Hai gawked, he always thought that using his Blood Ghost Staff all the time would be a bit too overkill. Now that Laura had reminded him, he couldn’t help but feel stupid. Just as Laura said, the staff was his own weapon, nobody else could use it. He can also take it out at any time. If he didn’t use his staff, then it would surely be a waste.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but give out an embarrassed smile as he said, “Thanks for the reminder. I’ve been negligent. I will do better in the future.”

Laura giggled as she gave Zhao Hai a kiss. This was the aspect that she liked about Zhao Hai the most. He knew how to admit to his mistakes. Moreover, he was very good at listening to suggestions and wouldn’t dismiss anything that embarrassed him. Not being angered after being corrected was Zhao Hai’s greatest strong point.

At this time, Addison and the others have reached an agreement. Addison bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, we’ve already made a plan. After we head back, we will immediately execute it.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Go, remember to keep everything secret, don’t let anybody discover our actions. I’d prefer we spend more time to keep it a secret than having other people find out.”

Addison and the others nodded. Then they bowed to Zhao Hai and left. Zhao Hai turned his head to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, supervise their actions. If they need any help, give it to them. As long as we can smoothly take the domain of the Five Element Skeletons, the Resistance Army is essentially ours.”

Cai’er gave a nod, she immediately understood Zhao Hai’s command. Only once Zhao Hai gained the Resistance Army’s territory would he become one of the three major forces in the Underworld. And with the Resistance Army in his control, he could now expand outwards and swallow the entire plane.

Cai’er was very clear how important the Underworld was to Zhao Hai. It can be said that both the Divine Realm or the Atlanta Plane couldn’t compare to the importance of the Underworld. The Underworld’s Dark Mist can block most creatures from entering the plane. This meant that Zhao Hai would have a very safe rear base. Moreover, this rear base would also produce troops, a steady stream of troops, which was also important for Zhao Hai.

Most importantly, there were also those huge skeletons as well as the plants of the Underworld. The Space was already more than level 100, yet it still couldn’t find out their uses. This was enough to cause Zhao Hai to place his attention to the plane.

What they need to do right now was to take the Underworld. After doing that, then they would go to the Atlanta Plane to look for the Ascension magic armor. If they couldn’t use the magic armor, then they could only ascend in the Divine Realm. Although doing so would cause Lu Wei to pursue them, Zhao Hai would be able to manage since he had the troops from the Underworld. And as long as Zhao Hai’s strength continues to go up, there would come a time where they wouldn’t be afraid of Lu Wei anymore.

Also, Zhao Hai had some suspicions about that fellow in the Dark Temple. Zhao Hai thinks that controlling the Underworld through the Dark Temple shouldn’t be just for acquiring troops. Perhaps there was another goal, but Zhao Hai has no way to find out about it right now.

Chapter 1028: 10 Billion Undead Army

Actually, once you subdue most of the high-ranked Undead in the Underworld, the low-ranked would be very easy to deal with. The territory of the Five Element Skeleton was an example of this. After reaching an agreement, the Five Element Skeletons returned to their territories. When they arrived, the Skeletons immediately had their people enter the Space.

Levels were very strict in the Underworld, this allowed the Five Element Skeletons to order their subordinates with ease. If their subordinates dared to rebel, then they would immediately be killed. Also, the high-ranked Undead under the Skeletons were in a soul contract. And unlike Addison, these Undead didn’t have any means to erase it. Therefore, these Undead could only follow the orders that their masters gave them.

After subduing all of the Five Element Skeleton’s subordinates, there was only one thing left to do, this was to send all of the remaining undead inside the Cities into the Space.

Compared to sending the Five Element Skeleton’s subordinates to the Space, this one was much more difficult to complete. Although the Five Element Skeletons were far more powerful than these Undead, there were undead who didn’t necessarily heed to all their demands. After all, the Five Element Skeletons didn’t have a soul contract with them.

Zhao Hai asked Addison and knew that even high-ranked Undead would have limited Undead that they could control. For example, Addison’s control couldn’t exceed 100 people. And then the control of these people couldn’t exceed 90. As the hierarchy goes down, then the limit of control would also decrease. In the end, most Undead on the level of silver skeletons could only control 20 or so Undead.

Addison’s army was built like a pyramid. He conquered Undead who in turn conquered their own. With this system, an army was slowly formed.

However, people like Addison wouldn’t just rashly use their quota for 100 people. This wouldn’t be too beneficial to them. If they encounter a high-ranked Undead but their quota was already full of low-ranked Undead, then it would be too much of a loss.

For this reason, King-level Undead like Addison wouldn’t form too many soul contracts. However, because there were a lot of Undead in the Underworld, some Undead would still surrender to Addison and become his subordinates.

This surrender didn’t mean that a contract was made, there was no need for one. It was a relationship similar to a weaker being seeking protection from the strong. Addison would protect them while they work for Addison. They were also an integral part of Addison’s army. However, it was still clear that these Undead weren’t as good as the contracted Undead. If Addison gained some good resources, then he would definitely prefer to give them to the Undead that were contracted to him. This caused a gap between the contracted and non-contracted Undead.

Also, there were some Undead in the Resistance Army who didn’t want to surrender to the strong. This made their lives much more dangerous, but they still didn’t want to submit to anybody.

There were plenty of these Undead in each City. Although these Undead gave respects to the powerful, they wouldn’t give their unconditional obedience to them. At the same time, it would also be impossible for a City Lord to force them, otherwise they would leave. And this would be the prelude of a perishing city.

For these reasons, it wasn’t easy for the Five Element Skeletons to gain full control of the Undead in their cities. If these Undead escaped, then they would surely spread the information. And if it reached the ears of the Gibbon Brothers, then they might be prompted to move.

Even if Zhao Hai could subdue the Gibbon Brothers using his overwhelming strength, the Brothers had billions upon billions of Undead in their cities. With Zhao Hai’s current strength, it was impossible for him to eat them all up in one go. Only when he subdued all the Undead in the Five Element Skeleton’s territory would he have the possibility to do so. Before that happens, Zhao Hai didn’t want information to be passed on. If the Dark Temple gets word about what was happening, then the trouble would be bigger.

The Five Element Skeletons collectively controlled 70 cities. The size of these cities varied, but in general, their overall population ranged from 600 million to 7 billion. Such enormous number wouldn’t be very easy to subdue.

What Zhao Hai dreaded wasn’t these ordinary Undead but instead those fellows from the Dark Temple. If the Dark Temple came to know about this matter, then they would certainly make a move. Because of this, secrecy needed to be kept in this situation.

Fortunately, in the Underworld, besides those who were had great strength, not a lot of Undead would go to another city. Most of them were only active in and around their city of residence.

With this in place, one could be assured that communications between cities would be minimal. It can even be said that each city was sealed of from the others. This gave Zhao Hai an opportunity to defeat each city one by one.

Because of this, Zhao Hai wasn’t too worried. They would start with Wood Skeleton’s territory first before proceeding towards Water Skeleton’s place. They would subdue cities bit by bit, one after another. Then they would proceed to the other territories, conquering all of the Undead along the way.

Zhao Hai had been very patient, starting to subdue one or two cities per day wasn’t a problem. With more and more Undead going into his hands, it wouldn’t be long before they would be able to subdue multiple cities in one day. After all, the managers of those cities had already become their people. With those people in hand, it wouldn’t be very difficult to conquer all of the Undead residents.

With this set-up, it took nearly one month before all of the Undead from the Five Element Skeleton’s territory were captured. Now, they would proceed to deal with the Gibbon Brothers.

Upon capturing all of the Undead, Zhao Hai noted that the Undead inside the Space had already numbered to over 13 billion. This was definitely a very huge number.

Fortunately, besides the Hell Space, Zhao Hai bought several other dark-attributed backgrounds. These backgrounds would be enough to house these Undead.

This didn’t mean that the Hell Space couldn’t accommodate all of these Undead. It was just that it wouldn’t be easy to manage these Undead if they were all inside a single Space. Therefore, Zhao Hai had 5 other backgrounds each with 2 billion Undead inside. Zhao Hai also established Undead Academies in these backgrounds. Naturally, these Academies were just branches of the original Undead Academy. There were no instructors from other races in these Academies. However, they still managed to inspire the Undead living in each Space.

The Five Element Skeletons were unaware about these matters until Addison told them. Upon knowing that the Undead could study, and even be taught by the other races, the Five Element Skeletons were moved, their respect for Zhao Hai increased even more.

In this month of time, while Zhao Hai subdued the Undead in the Five Element Skeleton’s territory, the Divine Realm wasn’t going very peacefully.

The O’Neal family already had a firm standing in the Taurus Continent. After transferring more higher levelled magic armors, the O’Neal family gained more courage. They started to explore the Taurus Continent, mining the resources while also surveying the Barbarian, Winged Pegasus, and Thunder Clan planes. There was nobody inside these planes to prevent them from doing so.

Because of this, the O’Neal family brought a lot of slaves from the Atlanta Plane. One shouldn’t underestimate these slaves. Slave trade wasn’t something new to the Atlanta Plane. Because of this, keeping and nurturing these slaves were very well managed. In the Atlanta Plane, slaves weren’t immediately taken to do work. Instead, they were trained to control civilian magic armor first. Only after learning how to drive these magic armors were these slaves allowed to be sold off.

The O’Neal family obtained a domain several times larger than the Ark Continent. Naturally, this meant that they would need a lot of manpower. Because of this, they bought trained slaves en masse.

The reason for the O’Neal family’s anxiety were the foreign races. They knew that the enemy were very powerful. If they don’t develop as soon as possible, then it was highly probable that the Foreign Races would seriously attack them in the future. If this happened, then they would have no way to resist.

However, the O’Neal family didn’t expect the Foreign races to attack so soon. It had just been two months since the last conflict between the two parties.

This time, the exchange between the O’Neal family and the Foreign Races weren’t huge-scale battles. Instead, the Foreign Races employed small-unit tactics. They would make a short attack before retreating. This made the O’Neal family anxious.

Naturally, this exchange was brought to Zhao Hai’s attention. He didn’t think that the Foreign Races would wage war against the O’Neal family in such a short time.

However, after further deliberation, Zhao Hai knew why the Foreign Races chose to do this. The strength of the Foreign Races came from their population. Because of this, these small-scale battles would be able to slowly chip out the military power of the O’Neal family. They would obtain great victory by grinding the O’Neal family down.

This idea was good, but the tactics weren’t executed well. After all, their speed was just on par with the magic armors. After looking at the battles for several days, Zhao Hai finally lost his interest.

At this time, Zhao Hai’s thoughts weren’t on the O’Neal family and the Foreign Races, but instead it was on the Gibbon Brothers. His interest was greatly roused upon hearing about the unusual pair of Lich from Addison.

Chapter 1029: Weapons of the Gibbon Brothers

The Gibbon Brothers, despite being Lich, weren’t using magic to attack their enemy, instead they use assassination techniques. This surprised Zhao Hai. What made Zhao Hai even more surprised were the weapons the two used.

The Lich were truly a very bizzare race. They didn’t have any physical bodies, so they weren’t afraid of physical attacks. But at the same time, this also made them unable to have any physical strength. Both attack and defense of the Lich were made using magic. There weren’t any suitable weapons for them here in the Underworld.

However, this didn’t mean that the Lich weren’t able to touch things. They were able to do so but not with their hands, but with their spiritual force instead. Technically, the Lich were able to make physical attacks, after all they can control these things.

But most of the Lich don’t use this method. This was because this method had a weak point. Since it used their spiritual force, making an attack this way would also allow their enemies to damage their souls. Once their souls were attacked, then they would be in immediate danger.

Additionally, the Lich hide in the Dark mist, bringing weapons would just make them visible. Because of this, no Lich was stupid enough to bring any weapon to the battlefield.

But now, the Gibbon Brothers became famous by using assassination techniques. This made Zhao Hai very interested. To be honest, Zhao Hai wasn’t interested in the pair of Lich, but in the weapons they use instead.

Powerhouses in the Underworld knew about the Gibbon Brothers as well as the weapon that they use. However, nobody alive ever saw these weapons; those who did were already dead. But everybody could affirm that these weapons weren’t ordinary.

Lich didn’t have physical bodies, naturally this included the Gibbon Brothers. This made it so that they couldn’t wield weapons like the other Undead. But for so many years, nobody had even seen the weapons held by the Gibbon Brothers. Despite that, everyone knew that the brothers weren’t using magic when killing. This made people wonder about the extraordinary weapon that allowed the Lich to wield them.

The Lich could also refine energy. Zhao Hai discovered this when he entered Kampala’s room. Kampala was able to compress magic to a certain degree and shape it as a weapon. However, using such magic in assassination wouldn’t work.

Although magic compression had a process, it was a process that was easily broken. If one sneaks up on an enemy and this process fails, then they wouldn’t even know how they died. This was because initiating magic compression would make the target know about your presence, making them quickly react. This small delay would allow the other party to dodge or counterattack before the process finishes.

If one uses compressed magic before they attack, then it still wouldn’t work. This was because such strong magic would surely attract the attention of the enemy. Also, compressed magic wasn’t any different than physical weapons, making it visible to those in the surroundings. Because of this, the powerhouses of the Underworld were sure that the Gibbon Brothers weren’t using magic.

The two weapons were what Zhao Hai valued. The power level of the Underworld wasn’t low. Experts like Addison were equivalent to low ranked cultivators in Lu Wei’s realm. It can even be said that the Underworld was a much higher-leveled plane compared to the Divine Realm.

And in such a plane, the Gibbon Brothers were able to gain reputation using their techniques. Moreover, nobody knew how they did it, explaining how uncommon their weapons were. It can also be seen that their weapons had qualifications to be used in the Cultivation Realm.

The more he thought about it, the more interested Zhao Hai became. He wanted to know what these weapons really were. If these weapons could be integrated to his own staff, then the benefits would surely be big.

At this time, Zhao Hai’s blood ghost staff already had a lot functions inside it, and its attacking power was also very strong. However, Zhao Hai always felt that there was still room for improvement for the staff. Therefore, he wanted to see if the weapons in the hands of the Gibbon Brothers would help.

After Zhao Hai took care of the Five Element Skeleton’s subordinates, he began to prepare for dealing with the Gibbon Brothers. However, before Zhao Hai could begin, flames of war began to erupt in the Divine Realm, diverting his attention. But after seeing that there was nothing important, he began to resume his preparation.

The Gibbon Brothers were very famous in the Underworld. It can be said that they were the actual rulers of the Resistance Army. Naturally, this was before Addison appeared. Addison’s appearance was an official challenge to the Gibbon Brothers. And it was the Gibbon Brothers who used the Dark Temple to suppress Addison last time. They wouldn’t allow Addison to threaten their rule of the Resistance Army.

But this time, the Gibbon Brothers had made a huge miscalculation. They didn’t expect that Addison would surpass their expectations under Zhao Hai’s guide. They didn’t even expect the Five Element Skeletons to be completely subdued. They also didn’t consider Addison to be subordinated to someone like Zhao Hai. It can be said that the Gibbon Brothers had become isolated in the entire Resistance Army.

Despite this, Zhao Hai still wouldn’t underestimate the brothers. The Gibbon Brothers had led the Resistance Army against the Dark Temple for so many years, it was impossible for them to be simple people. In the face of such people, making mistakes would be very dangerous. If Zhao Hai let them escape to the Dark Temple, then things would become more troublesome.

Zhao Hai also felt abit curious about the Gibbon Brothers. This pair of brothers were hailed as the strongest in the Resistance Army, making them the rulers of the group. However, they didn’t make the other powers in the army submit to them. Even after Addison was suppressed for wanting to unify the Resistance Army, the Gibbon Brothers still left Three Saint City alone, which was a surprise for Zhao Hai.

But no matter what, the Gibbon Brothers needed to submit to him. If they decided to resist, then there was no need for further discussion, they would be killed!

Zhao Hai’s plan was similar to what he did with the Five Element Skeletons. He would first find the Gibbon Brothers then directly send Undead to surround them, but this time this also includes their cities.

The reason Zhao Hai dared to do so this time was because he had enough manpower. His military strength had already reached beyond 10 billion. Surrounding 30 cities with such numbers was possible.

Addison and the others also agreed to this plan. Addison didn’t believe that they wouldn’t be able to deal with the Gibbon Brothers with the help of the Five Element Skeletons as well as Zhao Hai. And as long as they took care of the Gibbon Brothers, everything else would be a cinch.

Zhao Hai finally found where the two Brothers were located. The two were currently inside the most developed city that they controlled, Soul Warrior City.

There was a tower inside Soul Warrior City. This was also the tallest and thickest tower that Zhao Hai saw in the Underworld so far.

The entire structure towered at 200 meters. It also had a diameter of 100 meters. Because of this, although the tower was tall, it still gave out a strong and sturdy appearance.

The tower followed the architectural style of the Underworld which was extreme simplicity. Nobody could see anything special about the tower from the outside.

However, Zhao Hai can notice some fine details on the tower. There seems to be blood vessels on the tower’s surface. As soon as he saw this, Zhao Hai believed that this tower was the same as the one Kampala made. It can use the blood in a Blood Spring in order to control the city’s defensive magic formation.

The Gibbon Brothers lived in this tower, along with their subordinates. Since the brothers were Lich, they also cared for their own fellow Lich. Because of this, no other Undead lived in this tower besides the Lich race.

Zhao Hai’s staff had already mapped the entire Soul Warrior City. From what Zhao Hai can see, the Gibbon Brothers had yet to come out of their tower.

In fact, Zhao Hai learned from Addison that the two Brothers were just like the other Lich in their love for research. Because of this, they rarely come out of their tower to fight.

Zhao Hai also saw the two brothers on the monitor. There was nothing special about the two brothers, they were similar to the other Lich. Zhao Hai imagined them to have ferocious faces, but it was the opposite. They fairly looked like the other Lich. However, although they also had beards and looked like old people, the brothers could be said to be attractive old men.

After Zhao Hai confirmed the identity of the two brothers though Addison, they began to act. This time, Zhao Hai divided his men into two batches. A batch of 12 billion Undead, both from the Five Element Skeleton and Addison’s territories, were sent to surround the cities inside the Gibbon Brothers’ territory. These Undead would be under Megan’s command.

The other batch, a billion Undead which included Addison and the others, were sent to surround Soul Warrior City. The ordinary Undead were commanded by Lizzy while Zhao Hai and the others would be responsible for dealing with the Gibbon Brothers.

After arranging these things, Zhao Hai made everyone prepare to take action. He first had the undead surround all of the cities inside the Gibbon Brothers’ territory. All the Undead they came upon were captured and sent to the Space.

This process requires some time. This was 12 billion Undead, not 12 million. Releasing this much people would require a very long time. There was also the issue of setting ranks. Because of this, Zhao Hai and the others took 5 days before they finished.

After five days, when Megan was finally done with organizing the teams, Zhao Hai and the others departed. It didn’t take long before the team arrived above Soul Warrior City. The billion Undead had also surrounded the city, not even a drop of water could go through unnoticed.

Naturally, such a huge movement wouldn’t escape the Gibbon Brothers’ notice. The two quickly discovered Zhao Hai’s group as well as the multitude of Undead outside the city.

Upon seeing the situation, the Gibbon brothers quickly brought large quantities of Lich to fly out of the tower. This time, Zhao Hai didn’t hide as he just stood there with Addison and the Five Element Skeletons by his side.

The Gibbon Brothers looked at this and stared before a flash went through their eyes. One of them said, “May I know who His Excellency is? Why did you come to Soul Warrior City? Addison, what’s happening?”

Addison smiled faintly and said, “We are Young Master’s subordinates. Everything is the Young Master’s decision.” Then he said nothing else, showing that all of them had submitted to Zhao Hai.

The Gibbon Brothers turned to look at the Five Element Skeletons and began to feel restless. Then they carefully sized Zhao Hai up. Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t show his full image, he was still in his Dark Pharoah form. His aura was even hidden, one could just sense a rock in the place where he stood.

But this didn’t make the Gibbon Brothers underestimate Zhao Hai. The two bowed as one of them said, “May we know who Mister is? Why did you bring this many people to Soul Warrior City?”

Zhao Hai looked at the two and said, “There’s no need to act confused. I don’t believe that you’re clueless about why I came here. I just want to tell the two of you that starting today, the Resistance Army will submit to me, Zhao Hai. Refusing to accept will be met with death! You either submit to me or have your soul fires harvested.”

The Gibbon Brothers looked at each other, they didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this overbearing. Upon appearing, he immediately made his purpose clear, leaving the two with no moves to use. The brothers also knew that things weren’t going in their favor.

Chapter 1030: Soul Weapon

Not everyone could be overbearing, this was because it was a sign of overwhelming strength. It was an imposing manner, a kind of pressure brought upon by an absolute confidence in one’s strength. The same thing also applies when one was confident of dealing with the enemy.

But the imposing manner that Zhao Hai showed right now was due to his confidence in his strength. He was clear about his might, thus bringing confidence to his every word.

The Gibbon Brothers looked at each other. They were powerful experts of the Underworld, therefore they could feel Zhao Hai’s overbearing aura. They two didn’t hesitate as they both entered the Dark Mist.

The other Lich also followed the brothers in entering the Dark Mist. Upon seeing all the Lich vanish, Addison and the others couldn’t help but be on guard.

Zhao Hai coldly smiled and said, “This method is useless against me.” Then he waved his hand as an innumerable amount of Undead appeared in the Dark Mist. These Undead used magic attacks immediately after appearing.

After being met by attacks, the Lich immediately reappeared, causing them to be locked in battle. At this moment, Zhao Hai’s staff transformed into a huge bell, then he waved the bell making a huge gon sound. The sound waved across the dark mist and spread all around him. The Lich who heard the sound had a look of pain on their faces, their magic being sealed. A short while after that, cracks began appearing, sucking the pained Lich inside.

However, from beginning to the end, the Gibbon Brothers remained hidden. Even during Zhao Hai’s sound attack, the two were still one with the Dark Mist.

Zhao Hai’s eyes shone, then he smiled faintly and said, “Interesting, your weapons can actually resist by soul attacks.”

Just as Zhao Hai’s voice fell, the brothers suddenly appeared near Zhao Hai. Then the two proceeded to make an attack.

Upon seeing this, Addison’s expression changed, then he shouted, “Young Master, look out!”

However, this warning came too late. The Gibbon Brothers had already pierced Zhao Hai’s clothes with their weapons. When the weapons went through Zhao Hai’s clothes with little to no resistance, the Gibbon Brothers couldn’t help but be elated. They knew that it was impossible for people to survive upon meeting an attack from their weapon.

Clang! Clang! As the two weapons hit Zhao Hai’s body, it actually made a metallic sound. At this time, Zhao Hai turned around, his two arms capturing two things.

Upon seeing at Zhao Hai’s action, the Gibbon Brothers stared. Then their expressions changed. They discovered that their weapons were actually useless against Zhao Hai.

When they wanted to retrieve their weapons, two spatial rifts appeared in Zhao Hai’s hands. Then the brothers quickly lost contact with their weapons.

When they lost the connection to their weapons, the Gibbon Brothers were horrified. However, Zhao Hai didn’t allow them to recover. He moved his hand, retrieving the huge bell once more before gently swinging it. The faces of the Gibbon Brothers showed pain. Then two spatial rifts appeared right beside them, two giant hands extended from the rift, grabbing the two Lich Brothers in before vanishing.

Zhao Hai waved his hand, turning the bell back into his staff. Then Zhao Hai turned to Addison and the others and said, “Addison, I’ll leave this place to you. Remember, I want all the Undead alive.”

Addison and the others were shocked by Zhao Hai’s attack. Upon hearing the command, they couldn’t help but stare. Then Addison quickly said, “Yes, Young Master. Rest assured.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then his figure vanished. Addison let out a long breath before turning towards the Five Element Skeletons, he forced a smile and said, “Let’s get back to work. Let’s not make the Young Master make a move himself.”

Earth Skeleton looked at Addison and said, “Addison, I heard that you fought with the Young Master and managed to mutually exhaust each other. Is that true?”

To be honest, Addison didn’t know what to reply. Addison found out that Zhao Hai’s attacks had become more diversified and complex. If he were to fight the current Zhao Hai, then he knew that he wouldn’t last longer than the Gibbon Brothers. However, he really did fight Zhao Hai before, and both of them exhausted themselves. But if he said it right now, then nobody would believe him.

After thinking about it, Addison couldn’t help but smile bitterly at Earth Skeleton and said, “I fought with the Young Master for some time. But I think the Young Master is just testing my strength. Alright, let’s go back to work.” The group nodded before they carried an attack on Soul Warrior City.

At this time, Zhao Hai had entered the Space, naturally he wasn’t able to hear Addison’s words. If he managed to hear it, then even he wouldn’t be able to stop himself from smiling bitterly. He didn’t intend to test Addison’s strength, he truly had a hard time. That was the first time that Zhao Hai was able to experience that kind of battle, it was only later that he managed to find an appropriate fighting style.

Today’s battle was where Zhao Hai used his different methods. He used the Space to determine the locations of the Lich, then he changed his staff into a bell to send a soul attack. After that, his crystal body blocked the attack from the Gibbon Brothers before sending the weapons to the Space’s inventory. Then he used a soul attack once more to disorientate the Lich Brothers before sending them to the Space. This set of movements used a lot of Zhao Hai’s arsenal, but it allowed him to have full control of the battlefield. From the moment the Gibbon Brothers disappeared, everything was already under Zhao Hai’s control. What kind of attack the Lich would do had also been predicted.

This wasn’t the first time that Zhao Hai used this kind of method, he used these several times before in dealing with his enemies. But during those times, it didn’t feel great. It was only this time that Zhao Hai felt a type of control, it was very satisfying.

Zhao Hai didn’t immediately summon the Gibbon Brothers when he entered the Space, nor did he go and see the new weapons he gained. Instead, Zhao Hai closed his eyes and recalled the battle. His decisions on the battle was perfect. There weren’t any problems in his command, everything was methodical and without flaw.

Zhao Hai finally understood that this was the kind of combat he wanted. He always felt that there was something missing in his previous fights; now he knew what it was. This control wasn’t something that he felt before, and this battle finally opened his eyes.

Zhao Hai let out a long breath, then a smile slowly bloomed on his face as he opened his eyes. He walked to the villa to see Laura and the others looking at the monitor. The screen was currently showing Addison and the others seizing the Undead inside Soul Warrior City. Lizzy’s Undead army was coordinating with Addison’s group.

On the other hand, Megan’s army was also encircling the cities under the Gibbon Brothers’ control. The Undead inside those cities finally discovered that something wasn’t right.The cities launched their defensive formations while people were starting to look for reinforcements.

There was no need for Laura and the others to offer their help. Because of this, when Zhao Hai entered the room, Laura immediately welcomed him with a smile, “Brother Hai, your attack was very smooth.”

Zhao Hai agreed, he smiled faintly and said, “It is indeed very smooth. I need to thank you for the reminder. Otherwise, I wouldn’t have been aware of it in this fight.”

Laura smiled faintly and didn’t say anything else. Zhao Hai looked at her and said, “Alright, go help Meg prepare something good. It’s a special day, I feel like celebrating.” Laura nodded before she and Meg went to the kitchen to prepare some food. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai waved his hand and called the Gibbon Brothers over.

At the same time, Zhao Hai retrieved the weapons that the brothers used. The weapons caused Zhao Hai to stare. This was because these two weapons didn’t look like weapons at all. Instead, they looked like the fangs of a snake, curved, hollow, but quite sharp.

What made Zhao Hai more surprised was the fact that the two fangs weren’t very big, only a palm’s length. They look like two small transparent curved awls. If one didn’t have any idea, one would see it as a decoration instead.

At this time, the Space issued a prompt, “Unknown animal tooth detected, may be used as a weapon. It can attack physically and has the ability to target the soul. Can be nourished by one’s soul. Classified as Soul Weapons. Extracting weapon properties and supplementing it to the Blood Ghost Staff. Blood Ghost Staff has been upgraded and is now a soul weapon. Host can now nourish the Blood Ghost Staff in his soul. The longer it is nourished, the more compatible the host and the staff would be, further increasing the might of the staff in the process. Note, the soul weapon is the Host’s lifelong weapon. It would increase in strength as the host gets stronger.”

Zhao Hai gawked. This was his first time encountering soul weapons. After listening to the prompt, he knew that they were definitely good items.

Zhao Hai turned to the Gibbon Brothers and said, “Where did you obtain these things?”

One of the brothers answered, “Replying to the Young Master. We obtained these fangs after killing a dark beast named soul snake. It was a variant soul snake and we spent a lot of energy in order to kill it. The snake had no fiery soul and it disappeared upon dying, leaving only the two fangs on the ground. We wanted to bring it back and study it but we didn’t expect it to come in contact with our spiritual force and integrate into our souls, allowing us to use them as weapons. They are very convenient to wield.”

Chapter 1031: His Own Back Garden

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Then did you look for other snakes? To see if you can find another variant?”

The Gibbon Brothers nodded before replying, “We did, not only us, we also had our subordinates scour the area. However, we didn’t receive our desired result. We slaughtered a lot of snakes but didn’t find a variant. Not only soul snakes, we also looked for other dark creatures. But the final result was the same, we only obtained fiery souls, not soul weapons.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He can also guess that soul weapons should only come from rare variant souls snakes. Even if one looked for it, they might not necessarily meet one.

Zhao Hai returned the weapons to the Gibbon Brothers. Although the weapons were good items, they were now useless to Zhao Hai. Moreover, nobody else needed these things. He might as well return it to the pair or Lich.

Zhao Hai also asked the Gibbon Brothers whether they need anything. But Zhao Hai didn’t expect  that the two would just request for a place to research. Because of this, Zhao Hai led them to Wild Dragon Island and handed them over to Gimreden.

Since the Gibbon Brothers had soul weapons, their research was well-inclined towards the soul. This happens to be a lot of help towards GImreden’s study.

After sending the Gibbon Brothers off, Zhao Hai returned to Soul Warrior City. Then he proceeded to receive the GIbbon Brothers’ collection. One can say that the collection of the two brothers after all those years were quite a lot. It was even bigger than Gimreden’s. Unfortunately, they weren’t as good as Gimreden’s items. It didn’t even have a small beast skeleton.

At this time, the entire city had been seized by Addison and the others. All of the Undead inside the City were sent to the Space.

Zhao Hai didn’t manage them. Now that the Gibbon Brothers were inside the Space, there was no need to worry about the other people inside the territory. At this time, Zhao Hai was itching to visit the domain of the Dark Creatures. He wanted to see if he could meet a variant beast and gain more soul weapons.

However, Zhao Hai knew that this matter would need to be done in the future. He still needed to digest the Gibbon Brothers’ domain.

Now that the Gibbon Brothers were subdued, the Undead inside their territory became headless dragons. Additionally, Addison brought the other undead to attack. And with Megan surrounding the cities, the Undead couldn’t do anything. In less than one month, the territory became under Zhao Hai’s control.

Now that Zhao Hai had unified the Resistance Army, it can be said that he had officially become one of the three major forces in the Underworld. However, Zhao Hai also knew that the Resistance Army held the smallest territory. If not for the Blood River, then the Dark Temple would have already destroyed the Army. The Temple had more experts compared to the rebels. It was just that these Experts wouldn’t dare to cross the Blood River.

But Zhao Hai didn’t plan to expand the territory. Such action would just rouse other people’s suspicion. Moreover, Zhao Hai didn’t have any interest in the Neutral Alliance. What he was interested in was the Dark Temple. He wanted to know what kind of fellow controls the Dark Temple. If he can get to know who it was before he ascends, then that would be great.

Now that the Resistance Army has been unified, Zhao Hai’s next plan was to supposedly get some Blood Spirit Beasts from the Blood River. However, he actually changed his mind.

Since here was no need to immediate need for the Blood Spirit Beasts, Zhao Hai wanted to head towards the dark creature domain first. Actually, there were four powers in the Underworld. Besides the Dark Temple, Resistance Army, and the Neutral Alliance, there were the Darkness Magic Beasts.

However, Dark Creatures were different compared to the Undead. High-ranked Undead would command low-ranked Undead and make cities; Dark Creatures don’t do this. High-ranked beasts could still command low-ranked ones, but not all the time. These high-ranked beasts were usually alone. Only when dealing with a common enemy would these Dark Creatures group up.

Moreover, Dark Creatures have shortcomings compared to the Undead, their intellect wasn’t as developed. The average Undead couldn’t compare to a normal human, but Dark Beasts generally couldn’t compare to the average Undead.

This didn’t mean that the Dark Creatures lacked intelligent beings. It was basically the same as the Ark Continent and the Divine Realm’s beasts, high-ranked Magic Beasts could generally hold wisdom. However, forming intelligence for the Dark Creatures was much more difficult.

Zhao Hai had two reasons for wanting to visit the Dark Creatures’ Domain. First was to look at their strength and second was to see if he could find one or two variant beasts.

Zhao Hai expected that variant beasts would be very difficult to look for. He also asked the Gibbon Brothers more questions, such as special patterns on these variant beasts.

But much to Zhao Hai’s disappointment, variant beasts looked no different compared to ordinary beats. One couldn’t look for variant beasts just by relying on appearance. This increased the difficulty for Zhao Hai to find one of them.

However, Zhao Hai still wanted to try his luck. In any case, he could still be made aware of the strength of the Dark Creatures. Later on, Zhao Hai would treat the Underworld as his own backyard. Naturally, one would have to properly know what was inside their own land.

It can be said that everything that happened in the Resistance Army went on without nobody outside knowing. This was because Zhao Hai had been very silent in eating up the Resistance Army.

First Zhao Hai subdued the Five Element Skeletons, then after that he took care of their domain. Everything was taken care of in secrecy. Afterwards, Zhao Hai also took care of the Gibbon Brothers. Although the operation was large, nobody managed to escape and alert the others.

Because of this, nobody outside from those who were involved were aware of Zhao Hai’s unification of the Resistance Army. To both the Dark Temple and the Neutral Alliance, there was no force left in the Resistance Army that had the ability to unify it. Therefore, they lessened the attention they paid to the group.

But even if they had eyes on the Resistance Army, it was still useless. At this time, all of the Undead moving around the Army’s territory were Zhao Hai’s subordinates. These people were loyal to Zhao Hai, so naturally nothing would spill to the outside.

After another month of reorganization, the entire Resistance Army was fully integrated. The Resistance Army still looked like a loose collective from the outside. Undead still made trades on each city, making an outsider think that nothing has changed compared to before.

After integrating the entire Resistance Army, Zhao Hai carried on to his next plan, taking a stroll in the Dark Creature’s territory.

Zhao Hai called Addison over to the Space. By this point, Addison had become the leader of the entire Army. Zhao Hai ordered Addison to strengthen the Undead. And with the help of the Space’s plants, a few more people had been promoted to King-level. Because of this, the Resistance Army wasn’t weakened, instead it became even more formidable. Among those who were promoted were Guli and Jiang Zheng.

Zhao Hai had never been a stingy person. He treated his subordinates really well. Guli and Jiang Zheng were his earliest subordinates in the Underworld, naturally he would give them special attention.

Zhao Hai set up a meeting inside a city in the Space. There weren’t a lot of people who were invited. There were only Addison, Guli, Jiang Zheng, and the Five Element Skeletons. The others basically didn’t have any qualifications to see Zhao Hai.

After Addison and the others entered the Space, they immediately gave Zhao Hai a salute. Zhao Hai waved his hand, making them sit down. After everyone had taken their seat, Zhao Hai said, “The Resistance Army has been unified, however, I don’t want to wage war immediately. In the meantime, I want to see the Dark Creatures. So tell me everything you know about the Darkness Beasts.”

Addison gawked when he heard this. He didn’t enter the Space for more than a month and Zhao Hai didn’t bother managing what was happening outside. Because of this, he had no idea about soul weapons. Now that Zhao Hai suddenly wanted to explore the Dark Creatures’ territory, Addison couldn’t help but feel strange. Zhao Hai told him before that he would collect Blood Spirit Beasts after unifying the Undead. Addison couldn’t understand why Zhao Hai suddenly changed his plan.

However, Addison still answered, “Young Master, we don’t have a lot of understanding regarding the Dark Creatures. The Dark Creature’s domain isn’t a good place to visit, there are very strong beings there, even those on my level aren’t very rare. Because of this, we rarely explore the place. Why does Young Master want to go there?”

Zhao Hai proceeded to tell them about soul weapons, then after that Zhao Hai said, “I think these soul weapons would have great use for us. Therefore, I want to visit the Dark Creature’s Domain to look and see if I can find these variant dark beasts. If I can find one, then that would be great. I want to raise a batch of these beasts inside the Space. We’ll see if we can farm soul weapons for our future use.”

Upon hearing this, Addison finally understood why Zhao Hai wanted to visit the Dark Creatures, so he nodded and said, “Although we don’t have that much understanding with regards to Dark Creatures, we have ideas about where the high-ranked beasts are located. As long as the Young Master makes a map, I can point where they are.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Good, then point them for me.” Then he gestured to the monitor, displayed on the screen was a map of the Dark Creatures’ domain.

Chapter 1032: Soul Snake

Zhao Hai was a man who was determined to follow his decisions, so he would follow through in going to the Dark Creatures’ domain. Naturally, it was impossible to do so without preparation. While Addison and the others were dealing with the Undead, Zhao Hai released blood needles to explore the territory of the Dark Creatures. Because of this, the land was already mapped by the Space.

After seeing that Zhao Hai was prepared, Addison didn’t hesitate as he quickly went towards the map. Then he pointed to a few positions and then drew some circles. After that, he introduced each beast one by one and relayed their areas of activity.

Zhao Hai discovered that the magic beasts in the Underworld were just similar to the ones in the Ark Continent or in the Divine Realm. But although the latter two realms also produced variant beasts, but they weren’t that special.

After Addison pointed out each high-rank beast territory, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown a bit. The beasts that Addison pointed out were all located on the outskirts of the domain, there was no information about the central areas. Moreover, there were no less than 10 high-level beasts in this area, and from what Addison said, all of them had the same strength as him. In other words, the Dark Creatures on the outskirts of the territory were enough to contend against the Resistance Army!

If the strength of the outskirts was equal to the Resistance Army, then what of the center? When he thought about it, Zhao Hai’s brows couldn’t help but wrinkle even more.

Addison saw Zhao Hai and couldn’t help but feel awkward. He felt apologetic, he wasn’t able to provide much help in this matter.

Zhao Hai recovered after some time, then he looked at Addison and said, “The Dark Creature Territory seem to be very dangerous. But that doesn’t matter, I don’t think the magic beasts could do anything to me anymore. While I go there, I will hand the Resistance Army over to you. Remember to keep low-key while I’m not here. I don’t want a conflict with the Dark Temple yet.”

Addison nodded and said, “Young Master, rest assured. We know what to do.” Addison didn’t bother telling Zhao Hai that he would send guards to protect him. With Zhao Hai’s strength, nobody was qualified to be his guard.

Zhao Hai waved his hand, sending Addison and the others out of the Space. After the others left, Zhao Hai looked at the map and pondered.

The territory of the Dark Creatures was very strange. The area also had tall bone mountains. But besides those, there were also bone forests. Naturally, these forests weren’t made up of plants, it was a collection of beast bones. At the same time, there were also bone swamps! These swamps were an amalgamation of blood and bones. Apart from that characteristic, they didn’t differ from swamps of the other planes. Of course, its function was still left to be found out.

There were countless green lights on the Dark Creature Domain map. Zhao Hai was aware that these lights were magic beasts. From the number of magic beasts, Zhao Hai knew that he would be diving into a pool of dragons. However, Zhao Hai still had the confidence to head there.

At this time, Laura and the others returned to Zhao Hai’s side. As the group looked at the monitor, Laura frowned and said, “Brother Hai, you want to go there?”

Zhao Hai knew that Laura and the others would be worried about his well-being, so he comforted them, “I’ll be fine. After fighting with Addison and my recent breakthrough, nothing in the Underworld could threaten me anymore. I just have the feeling that soul weapons would have great use for us. If I don’t look for them, then my heart won’t be settled.”

Laura smiled faintly, she was actually confident in Zhao Hai. But as his wife, she couldn’t help but worry. However, she didn’t plan to stop him. She knew that once Zhao Hai decided on something, then nobody would be able to stop him.

Of course, if she didn’t want him to go, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t go. However, Zhao Hai would surely be restless. At the same time, Laura also knew that Zhao Hai wouldn’t be in grave danger. Therefore, she didn’t plan to stop him.

Lizzy looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, we can just send an army there and flatten it out. There won’t be any need for you to go by yourself.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t worry, the Underworld would later be our back garden. Naturally, I would have to inspect it first. Also, if we capture all of those magic beasts now, then what would happen in the future? Let’s have them continue living in the Underworld. It’s possible that they could only produce variant beasts here, providing us with a supply of soul weapons. We are still unsure whether the Space could do the same.”

Laura and the others agreed. They had stocked up on knowledge from the computers lately. After using the computer for some time, they were able to expand their knowledge.

They knew that the Space wasn’t very flexible. Take magic beast for example, almost all of the magic beasts grown inside the Space were mostly identical. It wasn’t easy for them to mutate inside the Space.

The Space could produce variant plants, but it would be after transferring an ordinary plant to the Hell Space. Variation in the original Space would be practically impossible. In other words, variant plants and animals would only come up during a change in environment. And in the end, this was only a possibility, not a consistent process.

The Hell Space was merely like the Underworld at this point. If magic beasts were brought to the Hell Space, then it was impossible for it to mutate. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t bother catching magic beasts in hopes of breeding variant ones.

However, the Space’s identical production of beasts also held a certain advantage. If Zhao Hai manages to capture a variant beast and sent it to the Space, then later on, its descendants or those who were bought from the Space would be variants as well. As long as Zhao Hai captures a beast capable of producing a soul weapon and sent it to the Space, then the Space would be able to produce soul weapons.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “The Gibbon Brothers obtained their soul weapon from a soul snake. Therefore, the first place I want to visit would be their lair.”

As he said that, Zhao Hai gestured over to the map to a region that Addision drew. Addison told Zhao Hai that this region belonged to soul snakes. Moreover, Addison also expressed that wasn’t confident in defeating the most powerful soul snake.

Laura and the others followed the direction of Zhao Hai’s finger and to a region on the map. Their brows couldn’t help but wrinkle. The place Zhao Hai pointed to had a lot of green dots, meaning that there were plenty of soul snakes present. At the same time, the frowns also stemmed from the fact that women generally hated snakes.

Zhao Hai looked at the women and smiled, “Alright, there’s no need to worry about me. These things are not a threat. I’ll take a look first, there’s no need to wait for me.”

The women nodded before Zhao Hai’s figure disappeared from the Space. The next moment, Zhao Hai reappeared inside the lair of the soul snakes.

The domain of the soul snakes was inside a skeleton forest. Large bones were seen everywhere. Zhao Hai looked through the bones and saw that they weren’t anything special. They were unlike the huge bones that he wanted to collect for the Space. There were even some bones that he couldn’t understand, while some had existed for a long time and had weathered through time.

.Naturally, these large bones were more sturdy than ordinary ones. However, they didn’t reach the level of those in Zhao Hai’s collection. Zhao Hai knew that these skeletons only belonged to powerful magic beasts, completely different from the ones he collects. Just like the difference between pig and dragon bones.

Zhao Hai didn’t fly too high, just hovering slowly half a meter from the ground. He didn’t plan to walk on the ground either since the floor of the forest was completely covered in blood. Since Zhao Hai didn’t want his foot stained, he can only hover in the air.

While flying, Zhao Hai also used his spiritual force to scan the surroundings. Although the skeleton forest wasn’t anything special, Zhao Hai managed to spot some soul snakes in the majority of the bones. Soul snakes ranged from more than ten meters long to those less than half a meter. Zhao Hai also saw something peculiar about the skin of these snakes.

Their skin looked very much like bones. They were gray and covered the entire body. Ordinary eyes would find it hard to differentiate bones from the snakes. More importantly, the snakes could mask their souls, making it very difficult to find them in this forest.

Zhao Hai captured some snakes for the Space, all of them having different body shapes. They were those who wanted to attack him.

Although Zhao Hai saw tens of thousands of snakes, he wasn’t able to see one snake that was different compared to the others. These snakes look very much the same, even if there were variants among them, Zhao Hai wouldn’t be able to find out.

Zhao Hai didn’t worry too much and just calmly proceeded. He kept playing attention to the snakes he came upon. At this point, those who attacked him got bigger and bigger in size. However, they still weren’t a concern for Zhao Hai. What Zhao Hai was currently looking for was a king-level soul snake.

While looking at the Space’s map, Zhao Hai imagined that the soul snakes’ domain wasn’t very large. But after coming over, Zhao Hai discovered that the place was actually huge. It was not smaller than the black wasteland and the carrion swamp combined.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect the region to be this big. It was at this point that Zhao Hai began to worry a bit. The main point of his visit was to find variant soul snakes. With a region this big, if he wanted to explore it all, then wouldn’t he be stuck here for a year? While he thought about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get a headache.

But Zhao Hai had no way to solve this problem, so he could only walk and pay attention. Unconsciously, Zhao Hai had already entered the high-ranked area. The snakes here were getting stronger and stronger. However, Zhao Hai still wasn’t threatened, he didn’t care about the attacks.

Five hours went by and Zhao Hai suddenly felt a strong spiritual force. This spiritual force gave Zhao Hai a very cold feeling. It seems like an ice cold snake had just slithered into his body.

After a little pause, Zhao Hai guessed that this must be a Snake King. Zhao Hai didn’t retaliate and just proceeded forward. He discovered that the spiritual force wasn’t specifically aimed towards him. It was probably an unconscious release of spiritual force.

As he continued on his way, Zhao Hai increased his speed. He felt the spiritual force getting stronger and stronger. This meant that he was getting closer to the source.

Zhao Hai also knew the reason why the other party had yet to find him. This was because the enemy’s spiritual force wasn’t as delicate as Zhao Hai’s. Moreover, the other party didn’t expect someone to enter his territory. But now, Zhao Hai began to sense that if he proceeded further, the other party would begin to be alert.

But Zhao Hai didn’t stop. He wanted to meet a strong soul snake, so naturally he wouldn’t retreat. Not only did Zhao Hai proceed, he also condensed his spiritual force and began radiating it out. Zhao Hai felt that it wouldn’t be too long before the other side comes to know about his presence.

Sure enough, after Zhao Hai released his spiritual force, the other party immediately discovered him. The enemy’s spiritual force flared up like tide. It was ice-cold, full of killing intent as it pressed towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai felt that he was staring straight into the eyes of a giant python. His body seems to be hit by waves upon waves of cold air.

Zhao Hai raised his spiritual force. He was like a piece of rock in the middle of the ocean. Wind and waves might constantly hit him, but he remained unfazed. Despite the deluge of spiritual force sent by the other side, Zhao Hai still kept moving forward.

Zhao Hai’s action angered the opposite party. The enemy increased their spiritual force even further, fully intent on turning Zhao Hai into a meat paste!

However, such a pressure was useless against Zhao Hai. With how powerful his soul was, no matter how much Zhao Hai was suppressed, his soul would remain unmoving. He proceeded as though nothing was affecting him.

At this moment, Zhao Hai could feel that the enemy was no less than ten li(5km) away from him. The enemy also knew about this. After hearing a roar, Zhao Hai felt that the enemy began to make its move!

Zhao Hai heard this roar and couldn’t help but stare. This was because he felt a faint pressure with this roar. Soul snakes shouldn’t be able to do this. Was this Snake King a variant?